Voices collide, the storm and the flame. Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive. In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
cheers to the friends the story gets stranger it never
psyche's show
I'll explain in just one second. Hold on one second.
One second.
Hear me now?
Okay, I'll explain. Hold on.
And it said like it said like I can't be posted so I don't know if it's my filter
And that's like considered like an ethnic word or something. Hey, look you see I got a light too
Little bit brighter you can hear me. Okay good. Yeah, I got a new bright light. How do you like that?
Unclick the yeah, I
Might be I might have to do like the just take off the moderation on
Community defaults. No, they're not even help. They're not even that's not even on shit
I
Don't know. I just like you might want it might what like I don't know if it will start blocking your messages or something
Hi guys
Okay
Yeah, well, but it doesn't have I don't think that's on like the review it's not the box is unchecked
I don't know I mean like my blockboards
Let's hope it doesn't issue for you, okay?
Who guys how are you?
So did everyone even see the
yesterday
Yeah, I might be yesterday. I did my interview with Alexandra. Well actually she said that her her main channel was
She wasn't able to stream from that
So the last minute was for kind of from our backup channel, which is alexander mayors al ex and d r a m a y
Ers at alexander mayors
Yes, I saw you there Christine. Thank you for being there. Thank you everyone who came there. Thank you so much
I saw quite a few people there really
Supporting and
Just giving good vibes and taking care of some of you know the inevitable trolls that are gonna follow
Yeah, Alexander and I both are both like we're astrology twins
Yeah, we can still watch it is on it's on my community wall the link to the the entire interview and
It was cut two hours. It was great
You just vibe get along share message. It was a good show. Yeah
Just want to thank Alexandra again for the opportunity like you know, she did invite me for a your three-part series to
Discuss some interesting interesting topics about astrology and tarot
She is amazing like absolutely and
Very kind-hearted and I just appreciate
You know
In a time when like not everybody is always supporting. Hey, what's up, Barry?
Yeah, I'd love to collab more and we're gonna do the next two and I can't wait
You gave me just you know the next couple Sundays. Let me get my glasses off. Hey, Barry. How are you?
No, I like Barry again. I've decided I like Barry the turtle again
I got my glass. See now I have a reason to have my glasses on my eyes. You can see my eyes very clearly through these now.
So anyway, I like very the turtle again. I was like, you know,
I might bring out the, I have these poster size pictures of your genitals that I have on my wall,
but when I got mad at you, I just put them away. So now I'm gonna bring it out. I'm just kidding. I don't have it.
This quick. I'm not sure if I like this quick. I don't like the position of the camera. You see underneath my chin. Yeah, I know. I'll fix it, hold on.
I just need to like raise it up, raise it up, hold on, I've got an idea, okay, I'll get
it more in my face, hold on, get it right, yeah, I'll get it right, it's in the museum
It's in a museum style, uh, you know, frame
You can see I'm a chin which is like not attractive. Oh, okay. Hold on. I'll put on this full box. I guess
It's not the guy
Oh my god, my dirty table. Oh shit, my back fell off.
Well, if you just want to see my dirty table.
That's the back roll on it. Extremely embarrassing.
You're seeing, look, it's like, not tall enough.
You want to wrench, no one's going to mess with you bisquick, but who is bisquick? I don't remember who bisquick is
Yeah, my mods here are on top of like if somebody's like doing something out right
My mom some of my mods have even done what I did, but I had to talk to them
I was like if I
If I time somebody out for a day don't tell them I pretend like but
I did have problems with rogue mods. I think I have all good people here. Is this better christine?
Someone that started a channel 2025. Yeah, I need like at least 2024. That's when I at least started this one
But I had you know on YouTube for several years, but I didn't even chat written until about two years ago
Started chatting it was like into the 90 baby on say
Universe I don't so much one one live stream his name is wine box poppy and I'm sure like maybe nobody knows who he is
But he actually had like 50,000 subscribers
He's a comedian
named Mark Karski. He's really, really funny. He's like kind of, he likes motorcycles, he's like bald, he has tattoos,
but he's like kind of has the feminine side to it. I don't know, he's funny.
But he stopped doing the live streams, but he used to do them every day.
But he makes commentary videos, regular videos, and those do so well.
This quick? No. No demanding rentals. Christine will not force to cue you.
I watched Heather? Who's Heather?
Okay, yeah, Christine is in charge.
Listen to Christine, you don't want to mess with my mods,
you know, the mods, my mods here are very,
they're very powerful, very powerful people.
And let's have all of you here.
So, let's see, you love summer, Barry?
Well, maybe she'll make an appearance.
I hope, I've seen her on her show recently.
You know, it's like.
It's hard for me to go on others. I mean, I did I love going to summer show and chatting with her
But I'm not I was like wow
I there's a lot of people because I was subscribing to all the people on my subscribers list with like
With like subscribers on a show that's like wow
There's so many people that's like I should like go see how to all these people like slowly
But it's like I've had negative experiences going into some chats
Very I mean, what's that what's happened very and very and I are friends again
And it's like we really are still it's good. I got finally started in my nails. Like really clean
I don't see like one that could be it. I don't know maybe there's oh
Heather Gilmore was the 90 day fiance show okay. Well, Heather Gilmore's a guy was a prison. Ooh, was that a recent one or was that a
I remember like a few people from prison in that show you have a question of what kind of
Table top you recommend free to buy. Oh kind of laptop
Okay, laptop. Well, I would say
If you're like, you know, you said you're concerned about like laptops
There's something, actually, there's these mini computers now, right?
Unless you're like a really, yeah, a mini computer.
Yeah, so unless you're really into the gaming and stuff and you need like a, you know, the
big fan for the gaming and the, I don't know if you're worried about any of that.
So basically, you can create a great mini computer for not very much, you can just get,
you know, get a nice monitor for not very much anymore, it'll cost very much anymore.
Um, what else do you need?
Yeah, just get out get out
Yeah, when I just got one of these
Get one of these get this meta quest. It's a wireless VR thing get this get this thing
Theresa get it you get did you want to like being you wanted to go to the middle of like
magical in a forest and like meditate like
Yeah, you can do it with that
So I would recommend that
But in that also, you know, you don't really need it
It doesn't need to connect it anything and so how are you gonna be from the 98 community and not know Heather Gillespie?
Okay, so KZ I
Haven't watched 90 day in like two years probably two years, but so what I don't remember
I don't think they have most of people on love after lock up with big
You know prison people I just say and I know the guy John
you know the guy from England on the show had a prison record the guy Paul had
he was like in prison for arson and
There's like one crazy guy with like the Russian chick baria and he was like he was Jeffrey and he
He's in prison for like the rest of his life and there's Darcy and Stacy. Oh my god. Did you see their show too?
Oh, okay, so, see, I do know, oh yeah, so she was on the,
yeah, hey what's up, hold on, hey wild German lady.
I'm sorry, I'm kind of rambling,
obviously if I'm missing chat.
Oh, you want the link, KZ, hold on.
Did it get Lenore, Doug Lenore, yes.
Yeah, but Kristian recommends that like a mini PC as well.
You can get one on Amazon, I just had to get it on Amazon
because then it's like you can send it back.
Hey Barry, KZ Van from a Raw Brex channel.
He knows why
Casey you have been banned from this channel various letting you know
You know why?
Thank You Barry
I saw Barry actually yesterday on a show,
like he was on a show, oh, that's why she was funny.
Barry, why don't you come on my panel,
and you can come see how my panel looks like,
that's why it is.
Well, and just KZ wants to come up.
I mean, I like, enjoy having KZ on
as much as Rob Racks, but I'm just kidding, KZ, you're funny.
Let me get the link up.
Hold on.
Barry, did you donate?
Keep going up the panel
Well, it's your wallet ready at the
Yeah, I had a I'm having another coffee
If I got it, I think it's like Samman's babe company. So it's called Papa's or oh
My gosh, right? It's not it's not an attractive angle. I'm pursuing
It's called Papa's or
Last time I was up I raged quit because Alex brother was talking shit like a or a kek brother. I don't know
rage quit from what?
I did, I don't, I don't really rage quit.
I just get, I just get like irritated and like,
I can't talk on the post, the show's like going
because especially with black people, they're,
oh my God, I was on the good pussy show
and I, I was, I sat up there for like 35 minutes.
She probably like brought me up on the panel.
She just kept bringing me on and I'll take me off real quick.
And then she brought me on like this, left me on there.
But I, like, I sat there for like three,
and then I was like, and then Birdo was in the chat.
It's not, I'm trying to be racist.
I'm just saying, it's community.
And the beef sector and stuff like that, they just yell.
They all said like, that's why he sounds like that.
He was there.
Again, and I don't know why.
I'm not like that.
My house is not that dirty.
I'm sorry, people are saying, not sure why it matters.
Like they all coming to your house.
Right, it's like, and if they were coming,
like I would like,
and you're recording every little thing,
but I'd love to have somebody come over and hang out,
but I'd probably really hang out at my house.
I don't think, I just feel like it's like a lunch and stuff,
because it's like, what, I don't know.
I just think I'm gonna do a smile or a relish or something,
but I don't know, it's like the people have cat allergies.
I like being on my own, is there any way to change chat
to where it shows the names instead of,
I know that's no trees, I don't know why,
oh Wild German, oh I don't know Wild German Lee
because it's YouTube doing it to like random channels
that are monetized, I don't know why they're doing it.
Rouse is dirty, and I can't say it's okay,
it's my house, the thing is it's like.
It was really kind of dirty, but I've been like really cleaning it for like a few weeks and it's like pretty
I'm proud of myself, but it's like it's pretty good
It's like and so I'm in the process of that and I'm in the process of organizing to make it less messy
because it's like now it's like clean and then it's like now
I'm just like trying to like keep it from being messy. I'm a little bit messy, but it's like I'm doing an okay job
But it's like oh my god, and then it's like they were like screaming like oh my god
What I like is you know I was telling them like they're say oh your cat all your cats are just running around
They're not neutered and something like well yes
They are new like like two of the males are
Let me see hold on. No the male is neutered one of the males is neutered and both of the females are spayed
right and it is
Tricks is not neutered
But it's also he's not gonna get pregnant. He's doesn't he's not a wanderer. He's not I mean he's not like a
Don't know there's other cats that like I haven't fixed and they get all big and scary
like Tricks is just like, I don't know.
But then this lady bathroom kept calling in,
she goes, oh my God, I offered him free bed
and I was gonna have a friend drive out there.
I don't remember ever anyone trying to arrange that with me,
but it's like she can say that now and stuff too.
She also didn't like me, like I don't think she ever liked me.
She's always like mean.
And so I don't know if I would trust her
sending someone over with like knives around my cat.
You talk to you too about the names in the chat
the change is here to stay.
Handles could be duplicated too easily,
but your channel name can't be the same as someone else's.
Yeah, it's like, and you can change both of those things
every couple weeks, but it can't just be the same
if somebody else's channel name,
only the handles can change,
and so they're making it so you can't just like,
change your handle all the time,
and like, you'd be fake people or something,
but you still get multiple countless,
it's just like, there's always ways to do it.
Hi, but I had a really good breakfast. It was like a cheese bagel with cream cheese and then a hot coffee with a lot of cream in it, and then a hash brown, and I still have one iced coffee left.
Hi guys, hey Jenny, Jen Jen. I'm sorry if I ever really think life's lady, but he's name.
Now, instead of looking at the, yeah, I don't think my reading glass is anymore because
I'm not looking close to the tablet, but the TV, it's like, I'm pretty good at reading
it, I can see it pretty clearly, but not always, and so, and also, I get half stoned, and then
I, don't mean to misread, but I know you don't have to worry about anything, it's just annoying
that name is there, and so Lucy, what's up, Trips?
Is Trips, Trips, what's Trips, I don't know, Tripsnip?
So I think he doesn't pay attention enough here,
or elsewhere, do you see the, yeah,
yeah, who has, which troll has a wrench,
or is it Barry the turtle, or who?
I don't see the troll with a wrench.
I'm not gonna take them off.
I know the wild German lady is not a troll. She's awesome
Charisma here in Hanna's is fine.
Charisma is a...
Yeah, oh Charisma. I like Charisma.
All I have to say is Charisma like always supported me so
like always like I never I never and really never like
She's... I never had any problems
Is it chippants? Is it chippantsip? Oh hey, chippantsip.
Are you the one that does the videos?
Thank you, I would.
Or let's flip a trip quicker.
Oh my god. Hard enough to say the one I'm expecting.
Not high.
Trip, trip, flip it.
I don't know. They're funny.
Charisma is a free control.
Yes, I think she had a membership once a charisma. Can you come on panel and talk to me? I think I have talked to her
She before and I mean I kicked her off. You just you did like
If I would be pretty bad charisma, can you come on and talk to me for a minute and
Yeah, I just want to like say we have a nice relationship
and
Even if I I don't know you've never done anything to me like I
Oh, you're not sure okay
Charisma, can you come up and talk to me and just show like,
even if you're a troll, you're a fan of this show
and I've been supportive.
This is, I look a lot at what people say
because a lot of people say negative things
and if she was like a troll,
I would expect like try to like drop some horrible things,
but she never did.
Yeah, let me cool the talk stickers like I've talked to you before right you're okay. Okay. He's gonna be like go out
But hey, they had have we had a problem or fight or anything
But have you did you didn't hide anybody did you or like do anything? Oh
Haven't seen easy around for a while. I know you guys were fighting
But, I don't know, we at the museum, we're kind of on and off, because...
I've heard her on panels. She came on panels, I remember.
And she was like, I think I had to kick her off the panel.
Because she might have said a little bit too strong language, right?
Christmas, do you remember that?
I believe it's okay. I believe that certain women will like, you know, if there are these troll,
like I'm not saying, I'm saying if there's a woman, but even when she was a troll, not, you know,
she could, she would find certain people attractive and like wouldn't, wouldn't maybe troll everybody.
I remember her, she's like, she's Hispanic. She's like, and she was like, yeah, I remember one time.
Yeah
Because I remember I had one person like
As if guys and she bothered anybody in the chat I
Think and I think people were kept blocking her so I made her a mod so she was good luck
Just trying to control your panel calling anyone troll. She doesn't like
to just connect
From your support let her what?
I'm not going to ever read things out loud again.
Okay. Yeah, I'm sorry if I don't.
So do you guys want to hear another song I made? I made a few songs.
Okay, but I made these songs in such an interesting way.
So this one is like kind of the face of my astrology.
I hope it doesn't fall. I hope it doesn't fall.
So I'm a capricorn rising in the sun and the Aquarius moon, and this song really focuses on that, I'll be sure of it.
Very back.
and sun voice of the dawn where the climbs begun words like pillars fire in my
hands I build the temple on shifting sands
It's a little, I'm sorry, I don't know, there's two versions of all the songs, so I don't know, I like the last one, it's a little bit, I don't know, I like the, I'll explain.
That has to do with, like, myostrology and all these different things about myostrology.
So I'll tell you, there's something called Sabian Symbol.
So every degree of the Zodiac, or every house, every, like, it's like, the Zodiacs broke
it up into 360 degrees, and so someone took each degree and they, like, did, like, some,
like, you know, meditation, channeling, whatever, and they came up with, like, a couple sentences
each degree and so they're called the Sabian symbol and so I went and I
compiled all the all the Sabian symbols and then I had them
Put into like one image
That's that image and then it had been I have all the I fit on my wall all the story
Yeah, I mean yeah, we are all trolls in a way even the trolls to be allowed a panel or the chat
I think so I think so unless they're like, but I don't want to troll me
I like because I like should be like I've already been initiated just like enough trolling
I mean, it's like and I don't want to like
Have to troll back
Hi spunky, what's up girl?
I didn't think Spongebob might like that song and like work too.
I think I'll offer a new service.
If you guys want me to do your symbols, do your astrology symbols and I can make you a song
and I can make you the image and stuff like that.
I'll figure it out but you know guys who hire me oh just check out my website you can like just hire
So waiting for what yeah pretty good when I come up on the panel easy
How much well it's like if
Okay, it was listed one thing. I think it's like $15 an hour. I'd like that lists it on my website right now
Like it and has like a bookie thing. I don't know if the bookie thing is working on there
But you can bet I think if you're like a you know, if you're a member of my or like a mod of this channel
You know, if you contact me, it's like
We can work single reason
I think it'd be be less be happy probably to do like
For my members, you know
How much but how much are you talking about? How much for a
How much for a re oh like an hour on the phone or like that's specific like making making the all that stuff making or making the
The specific saving and symbol and stuff like that. I'll just special I'll just special for members like members you want to do it, okay?
Yeah, okay, you just have to it's a semi or birthday then
I want to give you a big discount because, you know, you've been really generous.
Yeah, oh yeah, the Sabian symbols, yeah, I'll take the Sabian symbols and I'll like, you know, I'll put it into like, so, because that, that's all astrologically based, like that, all those symbols and everything in that, and it turned out there were some really cool things like the peacock, there's like a peacock that's wounded, but it's like it's still, it's still a...
strong or still like you know beautiful and stuff like I like that and then I
couldn't think of it because I had a wound on its chest right. I was like I have that beautiful peacock right no I love peacocks
though and yeah thank you so much yeah I think yeah I'm thinking that I would I'm
gonna I would charge like you know
Like 25 for that, but you know, I was but I for you I do for like
I'll do the whole thing. I'll do extra. I'll do a lot. So I'll do thoughts. I'll conclude a reading with it, too
I'll make it worth your while
It's one of the first people to first people to buy I think
Like you know, hopefully I can get some testimonials. You saw Peacock today. Yeah
So I can like tell you a little bit about what this
Says basically, I mean, it's so it's so interesting. I mean, it's like, you know, it makes me sound like a little bit
I don't want to stop. I know I do believe like we're here
We're all special and I think we're here for purposes of missions and like with energy and maybe a lot of it based on astrology
It's like a hint as to what this like our purpose is or what we're supposed to do, right?
Here I'm doing this picture
I'll explain it
Okay, so
But it said with it the story it has is the pilgrim of storm and banner
So it says, in a world where stars churned like eyes of prophecy, a solitary figure
immersed.
Psyche, the pilgrim of Storm and Banner.
He was not born to whisper in shadows, but to walk unveiled, like the girl bathing beneath
the moonlight, which is one of the Sabian symbols, what it's called, I know it sounds
kind of weird, stripped of allusions.
The heavens the heavens roar I need my other glasses on I'm sorry this is too
Too small
Perfect
The heavens roared as a thunderstorm split the night sky, each flash of lightning with
a surge of emotion, sudden, electric, impossible to ignore.
The storm lived in Psyche's chest and threw him at rolled-across villages and cities alike,
awakening sleepers and shaking tyrants.
Each step was a word, each breath a mantra.
His pilgrimage was not to conquer, but to ascend through speech and ritual, carrying the sacred burden of the seeker.
So each one of these paragraphs is like one of the Saviour symbols, or a couple of them, like, okay?
At the mountain crest, Psyche raised a crimson banner, bearing the heart of fire.
This was not conquest, but love made defiance, wherever the banner waved, the broken and
the outcast gathered, seeing in his folds a province that beauty could rally nations.
Kneeling nearby was the cloistered warrior, sword laid before an altar, psyche chewed board
the spout, power must serve something greater than itself, his ambition was chained to devotion,
his drive consecrated by duty.
Below, an artist's vision crystallizes the statues of flesh and stone, the dream becoming
fleshed, ideals materializing.
This was Psyche's gift to take prophecy and render it real so others could touch the untouchable.
A gavel hovered where dawn broke across the horizon, Saturn's judgment ushering in the
morning of the new age.
Psyche's trials were many.
but in each verdict she bore the role of Judge and Herald, the one who declared the old has ended,
the new has come. At the edge is a woman pleaded before the tribal chief,
lightning burning in her eyes, psyche new for voice, for it was his own, the cry for justice,
for innocence, for the protection of the tribe. His revolution was not raged, but compassion weaponized.
Wonders crossed the Starlet River under Neptune's stream.
They carried strange tongues and foreign fires, but Psyche welcomed them as kids.
For in his realm all who sought belonging were immigrants, and no border could deny the spiritual
tide.
A pilgrim held aloft an autumn leaf glowing like ember.
Psyche looked upon it and saw eternity, death not as finality, but as turning of the seasons,
transformation, encoded in the veins of a leaf. In the distance, an old sea captain rocked on a
porch, pipe aglow, eyes on horizons long sailed. This was Psyche's destiny to guide, not as a conqueror.
but as elder captive wisdom master of stories. At the corner of the vision, a peacock shimmered
with boiled blues and emeralds, its chest scarred yet proud. The peacock's wound was Psyche's wound,
mocked Envy's, wounded for brilliance, but also his healing, for by standing radiance,
despite scars, he taught others to shine. I think it's pretty beautiful.
I think, I mean, there's a lot to that too.
What happened to the channel?
It feels different, oh, in a good way.
Oh, thank you Spunky for that, thank you so much.
Yeah, and I will get that to you.
I'll get that to you soon.
I just need your, you know, your personal information.
You can do, run your astrology.
And I'll also give, I'll just tell you a lot of like,
get this astrological reports and like stuff like,
I'll tell you a lot of good stuff.
Yeah, yeah, I'll actually run. Yeah, I'll do I'll do like a I want to report you with like some focus on
I've an idea. Uh-huh. We surprise. I'll be surprised bonus, okay?
Hello, hello you guys too like I do have a you guys are interested in that I
Think for
For members
and mods, it's 6.15 and then if you're like not a member or a mod, $20 and you can catch up at...
if you're interested.
Oh, I hope they mean better. It's like it's not gonna be better to some people, but I think it's a lot better for me because I
need to have like
No, I'm good mental thing. I can't just be like
I don't know. I think I know like I'm not I'm over like whatever said about me and I've already had to defend myself again
I didn't go up in like four like you know saying things that this woman KK was like
You know saying oh, you know blah blah. He's so terrible blah blah cuz you know, I think Alex I kind of
had some had a little bit of a day like you know
It's kind of like some kind of words or something and
So then KK was like oh well this guy was like saying that I'm a bad mom or whatever and I was like
I was like well as like and then you're because she was talking shit about me and beat his chat like when I was there
She's a month and and she was like and I was like well you're talking shit about me and judging me and as they had
And now it's the Swiss karma for like because like now like you're getting like judge for your like parenting skills
It's the same thing and she's like what what what that's not the same thing. Oh, so I'm sorry. I'm so blocked
That's not the same thing. That's a different thing because you know
cats or other kids, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, I know, but it's the same kind of thing,
but now you know how I feel, and then I explain it right.
Then she did say that she...
She did kind of apologize in a certain way now
Who didn't apologize or who made these words was like sand man
I went on there too because they're doing the same thing and now it's just like be nice enough to come on the panel and
Then you know like I think that if I go I'm like established enough where I should I should be able to go on a panel and not
Not just be attacked or like, you know, but like, you know, they bring on kiss my cheeks on the phone
And then they're really bad there the phone and I got these people just like talking to me like I'm the piece of garbage on the earth
Like, you know, and I'm trying to explain things over and over again like
that
I'm all good. I'm please cats are all good. I'm good like
The house clean hey, no tricks right there tricks is right there behind me trace the reviews over there
He likes to sit the sun. I was chilling
Let's see
Hey, J-Voc, you know come on panel somebody. You want to come up and say hi. I know I've been here. I've just been like
I'm dual streaming this on kick today
You know, even on Twitch, I like, oh, thank you,
like a couple people signed up,
or they did not signed up, but on Twitch,
if you have an Amazon Prime.
you can go on Twitch and like choose one person
to get a free membership and then it's like,
and then Twitch will pay them
for a few bucks for the membership.
And so if you guys are interested,
like that's the way to support me.
If you just, all you have to do is like,
but you get one and so if you're like friends
with somebody else or like you're a fan of somebody else,
you can use it for them,
but if you get every month,
you get to choose somebody for like, you know,
so that's just a benefit like in,
you know, especially like something
if people don't use it, it's just like, you know.
Waste right up your J-Dog up
Hey, what's going on psyche?
Okay, good. I've got you bro. I owe you an apology man. Oh
Okay, what's up? I want to tell you I'm sorry man for you know, I
Don't mean to bring drama to your your channel, bro. I know your your channel's more positivity more life
chill vibe, you know, positive energy, good vibes, you know,
you know, I felt bad,
you know, I felt really bad, you know, I really, you know, looking back and thinking about it.
I didn't mean to, you know, start shit, you know, on your panel or on your channel at all.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I saw like, you know, I was getting all these screenshots, screenshots and it's like, well, it's like, I know some of you guys fight sometimes and then you're friends again and then you fight sometimes and it's like, I'm trying to stay out of, out of it and just like, just have my own personal relationship with people and it's like, I don't want people to fight or like, but I think, okay, I think I'm okay.
Like I say, I just can't have people say,
oh, that person can't be on it.
I don't like the like ultimatums on it
because I like to just like have people
when they want to come up or if they want to come up
most of the time, if I like to get along with them.
I get along with them.
Just like, you know, I said, just no doxing
or like, you know, don't do any of that on my show, you know.
Yeah, I respect your rules psyche. I respect your rules and man
I apologize to you man if I broke any of your rules or if I disrespected your gas care or
Disrespected you in any type of way. I apologize as a man to you man. I'm sorry
You know, maybe like hopefully you can you know talk to some of the other people that are bad and stuff like that
But I know some of the stuff you said is true. They were a lot of it, you know
And it's like I just don't want to get too involved in like
Well, I brought up a lot of personal stuff that I should not have brought up, you know
Especially a lot of stuff that you know behind the scenes that a lot of people are not aware of and so that was bad of me
And I don't want to bring up stuff that
You know, I'm not trying to bring up personal stuff that has nothing to do with anything, you know relevant here
You know what I mean like yeah, I don't want to you know say stuff like that
So well that lady stargazer you were very they were pretty rude to her like for you know
She's like a little like the spicy old spicy old lady. Yeah, I went at her heart. I apologize man
I you know, I was high that day, you know, you know, I
I wasn't on my right mind and you know like I went at her crazy and I just respect her and you know
I'm sorry, and I do apologize care
Okay, no problem. Well, okay good, and I'll never happen again. Never happen again. That sounds good
and
Yeah, so what's up with you? Like I was what's now?
Chilling chilling just getting ready to go out there and hit me hit the road with the ice cream trucks
Yep, can you can you like come by my house and bring me was mr. Goodbar?
You know what if I'm by your house. I'm gonna ring the doorbell and I'll be like hey come get whatever you want psyche something house
Okay, I just back because I look like it's
You shaved off psyche you take your beard
Mustache and stuff, but I tried to shave off some of my beard. Hi James. Yeah
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, you got a you got a new look looks clean bro. It's really clean
Yeah, I think I like I think and I've been trying to like no say like look bigger like the violent male
Yeah
But they were talking mad crap that day, right?
Yeah, I seen that that day. I'm not allowed on KKs because I am a doxxer so I'm not allowed
on KKs as far as, you know, I got into one of her, you know, wine mommy gal pals and
docked somebody on her. So that's why I'm not allowed on KKs. Otherwise, I wouldn't
I went up there and defended myself with her
and I think it went really well on her show
but then Sam and like brought all these people
that were just being all loud like a play battery
and they're all like saying, oh my God,
they're just like, you know how like they're overreacting
so that they're just like, it just like makes it so hard.
It's like the crowd just like totally is like,
you know kind of swept up in like the mood of the room
sometimes and it's like, it's just like it's all like,
Hey, hold on, I'm going to take it.
Hi.
Just saying hi, starting my day off right.
Actually, I've been up for a long time, but just saying hi.
Hi, J-Dog.
I hope you're having a good day.
Hi, Alan.
How are you doing?
Good.
How about you?
I'm turning my camera off.
I'm turning it off.
No, no, no.
Don't turn it off.
Oh, I don't look good right now.
No, no, no.
How are y'all doing today? Early afternoon for me, not early. I'm just on a weird sleep schedule now, but
how are y'all doing?
Work-chilling, chilling. I guess I'm parapologizing to Psyche for, you know, I was on bad behavior.
Well, you know what it takes from people to apologize and that's cool. That tells me everything
I need to know about you. You're
Amazing because a lot of people don't have that in them to apologize. Thank you Alex. I appreciate you Alex
Thank you. And you know psyche is a good friend to have you know, I know
You know, you had him on I saw the show yesterday and you know, I just subscribe to your show Alex. Yeah, it was a amazing show
I look forward. Are you gonna have him on some more times Alex?
I'm hoping Thursday as he has time and then Sunday if he has time but the next show will be better because
I wasn't as prepared as I should have been for the first show. So in the next show,
it's going to be better graphics. I'm going to be more prepared. I'm not going to sound
like I just finished having a concussion and I'll be better. But psyche was amazing on it.
I hope you're okay. Thank you so much. No, no, no. I know I said I didn't want to sound like I finished having a concussion
I I don't think I I was prepared enough
Yeah, I haven't had a good question to my knowledge. I hope I have it maybe. Yeah, no
I love you. No, I love your show. Your show is like so so a professional and it's like, you know, it's so great
Just talking to you and it's just like such a
Easy conversation, it's like, no matter what the topic.
So, oh, thank you for gifting the membership,
my traveling gypsy, I don't know.
Let me know who got that, I can't see my,
I don't see my screen right now, but thank you for that.
Am I traveling gypsy, Tarot?
I see you.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, there's, I felt like there was a good,
very good vibe with that statistic.
I think it's, and I was like, I keep thinking,
you guys, I think we're like,
Yeah, we are like the astrological twins in a way, right?
We are.
Well, I feel like you're like my kindred spirit in a lot of ways.
Yeah, my own cousin saw the show, and she was like...
Since when are you okay with Tarot?
Cause she's big into Tarot and astrology and everything.
And I was like, I have them, but like within my family,
we have a certain dichotomy.
It's like a split.
Some people are okay with it.
Some people are not.
And she was like, I am so glad that you did that show.
She loved it.
So that's what means something to me.
It's like when your family sees your stuff
and they're like, oh, that's what you're up to.
So yeah, awesome. I told my family about it. I think my brother, my brother will watch it, but
yeah, um, well, I hopefully look at that open some people's, you know, eyes to,
you know, you know, be interested in astrology because, you know, it is a fascinating way to, um,
to
Know about yourself, and I think know thyself. Yeah such an important important
You know thing to do and know thyself love thyself all the ones that we have somebody else coming on the channel too
Oh traveling gypsy ones. Here we go. Yay. Hi. Hi. How are you guys doing?
Pretty good just finishing work to stop it to say hi say hi to psych
I need Alex Alex you're so friggin awesome on your show. Keep up the good work
And I'm so proud that you stepped up for psych for a tape. That's awesome
Thank you for it. Thank you for being supportive and for giving me that time. I blocked you and I was just like hey
Don't worry. No worries. I so get it because like you never know, right?
I'm just like certain friends with certain people that I click with but that's about it. I don't
Like psych and I have actually known each other. Holy shit psych for two years
Yeah, yeah over a year for sure like I'm yeah
So but I missed the show so what is it like on yours is it on your stream psych?
Actually, I like did I like her to her to her
video. On my community wall, my post is there, but I think I got her channel.
No, I'm subscribed to Psych. I just, to Alex, I just, I missed it yesterday.
It's not our backup channel. It's on our backup channel. It's just Alexander Mayer's.
It's actually my original channel, my original channel. That one, I'm not really active. It's
where I do my Bible reading, the Alexander Mayer's channel. Yeah.
but it's like you should download or if you want to wait for the edited version. Oh my god,
I just thought about what I could do. I'll make you your own intro to it and edit it.
That way it's considered completely unique content and you could monetize it and I'll
do that for all of them. That way you have
your edition, I'll have my edition, and, you know, then there'll be the original raw edition.
That's the best way you could make shorts. Look, when it comes to social media marketing,
I do kind of know how to do it. So that's what we'll do.
Yeah, thank you so much. I appreciate that sounds like yeah, I love your intro
I can't wait to see more but I'm gonna head out
I'm gonna go pick up some banana chocolate chip muffins at my kid's house
So I just wanted to say hi to everybody and say hi to you and like yeah
Alex and like yeah. All right. Hey guys
Okay, you too, but
She's sweet. She's nice.
We had a lot better energy lately here.
Just like, nice.
Well, except for that bag, that kind of last little kind of Saturday night,
not as good.
Oh, that was comedy. That was comedy, okay?
That was pure comedy, in my opinion. That was funny.
Um, yeah, well, you know right now you are I won't say the but one of the most popular
metaphorical guys in school.
That's what I call the streaming communities the school and you're popular right now.
You are popular.
You're going to have to wheel to your popularity.
I would like to get my numbers up and stuff, but yeah, I would say I'm kind of well up and I don't know if I'm famous or infamous, but I don't know, if someone was saying today, they were like, oh yeah, I don't know, they were saying that...
I don't know, I felt like not a lot of people were like,
said nice things about me, so I don't know.
I forgot what you guys said though, I'm sorry.
Well, first comes infamy, then comes fame,
then comes you running away from fame
and becoming reclusive.
And then you come back out again
and you help other people going through the same cycle.
That's how it works.
Yeah, and I have I have like constantly always been like you know going like having these long periods of being alone and things like that and then
This time I was able to click on it because I wasn't even talking when I first started like watching like lives on YouTube
I was like what is I didn't know like what did like understand there like the live streams were getting popular and
And so then I slowly started talking in chats,
then I became a mod in some chats,
and then started doing some panels,
and then started my own channel,
and I just did things step by step by step,
just like a goat will climb a mountain,
step by step by step, you know?
And I always knew it would be successful.
I was like, well, I was like, I have the rest of my life,
till like,
Do something with it like something's gonna happen. It's like just like if I keep it in content and I know people and
And I it's like something I do some there's people out there for everybody, you know, and I was very very I was very like
Shy about coming on camera my first videos which are up again. I never like was on camera. I was just like
They get the beach and stuff like that, but now I'm like I can't get off camera. I'm much more confident and
Good
So I came out I came out, but I'm also able to share all these things I learned when I was in this like large periods of solitude and
I also like solitude is good for me once in a while. It's very healing and very
You know you can give it to you to like rest. It's like a hermit mode a little bit, but then it's like
Yeah, I'm in her I'm in her mit mode until the beginning of the fall
I've been in solitude people have been like where's Alex we got to use our we got to weaponize our
To figure out where she is when she has her video up
And I mean they can do it if they want to but unless you have four wheel drive
It's gonna be hard to get where I'm at, but I'm so extreme
That when I have to be in solitude, I go where nobody, but I'm at the end of the summer, I'll be ready to come back out again.
But sometimes, you know, especially being a Capricorn, you know, we do.
Have those modes to where we have to prepare ourselves because we kind of sometimes.
You know, talking to you has been incredibly therapeutic for me because.
You reminded me of a lot of things that I forgot about when it came to some lessons that not only my dad, but his partner also have taught me over the years.
And I just hadn't revisited that. So, you know, you say I've helped you not as much as you've helped me.
And I mean it when I say that you are a natural counselor, you're a natural therapist, you bring in humor, you bring in astrology, you bring in the tarot, you bring in kindness, you're a very good person, and that's why people are coming at you.
And I've seen it with, I mean, there's been some people that, you know, I said, I'll never talk to again, or that I've had disagreements with, but just because I have, it doesn't mean that they weren't unique special people.
It just got to where it was too much for me. And I have a very hard shell, as I'm sure you can feel, but I didn't always.
And I hope that you never get to have as hard of a shell as me, because I would like my shell to soften.
But with you ignore these people you got a lot of jealousy
That's coming at you right now because you are
Talking to a lot of the women in the community that a lot of the men
Would love to talk to but they don't have the courage it doesn't matter if you're hetero or LGBTQ
It's the fact that you're a male
and you have amazing social skills.
And there's some men who are coming at you,
even if you didn't exist,
they would never have the courage to talk
to some of the women that you routinely talk to.
Bita, Bita is a hot woman.
I don't care what anybody says.
She and I have gone back and forth
and I've said things that I wish I had never said to her.
But the fact of the matter is she's a hot,
sophisticated, cool woman.
Elisa Giordano, I know you've communicated with her.
She, without a doubt, is like the queen
when it comes to glamour and just professionalism.
I've never spoken to her,
but I really admire her in a lot of ways.
Who else?
Who else, let me think of.
It's been a lot.
There's been a lot of women in these communities,
and you'll probably talk to more
and the guys, they're gonna get very envious
because they're like, oh, he's as psychy than he is.
Really?
That's what it is.
So prepare for that,
but you'll have men who come at you who get jealous too
because you've talked to,
you know who you really vibe to with?
Well, I saw the stream,
Benny Blanco, I forgot about him.
Yeah, it's a nice dude. He's nice
He's super nice. So yeah, he was like where I basically started on his show
Like that was like one of the I was just watching a lot of tarot on YouTube
And then like I just like came across him in my like algorithm one night like in my and then and he was like
He had like a hundred people in his chat. He was like he kept saying bro, bro, bro
And it was like really funny and then he ended up falling asleep
And I was like talking in his chat like three tarot readings in his chat
And that was like the first people that were basically subscribed. He like
He would actually say, oh, subscribe to give it to his 50 subscribers.
And it happened pretty quickly after that, given he just really inspired me, which is
like maybe some of it is not so positive.
Like I was like, oh, I want to get drunk on Stream 2.
And I got pretty drunk the first six months of my show.
I was, I got pretty damn drunk on my show.
But I was like, I've done all kinds of stuff.
Yeah
Yeah, but he's great. Yeah, I love Benny. Yeah, he's for you. He's interesting. He's very interesting
He looks like he should be an actor in a remake of the portrait of Dorian Gray
He has amazing facial features. I always I'm very into aesthetics. I look at people and I'm like, hmm
Hmm, that's a beautiful person. Yeah
Yeah, he and I love him. Well, I would say he always got trolled. I think they're like where people say
Yeah, no, no, no, he's gonna age and he's he's so young still when he's going to be there. Have you ever seen as he's three
Ever see his dad I've seen his dad. Yeah, he's really good looking
Oh, yeah, well I just kind of seen his dad from the side or like not too much on camera
But well, I didn't see I thought his dad was kind of like this balding you saw
Okay, maybe it was a different maybe it was a different person I saw but
No, he's gonna grow up to look like him. Maybe maybe that was his mother
I don't know who it was, but I was like wow
But you know his mom is like that like like kind of like Roseanne, you know
It's like it kind of reminds me of Roseanne like
You know in the 80s, right and there's a thing where he like was fighting his mom or whatever
And I was like I saw the videos and stuff people can't tell me oh my god
Like look what he's doing and like I was like
He's a puncher in the face
It looks like he's a quister on the shoulders and it's like and then you don't know like how some guys their mom
It's a physical family and especially when moms have boys the moms
A lot of times because when the boys are little
They have to be physical because it's a boy instead of a girl.
I don't think that he's abusing his parents or anything. Yeah.
He's frustrated. I think that he needs, I was really proud of a guy known as Q.
And he's in California, I actually I'm hoping at some point I can communicate with him directly because I've decided that's who I'm giving my e-scooter to if he wants it.
I'm just going to gift it to him because I do want to write it one more time, but I'm a little afraid.
Yeah, I'm a little afraid because.
I gotta live, I can't be knocking my head around too much.
Well, you know, like, are you a runner?
You're like running?
When I was younger, yeah.
I do run on treadmill sometimes.
I haven't run in a few months, but when I was younger,
I had the record in high school
for the mile run for many years.
I used to do long distance and I have a lot of stamina not now because I'm a smoker. I'm gonna have a cigarette right now hell
but
When I was younger, what about you did you ever do any sports you look athletic?
I did cross-country. Oh, I played I was on it. Yeah, I was cross-country to high school and I was actually
Invited sports banquet because I was like I got was most improved or something like that
I was a smoker too like back then when I was like 16 17 or something
Yeah, I spoke to that was like 14 13 and like people would buy me cigarettes as friends
I was gonna say how did you even get the cigarettes? I mean I remember one time. I thought I'm gonna be cool
I tried to buy some cigarettes once when I was a teenager and the clerk wouldn't tell him to me
He's like I already know your mom. I'm not giving you anything. I was like, oh
Yeah, I tried a lot of things when I was young and I would get in trouble
Nothing
me too. But I got most improved and I actually got a trophy and I got invited to the sports
dinner at the school and stuff. And that was like, wow. But I was on a basketball team
when I was younger too. My mom was like, you know, I got out of the baseball team, but
I hadn't been on the basketball team. And I didn't really get at the audition. So they
put me on a good team. But I was like, I just sucked. And it's like, but I played, I didn't
I don't not think about it still. I didn't learn it. I just was like well
I can tell because he called it an audition
Call the tryout we called it tryout, but you you
Can I ask you something you don't have to answer, but I'm just curious. Have you ever been an actor?
Yeah, he's having an actor's face community theater. Yeah, I did like three like kind of community theater plays
this place called the Norse theater in
like, you know, Palisbury's where I'm from and it was like when I was probably
six seventh six and seventh grade or fifth sixth and seventh or something because
I was in the play sugar, which is like some like it hot. It's like based on that some like it hogger the movie
It's a Maryland movie Jack Levin and stuff and then I was then bye-bye birdie
And then I was in this one called what's about a mattress, which is like the princess in the pee
But yeah, but it's a princess and a pee and then the pee like updated and like
Carol Burnett started it and like the 50s or 60s, whatever, but yeah, yeah, it's a really funny. It's a pretty funny play
Is this in California? Is it? Yeah, it's different. Okay
So, so well, you're you're fortunate you grew up in California
Because you've always been around actors and actresses then
Yeah, there's a lot of them here and like, you know
You know, but I did notice like the African Americans when I went to theater class in like college
I said they were like the best actors like I had seen like they were just like
Very impressive. I was like, oh my god, thank god
We're just now really, as African-Americans, getting our due when it comes to having filmmakers that are making major moves and, like, what's that guy's name?
Tyler Perry, he's made his mark.
There's Angela Bassett is starting to do some directing
and producing, but quietly,
there's always been a lot of female artists
in the music industry who are black or African-American
who have quietly funded a lot of independent artists,
not just black though, white, Latin,
You know who I think really has a lot of bias against them in Hollywood Asian people and people don't think about Asians very much, but Asians, especially East Asians, when it comes to drama and action films, you have some amazing performers and a lot of times they get passed over.
And I don't know why.
I'm hoping that, you know, with the equalization of producing flicks or films, whatever, you're
going to see more people that you normally wouldn't see.
But yeah, you have an actor's face.
That's why I asked you.
You have a nice jaw.
You have a good jaw.
Thank you.
Actually, I got told, okay, so I had a nose job when I was like 17 years old.
Really?
Yeah, I did.
And but but I had to go to a few doctors for consultations and like the first doctor was like this this doctor
He's like he's like well, it's too complicated of a surgery, but that's your nose is too complicated
So I went to another lady. So the second people I went to was this lady and she was like, okay
Yeah, we're gonna you know, we're gonna break your nose like if you arrange it and stuff
And then she's like no one wanted to do a shit implants and like a forehead
She like and so what are all these implants and stuff?
Yeah, I didn't think so and I was like, I had a nose. It was just basically like a like a bird's beak. That's what I could I give them what I can't do. It was just like, it was just like, and so this tip of it is like, do you see it like a perfect, like, perfect tip?
Yeah, I wouldn't have thought whoever it looks pretty, it looks natural. I didn't think you'd had anything done.
Plastic Surgeon that did it has passed away now, but his name was Dr. Leaf and he was in Beverly Hills and
he did Jane Fonda's
Facelift that was
That's what I heard you know before I got it
If you I can't find the pictures anymore, but I used to have some pictures when they did the before photos after and it's just like so
Such crazy difference like
But I don't, and that's the only thing I really did.
I mean, I think I also like had,
I had lasik of surgery and.
I want to get the eye that, you know,
my sister was talking about it and I was scared for her.
I was like, no, but as I'm getting older,
I'm kind of rethinking that I wouldn't mind having,
I'm just afraid like, what if something happens,
you know, and then I can't see.
So well, it's like I remember it's like it's like a very quick procedure like they basically like laser
Like you're a flap of like a flap of like on your eye
It's like it's like all it happens in like two minutes. Basically, you're awake during it. You're on
Oh, I don't want to be away. Yeah, but it's like so quick. It's you have to be awake because your eyes are open, right?
it's like and
And so basically you just sit there like stare up and it's a little laser
It does most of the stuff, it just pulses your eye.
And then it's like, they put the flap back over it,
and that's it.
And then it's like, it was like, I had 2020 a vision.
And I had really bad vision where it's like,
I can barely, all the lights were all blurry everywhere,
and I could hardly see the drive,
I could read street signs or anything.
Then I had 2020.
Now it's maybe, I had times where reading glasses
sometimes up close, but.
My far away distant vision is what's bad.
Up close, my up close vision is shifting.
I can, I'm noticing it, but I'm gonna wait.
I'm gonna give it a couple more years to see what happens.
So I'm just gonna wait.
But when I'm, definitely when I'm 55,
I'm going to go to Brazil to get my plastic surgery.
I'm gonna get a facelift.
And it depends on what kind of physical shape I'm in.
I might get lipo, but I might not need it.
We'll see.
They do have like amazing surgeons there,
but I don't, yeah, I mean, just say the beautiful like.
Of course, like, you know, but I'm not beautiful enough,
not enough, never enough, never enough,
not in my opinion.
I don't think that you can ever,
but I'm only talking about for me, not for other people.
I'm just, you know what it is?
My looks were basically my trait for such a long time.
It's not at all, which is great, but still, it's just vanity, and I know it, it's a little
bit of vanity.
Well, I mean, I don't think vanity is that big of a sin, it's like one of the seven
deadly sins, but it's like, I don't think it should really be on that list, because
I like I do like being attractive. I'm not gonna lie about it. I it's it's a difference because
You do it's it's good, but bad some people there's this
YouTube short. I should send it to you. There's this woman who lives in Dubai
And she's like a motivational speaker. She probably at one time was working in the sex work industry
But she's gorgeous and she's very intelligent, but she really breaks down what it is that's perceived as beautiful. That's like her whole thing, beauty, what it is when it comes to the public's perception of looking one way versus another way.
And she's right. You actually have more adversity being viewed as attractive than not.
But it's an advantage. Mr. Bigpipes isn't here saying he thinks you look better than any other time. He's known you five years now
So I have none. I'm a little I don't know what to think about Bigpipes right now, and I'll tell you why I
Know who he crushes on I do know very well
And I still want to see big pipes become full force.
I haven't seen that from him yet.
I haven't seen big pipes in full force, meaning that guy who's going out on the town,
who is just confident and, you know, knows his shit, don't stink.
I really, I like him, but sometimes I don't like him, but then I like him again.
I really do that I really do that like I had a
On the show that I kicked him off and like banter for the streamer for a while, and I was like so mad at him
I mean, I don't remember why but I put him in there
There's a guy he invokes it. He invokes he doesn't on purpose to him
You know that but then I came back like or like I was on like a
gymnics show and he was there and then like
We're getting along again and like so I was like we can come back to the show and then
Mr. Big Clips has been through he's been through a lot
He's and I'm not gonna disclose because I don't know like what y'all have talked about
But what I know of him. He is a success story already
When it comes to some adversity that he contended with when he was younger. So, you know, I'm always him
What's his name say?
you
Crack-a-donna
Joe Shippley
I'll even say as much BS as I dealt with him
Tommy James those are
Like I have a soft spot for them. Those are my boys. I consider them my boys and they're bad. I have bad boys. I
Don't know why
Yeah, well, yeah, I mean so many of these people like blogger cue Tommy James like a lot of people
I'm like a lot of a lot of guys that are also streamers. They don't like
Blogger you like blogger. They don't like because well, they don't like themselves and they got to work on that. That's what it is
Well, oh we lose you. Oh
Yeah, you blog bloggers listening
So, well, hopefully Alex is back in a second.
Where's everybody in the chat though?
Why is everybody in the chat so quiet?
We have over 30 people in here.
Come on in.
Anyone want to move on the panel?
Oh, yeah, I'd need to pin that down.
There's a video there. Is anybody there? Oh.
I got one of those I got one of those emergency things like I'm not against the emergency thing
they're saying that where I am there's going to be um some sort of weather um it could be I guess
nothing I can do about it but whenever I get like an alert it comes through and it pops up my
Stream my streaming
But yeah
Blogger I've I've blogger
For some reason blogger thought that like he had to answer to me at one point. I'm like what in the world. Oh
Maybe he just wants someone to answer
It's like this thing a dog looking for its owner, it's like what are you
master. If you um well I have some clips of him which at his request I have
unlisted but I have some beautiful compilations of some of his older streams.
I turned them it like into little
I turned his life into like a little mini-series, you know, I will send you the playlist if you ever want to watch it because I put cool music with it, I edited it.
I was just kind of practicing editing series using his content because he's such a good performer. He doesn't even realize it.
And everyone really loved a lot of the compilations I did of him, but they weren't just compilations, I made it like a series, I called it, well, but would I call it blogger, the, it was something files.
It was something called the something files off to look it up like they got what I named it.
But blogger inspired me he was cool.
He tries to not be himself. He's a natural actor
Natural actor, yeah
Oh, well, I mean it's like I get along better with blogger now
I we had we've had a couple incidents, but I get along with him better than most people
But I try to make it with Tommy James and clumsy and stuff like that and different guys
Like I think that we were calling him kind of colleagues doing the same thing
And we should just like you know at least be like on good terms or supportive. I think Tommy Tommy will end up
Being someone who you're friendly with because he's probably watching him right now everything. I do he watches I
I met him. Yeah, we hung out for about three weeks. I flew him down to Houston and he let
In his core, he's a good person. He actually, he's made some very good points lately when it's come to something. So I hope that he stays on the path that he's on because he's been healthier.
He, yes. Yeah, I'll leave it at that. I think that he's stopping doing some things because he's realized that there's unfortunately.
Some people who watch these streams and they want to see like they view the streamers like they view is almost like we're
characters in a video game
And like instead of helping us win the game
They want to see us like be destroyed and they try to figure out ways
to fuck with us
But maybe that's a part of the game
Sometimes tables are turned
right
I mean if you think about it, if most of it's psychological warfare, right, and it's like that's a lot of power too
It's like most of it is like we also have a lot of attraction
We can like start to believe these negative things or attract these negative things born into our life
You know by just concentrating on them giving them energy because our attention is with what the world of the world is made of a
consciousness and
Where attention goes energy flows, right?
Have you seen this this this isn't see they're going to the screen. Do you like that? I do I notice that you changed your
Main avatar to this. Yes. Yeah, I like that
It was on the flag. Yeah
The heart with the rays around the rays around I'd like the sign. It's the sign
I really you know, thank you for the brief, you know, you I'm sure you do realize it
But I rewatched our stream and the advice that you gave me through the reading especially that final card
You're so right about that and it's in the process of happening. I'm not gonna say what it is that way
You know those who want to talk about you after watching the stream, but psyche really so on point with his analysis of exactly where I am at this particular juncture of my life, and I know that you only focus on the present, but you did for tell something with that last car.
You absolutely did.
Thank you for thank you for the confirmation. I love I love that. Mm-hmm. Happy
Yeah, see that's what they think and it's like right now it
Right, you know right in yours. You just know it right right before so
Hopefully you gave me some guidance on that. You did. Thank you very much
What is that? What is that instance that you're burning at this moment? This is called cabala incense
Oh. Okay. Yeah. And it says hand rolled masala incense sticks and I came out and like this. There's some other kinds too. And I've already been through two packs. I think I went through like the there's one called which is brew. And then there's one called go away evil or something like that. And then there's like one more. Yeah. And I have one more. I need to go away evil. That's what I'm going to pick up.
I like since normally I like I do like like when I'm stationary like in the winter time, especially I love burning incense
certain candles and whatnot in the summer. No, not in the summer, not in the spring, but probably going into November.
My mom, when I was younger, she would do that.
But out here where I am, I mean, I feel like the desert is in since in itself, and I think I'm going to live in the desert.
I'm really considering living in the desert, but I really like the community that I'm in right now and.
I was talking to, I went up to the little store a little earlier today and it takes a while for people to get used to seeing you and everything around here. But they're used to me now.
And there's a young woman who works there. She's like, I hope you move here because whenever I go in, I like to talk.
And I chit chat with her and she's like, don't leave. And I'm like, well, when it comes to the fall, I have to.
But I'm going to be back in the spring, but what I think I want to do is like, you know how I was telling you, I really want to do some things for mothers of daughters.
I am going to figure out how to establish myself as some sort of like a.
A shelter.
It doesn't only have to be a little girl. So I've decided, you know, you could have a little boy too, or multiple because everyone has different circumstances, but I'm going to buy a plot of land.
I'm going to make it like a sanctuary and I'm going to have really nice RVs.
kind of disperse throughout like a camping place, you know, but specifically for women who
Because if there's one thing I know how to do, it's how to disappear
I'm probably really like one of the best of people at it
but some women don't know how to do that, especially if they have like a crazy stalker at or
something going on
I'm gonna make and it might not work out. I was telling my mom about it and she was like
Good idea, but you're gonna face legalities and I'm like, I know I know but maybe that's something I have to fight
because I do have relatives that are
attorneys
And they can help me and I told one of my relatives who's an attorney and she was like
You have to do it. You have to face the legalities because otherwise the predators keep going after these women and that's why they don't get away.
So I just want to do that.
Yeah. Well, a lot of times there's like there's like Stockholm syndrome. There's like also like the feeling of helplessness is where am I going to go?
What am I going to do? I'm going to have children. I'm not going to have a place to stay. I'm not going to.
You know, I'll be, I'll be just out.
There's so much the first thing to be looking for on top of that. She's gonna be really like looking over her shoulder the whole time doing all this. Yeah
for a lot of things, so yeah, I have a
Long time friend who I used to know from the adult industry
He wound up becoming a security guard then a body guard then he opened his own body guard security firm
And I was telling him about it, and he lives in this area where I am.
That's part of the reason that I'm here because he's known some things that I've gone through.
And when I left the adult industry, I actually came out here and I stayed on his property
because I did, I had some people after me.
And he taught me a lot, but I was telling him and he's like, well, if you do that.
Hire me, I will basically give you a 90% discount and I'll use your situation as a way to train my guys as to how to deal with things. And I'm like, great idea. So that's what, if I move forward, that's what I'm doing, but I didn't have the confidence to do it before.
I can I can do it now because I don't like when you're a woman and you know you work and everything you do have that expendable income and even for tax reasons you do have to find you can't just sit on money especially nowadays and I'm not saying I have like all this money because I don't but you cannot sit on money you have to find a way to keep it circulating and that's a spiritual thing too because money is a manifestation of energy.
So that's exactly and yeah and it's basically it's and it's also said like
the money is not the root of all evil it's the love of mine or that's the
root of all evil it's like loving money more than like you know people hold on
to it yeah if you hold on to money you don't like the more you circulate money
the more you're gonna attract money that's what I don't think some people
If you hold on and you're constantly like, you know, screw to make duck
You're never gonna have much of anything. You'll actually lose money that way
Quickly, yeah, you know, well money is always just burned
It's kind of through my hands because it's like I just say
Have it and it's like but I've never really saved any, you know, it's like I always will
I'll spend everything I have like, you know, I'd like three
So I don't know I need to work on the saving part of it, but I do like good deals. So too though
Well, what are you spending on a lot like what do you think takes your money from you?
Well, I mean, it's like, you know, I mean lately it's been kind of like the
ordering Grubhub or DoorDash or something.
Do you not like to cook?
I do like to cook, but sometimes
I get tired of the whole foods here
and I think the markets are kind of far.
The other markets are kind of far.
Well, whenever you decide and you might not ever and I will not take offense
But if you ever decide that you trust me
Let me know where to send you something too because I told you I wanted to do the mail plan
Because I'll be honest. I want to fatten you up a little bit. I think that you I would try I
Think that you do need a little bit more meat on your bones and I understand that you have a very fast metabolism
But if you ever give me the chance, I could probably help you gain a little bit of weight if you ever want it to
Thank you
Thank you so much because you know, it's like sometimes that way, you know, it's not a rush
I told you I would monitor you for a month
But if you ever want me to send you some meals like because there's some really good
Companies that send all you gotta do is put it in the oven
and it could become a part of your stream.
You could show your people you preparing meals and eating
and then you know what, if you don't get any weight, you don't.
But I think that I can do I can do push-ups to and pull-ups and stuff like that
And maybe I'll get so I'll get muscular and stuff
I used to be like running around half naked on my show. I was like, I'm like
Embarrassed myself in that speedo so bad like now I don't feel like ever like did you wear a speedo on your street?
it was in like July, it was like the week before like July, it was like July like for
second or third, right before the 4th of July, I say a stadium for the 4th of July but we
didn't ever fighting and so then like when I went one night in her chat in this video and like
she said she like we made up it was so funny and then I went and I and I flashed I flashed
I went on his show, and I pulled down my pants, and I was wearing the Speedos.
And then, unfortunately, I went, and I got kind of way too drunk,
and I put my legs in my head, and then somebody took a picture of that,
and it's like there's like profiles, psyche, like dick and fish tacos or something,
and then, and with me, those pictures of me, and whoever that is, I'm gonna find you.
I don't know what, I'm gonna make you take it down.
I'm gonna make you take that picture.
Picture, yeah, it's embarrassing.
I'm just kidding.
I think, it looks fine.
I'm very, I am very flexible, Alex.
I can actually do something really cool with my arms.
I think I probably showed you.
Well, you know, I think it's better to start out
to skinny opposed to overweight.
I've always thought that.
I have seen some amazing transformations
of people go from thin.
to looking like, you know, a fitness model.
So you're in a good position, but I'm not criticizing you.
And I hope that you don't take it that way.
But if you ever do want advice on gaining weight and whatnot,
I am a good person to talk to when it comes to that.
I do know a lot about that kind of a thing.
Thank you.
I do appreciate because I do neglect my own.
Like, you know, there's some nights I'm like, oh, like, I don't have any food here.
It's late.
And then I was like, but I don't want to like order because it's like, it's so
expensive.
And it's like, so whenever you're ready, just tell me.
It doesn't have to be your address.
It could be a PO box.
It could be anywhere.
I will start sending you.
There's a company that makes some really delicious meals.
And all you guys do is put it in the oven.
and it could be a part of your stream.
Sometimes you do have to put stuff on the stove.
Sometimes you got to put it in the microwave.
Oh, yeah. Well, I don't have a microwave.
I have everything. I have a stove.
I just have a gas stove.
Then I'll send you a microwave. That's not a thing.
It doesn't matter, but I would like to see you have some healthier food, and I'm not saying that you're not being healthy
But I would like to see you have some healthier food
That's just me being me
Have been eating a lot of McDonald's. Well, thank you so much for looking out for me
I didn't have a pretty good bagel today and a hash brown
from the
Bagel store because I woke up earlier
But, I've been trying to...
Sometimes I'm hungier than other times, like coming from like
the middle of the night after drinking a lot and like, you know, then that
like, I ate so much Taco Bell the other night, like this big box, but
four different of the entrees and like
Cinnabon, donut, like cream bites and like, yeah, what else?
So you're eating junk food, you're eating junk food, okay.
Yeah, well kind of eating fast food like sometimes, I like burgers, I mean it's like, I don't
try to watch my weight and so it's like I have like, probably stuff that's pretty bad
for you and like sometimes I was like, yeah, I like, but I don't eat, I used to like eat
a lot of ice cream but I don't eat as much ice cream anymore, but yeah, I don't eat
I was always a big dessert guy in my family.
I would always order the dessert for the table
and everyone else was always on a diet.
So they were like, oh, Mr. Big Pipes is up to say hi.
Hey, what's up, Alex?
Hey, how are you doing?
Hi, how are you, Big Pipes?
I'm chilling, yeah.
You're just chilling?
Like a villain?
I'm chilling.
I saw you on, you were on Jimny's show the other day and it's like, this guy's SIG was
on what?
What's up with SIG?
Isn't he like terrible?
Like he just says such horrible things?
Like you think so?
Yeah, I've known him for a while.
Like I actually have a video of him threatening to un-alive the president.
Oh my god.
Well, let's not even talk about that, I don't want to do those words.
That's the kind of stuff that dude says, like...
Well, yeah, but I don't think he means it.
I don't think he means it, and also think about the age of him.
He's a lot younger than all of us.
He defended it by saying that the Secret Service already contacted him, and he doesn't care.
Well, he was just saying, like, what else was he saying, but he was saying spats up
big pipes.
He was saying, like, oh, like, psychopaths should, like, slit everyone's THROT, like,
right?
What was he, what was he talking about?
I don't know.
He's a sicko, right?
Well, the only thing you got to worry about with that is that, unfortunately, you have
people in these communities, when they hear you say things like that, they lie.
especially to law enforcement and say that you're threatening them directly
when you never did. Hell, you got people in your chat who've done that to me.
right now. Right now. Oh, I I've been
threatened. You should have my family threatened like on this
channel before on this. Oh, come on. It was like, you know, I
can't help what's with Q. That was Q, right? It was Q saying
that. So, yeah, I remember that but it was not necessarily
Hey, Panda. Panda, do you want to come up on panel? You can't. I
want to I want to meet you on panel if you want. I mean, I'm not
like I'm just telling you that happened. I can't but it didn't
I don't know maybe
They're not specific and I know but I had this it's like not serious, but it's like, you know nuts
They don't take it seriously. There's just a troll
You know for the most part when they were trying to define anything to annoy you. That's a bad precedent
Okay, so what's your big pipes you haven't been on video. That's rare for you
Oh, I'd like this new streamer setup where I'm using my phone as my camera, so I mean I've been streaming like every like three four times
But it's not a very good setup if it doesn't include a video though
It's like that that's not you know like look at look at it on my on my channel like I stream last night
I can't see anything you're you have a green arrow on my YouTube channel like on mr. Big Pops YT
We have to go to your YouTube channel to see you.
That's what you're saying?
Like, I'm on my computer right now, so, like.
For me to go have a webcam get those like an eight dollar webcam you can buy it put on your computer to plug it into USB
You'll have even I use OBS and a scarlet
For you can still play you can still use it in your in your regular. I'm on your channel right now
I don't even see you live on your channel. What are you talking about, mr?
I'm saying on my other channel. It's not like I'm afraid to go online
I just don't like have that well
I'm not saying you're afraid you don't want to be on camera. You don't have to be on camera
I'm not a camera right now
Here, I'll pop on real quick.
Here I am.
Absolutely.
I have a heart.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think I'm going to put it up.
No, that's my face.
That is my face.
I am the heart with the sign.
That's me.
Peace out.
Yeah, peace.
That's great.
That's perfect.
I like that.
Actually, I could have that on my stream.
That's all you see.
That's the heart with the sign.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Okay, well, it's like, you know, we don't want to make any accusations against anybody without
That's like just avoid doing that. He used to do that. Where's like makeup and stuff, right?
I know it's kind of pan to the torture cloud. Can you see him come up it? I don't know if you
You're saying that I talked to minors is what he was saying. Oh, was there were you ever talking to minors? No
Okay, well then why do you care I mean have I ever talked to a minor like in what like what situation like and then it's like
Ooh, gotcha like what the fuck?
Well, I know but it's like not like to meet the prospects. I guess is the position. No, no, Mr. Big Pipes
If I were in your position, I wouldn't worry about it considering certain things that are at play that others don't want to acknowledge
That are definitely provable reality
opposed to just you know
Accusations that are unfounded ignore. No, I do miss. I don't associate block the fucking weirdo
But, it's like, I don't associate with people who say that shit, like just imagine like chilling with cool people, and someone starts like spouting out like that, and then it's like, if you're not doing that in real life, why are you doing that online, and you're a pretender?
Why are you a pretender? And what else are you pretending about? Fuckin' weirdo?
Well, that's a good question.
Who are you talking to though, Big Five? Who are you talking about?
Uh, the pretender weirdo wears makeup and says I talked to him.
Oh, okay.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I mean, you've made a lot of progress, Mr. Big Pikes.
Don't let people keep you.
No, like, once that meant to my face, I would literally, like, slap the shit out of them.
Well, that's not threatened violence or anything
Maybe we can work it things out if he wants to come up and have a chat with you and make sure that you know
I'm not like there's I have no interest in talking to some weirdo
that wears makeup and
fucking
Hangs out on these panels and spurs out making up shit about people talking to minors. I don't
Well, don't take too seriously because I think he's I think he's his pan to the clown
So says yeah, you're crazy going on a panel torture. So he's a pretender. He like doesn't have a personality like
Personality in a pretender online minute 30s or something and I like
Going on a 30 year olds. That's like wrong with going on a 30 year olds panel
I think I think people like 30 years old want like basically
No, I'm saying he didn't have he doesn't he obviously doesn't have a personality
Well, he I mean he's worried like, you know, he's making his person. He's making his personality like oh, I'm the wacky
Mr.. Big Place, do you know how many people lie about me constantly? Oh, you do know you're very aware
What so don't care who cares why would I I don't I wouldn't associate with those people
Well, I don't. They follow me. I mean, right now, I'm looking at the chat. There's at least three people in the chat right now who have lied about me to law enforcement.
They have threatened me. They have tried to extort me. They feel like their presence in the chat is going to deter me from being on the panel.
Every single one of those people, male or female, not only can you go to hell,
You don't matter and that's the mentality that you have to have because they're miserable and misery loves company
They wish I mean mr. Big Pies. You're in a very good position in life. You are single
You have no children. You have a full head of hair
What else do you want? You have intelligence, yet you're choosing to let people who will
never cross paths with you in person affect you.
I do I'm like hey, I would be like hey, are you the dude that calls me a PDF online? I'd fucking rip his eyeballs out
That's what I would do
Literally everybody is called that like literally everybody. I mean I say I don't think there's anybody that hasn't been accused of that
There's a woman. There's a woman in who was in this chat today. So that doesn't mean we come with an actual
person who actually groomed a minor
who lied and said, I'm a PDF, where as clearly I am not,
I never-
I'm not, I don't need to say, I'm on Psyche's piano,
just let it be.
But what I'm saying is, do these people matter?
No, they are never going to get anywhere in their life.
They're always going to be where they are.
I'm not even gonna throw any insults because I feel the power of psyche holding me back
I feel like I feel like it's almost like a schoolyard fight and I'm trying to get somebody and
Psychies holding me back. He's like hey girl. Don't do it. Don't don't don't hit that person
So I'm not going to but you hear what I'm saying. Just don't let the noise fuck you up. Don't
I'm sorry even used. I haven't used the bad word just now
I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
Hi. It's me. Hi, guys. Hi, everybody.
Alex, Mr. Bike Pipes really does creep me out.
Does he give you that same vibe?
I've known Mr. Big Pipes for many years,
and I almost met Mr. Big Pipes.
No, he does not make me feel that way.
All right, that's it because I've seen him creep out a lot of women and he says like jelly and he talks like this
You're a bully
I would just want your opinion. That's all well. I gave him my opinion
I almost met mr. Big Pikes when I went to visit family in st. Louis many years ago
Mr. Big Pikes is someone that I do consider a friendly acquaintance. Would I be afraid of him? He's a cat
No, I do. So I appreciate your your perspective here. That's all. It wasn't being a bully
Just ask the question
He bullied him
Well, it's not my fault he's sensitive. I was asking Alex.
Well, I looked here and never sensed it.
No, I have a different point of view. That's all.
He has a BG for that.
Alex, I appreciate it.
I just gave it a little bit. He has a musician's temperament.
You know, musicians are a little bit...
Yes, yeah, he is a musician. He's an amazing musician
Mr.. Big Pipe's is self-taught on several instruments he can play by ear. I think that's pretty good
Can you can you see that he's amazing? He's great, but I can't
But he's very good.
He just needs to get appropriate, like a web camera
and like, you know, he acknowledges it.
You know, I've only heard him play
when he was very, very drunk.
Maybe that has something to do with it.
Yeah.
He's been very drunk on my show, yeah.
He's been very drunk on the show before and like.
That's why I like bigger, big pipes is what rocks are.
He can be all thick, OK, sometimes.
But he does get a little creepy sometimes.
Yeah, that was my opinion too and apparently Alex sees a different side of which is why I asked I wasn't trying to bully anybody honest
Honestly got
Well, you know might my tolerance level might be different because I've been around a lot of different kinds of people in my life
especially musicians
So maybe my perspective. Well, I don't think he's so creepy that he's like I wouldn't be around him
You know what I mean, but he could be he could be good
I mean, I think most guys around here can get a little creepy once they start drinking a little bit to be fair
So well we as women can get creepy too
Yes, we can. I love a good old fun sex talk.
How are you doing, Summer? I haven't talked to you since.
Be it as per animal, how are you doing?
I'm doing good. I'm doing a little busy.
I don't think I talked to you since being a panel.
I could be wrong.
No, I don't think we've been on a panel together now.
But I love the show that you two did yesterday, by the way.
I just want to say I was working.
You saw it. You saw it. Cool.
Yeah. Yeah.
We actually modded me to just kind of help watch the chat.
So I was at work and I was checking that, you know,
watching that.
That was, that was you.
So you're the same summer as, okay.
I wasn't sure if you were the same cause I know.
Okay. Okay.
Hot mess summer is me
And I think you
For your opinion Alex take care
Have a good day, RJ. Bye
Bye
It was it was definitely I loved the um, I love purple so I loved the background and everything
I thought it was really pretty especially for you just making it like right then. I thought you did a good job
I've already revamped it. I've already made it better
I'm just I'm the kind of person to where if it's not the way I really want it to be
I'm gonna make it the way I want it to be so it's good the next time it will be better
That's good. That's good. Yeah, it was a good show. I liked it. It was I liked it was nice
Yeah, did a good job this Thursday this Thursday, I think we were doing another right Alex
Yeah, I hope so. It's it's on you 12 p.m. Oh, yeah
under time
Be there be square
Okay, it can be it can be healthy there, but all right summer. You should come on the you should come up summer
Cuz yeah
That's what you should do if you know, it's like you were working well
This was my last day okay done until Sunday as far as work work goes
Okay, as long as I'm up, but then what's how well? I don't know 12 o'clock is what time see I'm in, Kentucky
So what time zone are you on? It's it's 6 30 right now. It's the oh, so it's the Eastern Eastern
Three hours. It'll be three. It'll be you'll be 3 p.m. It'll be 3 p.m. Oh, that's perfect. Yeah, that's good. I can do that
Yes
I'll be up by then.
I didn't even have to do that much research because I didn't know most of the stuff, but
I didn't just skip over myself a little bit in pressure.
And I had enough good knowledge, like book knowledge, because I do feel as an expert
in some of these things.
You are an expert.
You're like a freaking professor.
He's an educator. He's not just the reader. You really are. You're very
knowledgeable, more so than you may give yourself credit for, really.
You know, I think the spiritual religion, like that conversation in itself,
I think it's a cool conversation with, if you can have it with people that, you know what I mean, like,
obviously you two had a great conversation about it.
It's been, it's definitely been a journey, you know what I mean, for me, and different, different elements in different ways.
Um, but yeah, I think it's, I think it was really, I think it's really dope.
How has it been a journey for you if you don't mind me crying and being invasive?
Um, so in, so in the beginning I was raised in, um, in a church and everything like that,
like my, my uncle was a big time past, Southern past, uh, pastor and, and things. Um, and so
I was in a church choir, believe it or not. Um, and all that.
Nice.
And then things just happened throughout,
which we could talk about that maybe
on the atmosphere of another moment.
But a lot of things happened in my journey of that.
And so it kind of made me not trust God.
So, but then that was my very naive self right and so I've gotten older and I've been through a lot of things and now I definitely trust God
He's got my back, but I don't know how I like like, you know
I don't really do organized religion because of some really bad experiences
Through
Some pretty serious stuff. So it's it's I don't know. I'm a little spiritual. I'm a little God
I'm like I have a bunch of different things mixed up and I it works for me
I'm a lot of people be like when you can't do that
You can't you can't believe in crystals and witchy stuff and and Jesus and I'm like well
You can't tell me what I can't do because it's at the end of the day
I'm standing at the end of my road and no one else is gonna be there but me so whenever it works for me
I'm gonna let that work for me
and you know so
In my opinion, you sound a lot like me.
That's not really, I kind of feel like,
like I hadn't even thought about how it was my dad
who introduced me to astrology
until the morning of the stream with psyche.
I don't know why I hadn't thought about that in a while,
but I'm glad to have had the traditional,
You know, basically Southern Christian upbringing, that's my mom's side, but then some other things on my father's side, but a lot of people on my father's side are devout Catholics, actually, so I have a mixture, but I think that we all just got to figure out because it's only us experiencing our own life.
Have you ever seen Being John Malkovich, Alexandra, or Summer?
Have you seen that movie called Being John Malkovich?
I have seen that before I haven't I've not okay basically the plot is that there's an actor named John Malkovich
He's like a bald actor. He's like a lot of stuff, but it's like you know
He's kind of obscure, but he's well-known within Hollywood
So there's a camera and Diaz movie called being John Malkovich and basically this guy moves into the apartment
and he like finds a sort of like kind of like
Like a hole behind inside his apartment and he like looks in the hole and if you go into the hole you go into like
John Malkovich's head, and you're John Malkovich,
you get to just experience with John Malkovich,
experience it for like five minutes,
then you're back in reality.
But then he starts like charging people to go down the sole,
and then people get addicted to going,
and John Malkovich is kind of like...
like the real one is like kind of like what the fuck is going on like he's
losing kind of consciousness every five minutes but it's a really funny movie
it kind of kind of reminds me of that a little bit like you know experiencing
somebody else's actual consciousness which is like an interesting concept or
are we all the same consciousness that was consciousness the thing is it
Well, when you really think about the like, you know, the real streamers who actually
do IRL, especially from point of view perspective, POV, they are giving people who maybe aren't
able to go outside that sort of experience.
Yeah.
I saw a cat.
Right.
Well, I...
She was like, is she with Sam Rao?
Yeah.
Guys in prison on there, they got a hold of cell phones and they are all.
Oh, really? Yeah, something told me not to go on there.
I, they're on Facebook, too.
All right. I look, not to cut you.
I'm sorry, Zygie, but I was going through Facebook the other day, actually.
And I don't know who added me to some group.
I use Facebook a lot for a community stuff and local stuff.
I can get stuff done really quick.
Anyhoo, I'm going through my newsfeed and next thing I know there's like three dudes in a fucking cell all like with their shirts off
I was like, but it was just the fact of like
What the hell the fuck I even get in this group. I was like I guys and Joe like I'm done with that hole like I'm when I met
My husband I said I said listen
I've dated enough dudes that have been in and out of fucking Joe
I was like if you're on if you're in Joe or you're going to Joe. I don't want nothing to do with you
He's like no, I'm good. I'm like, all right
That was like my deal breaker. I mean because you know, I was
There wasn't a lot that was my deal breaker, but that was definitely my deal breaker. They really but they really really what?
a pen pal like even a guy they just want to they want someone to talk and fuck back
I can't do that life no more. Sorry
I would suggest avoid because you don't because you gotta be careful about who you're around because
their energy can transfer essentially to you just you know whether you want to call it influence
Yeah
We know about that that's empathy and intimacy, but a lot of people don't realize it's more than just you know
You can you can definitely swap it over people. Oh, well, do you know about sexual soul ties?
Have you ever heard of that concept? I do know about it. Yeah
That's why I'm look
As someone who has been very heavy in certain arenas,
I am the opposite today.
That's why I think it's funny certain people say certain things about me.
I will not say I'm celibate,
so I'm not celibate,
but I am very, very, very, very particular,
and my partners are feeling far between specifically because of that.
So I had the same part here for 18 years, so I'm good on that.
But I also came out of the adult industry.
So, um, oh, I didn't know that about you.
I did not know.
So thank you for sharing.
Cause now I understand.
Um, I've done, uh, I didn't do playboy. I had an opportunity to playboy, but I didn't do it. Um, and I'll, and the only reason was because at that particular time, and I wish I'd have done it in some sense, but then again, I'm glad I didn't sacrifice my morals for once in my life.
My grandfather was done. And so it was either I go and do a trial shoot or I go and do help him and I chose to go and help him. So I missed the opportunity.
I agree, I agree, but I've been, you know, I've been super, I've been awesome.
You're beautiful. I mean, I don't know what people in the chat are saying because you don't,
I guess y'all didn't see her in her bikini when it was that impromptu bikini beta titties thing.
Summer looks amazing. She won the contest, so all of you who are hatein', you can get a hell.
I'm just saying that orange was popping on you girl. I was like, okay
That's what made me you're the one that made me get up and get in the basement because I was like, wait a minute
So this is what we're doing today. I was like, all right
Here we go, here we go, all right
Breakdown, you know, Alex like you look great
The journey I'm on now, so I've been done this, you know, just about every part of the sex industry, adult industry you could do, right?
Um, you know, I've been a victim and I haven't been a victim and blah, blah, I've had a lot of shit happen or whatever, you know what I mean?
I've gotten to a point in my life to where I just love that, like, I'm healing and I'm healed, you know, I've healed from a lot of shit.
And I could for once, like, own and control my own sexuality.
Beautiful thing for me that like, oh, yeah, I'm all about jumping up on a bikini like I just not bothering one bit
You know, like I think about the negatives of when I was in that world
But I also think about like like here's my positive
No one in my entire life can ever tell me
That when I was young, I was not a hot little thing because I sure as fuck wise and so I have the proof
It's like really you're gonna say it's like we'll get to what?
You're you're pretty you're not an ugly woman alex
But it's different when you it is different when you hit almost 40. I'm I'm gonna be 47 next year
It's a little different. I'm for I'm 46 so
Oh, we're so we're the same age. So you you get it. Yeah, but I mean, I'll be honest with you though
Like this is for once. I mean, yeah, I mean, yeah, I was hot and all that stuff back then, right?
But like it's just different now like I like being I love being in my 40s. I am I know who I am
I'm comfortable with who I am and every aspect of it, you know, I mean like I'm like I said
I'm on this big journey because like I mean even though I work in the sex industry and all that kind of stuff like owning my sexuality
I mean, it was more of a job, right?
So like between the trauma and the job, it, you know, it was like, whatever.
So to be able to own it and like walk in it and appreciate your sexuality.
That's a, that's a pretty cool journey.
I'm really digging it.
It is.
Well, I mean, I get what you're saying because I've never, well, I did go
through a point where I regret it or I felt ashamed.
That's gone.
Okay.
Now I just feel like.
And that's what I was saying to psyche earlier. I'm like, you know, I got to watch the vanity because I feel like hey
I do look good for my age. Let me flex
So every once in a while you will see me in a bikini for no reason every once in a while
Yeah, you know just to do it
It is okay, and there's that they're wrong with that and you know people on the internet are gonna say whatever they're gonna say
But at the end of the day, maybe you know and you know I mean like we know we know so don't even worry about this
So do you well my my old like I always kept in contact with my old
Fans when I was in that world and they motivate it that you know if I am starting to look a little
Like I shouldn't they will tell me and I appreciate it
They're like, you might want to go into gym and I'm like, you know what? You're right. And when I do, they're like, Yay, you know, you need that because that is a part of me. And that's why I like to encourage. And like I said, psyche, whenever you, if you ever want me to, I will transform you.
I work out a lot.
Let me pay you back. Let me pay you back, please.
And I do that shit all the time. Don't ask psyche. I go to the gym. I'll be like, come on y'all. Let's do this
You know what I mean? Like I'm all about like fitness, but like I like
Like I want to be fit, but at the same time I like, you know, I'm saying I like being a little curvy, too
So I try to watch it because I love my life and be fit and curvy. Well, you're very curvy. You got all the curves
I think you stole hers from some people. I don't know who and I'm not I'm not gonna report you. Don't worry
It's definitely a fun curvy road at times
Look, I was happy to develop some curves cuz it
Up until even like my early 30s. I was still basically a stick then all of a sudden I gained some weight
And I'm just now becoming comfortable more so with where I'm really going to be
Going into you know late 40s early 50s
I'm happy about it. Like you said, I do like being the age I am now
But mainly because I've I've lived and I like having the knowledge base and the experience
Yep, and listen, I don't give a shit people would be like, oh you you oh tags. It's okay. It's you call me what you want
I don't give a shit because you know what I know that we still got it
So I ain't worried about that. I'm happy with me and what other people think I like your avatar picture
That's I'm just now looking at it cuz I'm like zooming in that's a badass picture girl
I just did a photo and it was one of the pictures from the photo shoot
Well, that's a beautiful and I like how you're sitting on the graffiti it like like there's a lot of unity in it because you have the beautiful tattoos
You got the red lipstick. You got the background with a little bit of red. It's mainly turquoise. You look like your son kiss
Oh black and white. Okay. Let's look at that
That's beautiful. So you're you're like a muse
That's you you're you're like a inspiration you're in news
No, I I just like you know, I mean, all right
Ooh, I like the one you're laying on the rock. Yeah here. I'll show you that over the summer
You did that this summer?
Well, well, no, I think I did it early in the very early beginning of year. Maybe last there's the end of last year
I can't remember well, it's recent. It's recent. Yeah
Go girl
Yeah, Alex Alex Electra made something for us. I just want to show you I
Love it. I love it that look I like when the little characters. I think it looks like me. I like it
Yeah, you only good. Is that is that um baroque eel is a baroque eel gonna appear. I think so
Well, it looks like Apollo kind of because he has a laurel the laurel crown and then like yeah, it could be a follow
Yeah, it looks a little bit Apollo-ish, but I mean in the Roman, the Roman toga kind of in the red cape and the
The archangel energy, but it's like who's to say that some of the gods weren't
Maybe the angels or something like that
And I think that they might have been yeah
I think that there's a lot of overlap when it comes to various forms of theology or religion
Yeah, somewhere. Do you like you like that banner though somewhere that banners cute
But I love the heart that go back to the little heart. I like that how that's in the middle
We like though I do like the banner, but I do like the way that just kind of
It was actually like on first it appeared here like and then I was like wow
I really like love this symbol like because we were talking about how like the Sun's rays are like the crown of forms
Yes
Yeah.
And then it's like, this came with a peacock, Alex, I don't know if you heard the part about
the peacock, but it's like, the peacock on his chest has a wound, but it's still like
beautiful.
It's still able to be beautiful and proud.
Also there's like old sea caps in right there.
There's like that.
These are all from the Sabian symbols from my astrology, I don't know if you're familiar
with the Sabian symbols, but they're basically a sentence for each degree of the zodiac.
So this is all the all the all the sentences of all my chart all put together or the symbols all brought together at one piece.
Interesting. So all of one mural, okay.
And if you go to my post, you go to my post in my community wall, it goes through every all the symbols and there's a whole story there.
But I even have more, you know, I get that there's a confirmation.
But I'm actually doing that if you if you guys if anybody is interested in having me go through your Sabian symbols creating you.
the art and then creating also music with it, too.
I can give you a song where they bring the symbolism
into it, also put a story to it,
but also go into some of your astrology, too.
So that'll be okay.
You know that, you can use me.
Use me, baby, use me.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice. So you so on the next show what we really got to do is break down
Kinds of packages that you offer because that's something you have clarified it verbally
But not in written form
Right, I know yeah, yeah, I'm getting more like now that I have like my my website set up
I do have like a booking program set up through there and I have like you know, I actually have my power chat
Is set up for your stream labs and stuff like that
I just had I was always doing the panel and it's like it's not quite perfectly compatible with StreamYard yet
But I'm trying to learn OBS too, which is a really great
If you want to learn OBS tap me tap me for that because I can walk you through it
I consider OBS sometimes like you heard me say I'm like oh, yeah, I'm doing this ghetto style, but you're right
It's not um get um OBS you can do a lot more and you can um
Implement it with stream. Yeah, I do both at the same time. Yeah, you can bring it up
Yeah, well the power because for the power chat like you know, that'd be a reason I would want to
Be connected through there. So it would just say it out loud on the screen automatically
allows you to create something called a virtual camera, so like whatever's on your screen right now you can overlay stuff on
OBS on your screen and you can just make it a little bit more fancy-shrancy
Yeah, I'll be working on that. I'm working on some of this stuff. I'm gonna see if I I'll show you my the power chat link
If anyone wants to help me test it, let me see. Hold on a second
I might help myself to see if I see and then it's like well power chat is what Elisa uses and she was like don't even
Don't even bother with the super chat. Just use power chat. It does go to like I
Immediately to like a bank account
Let's see. Yeah from what I've heard at the guy who created power chat. He was a streamer
Um, he you know power chat is specifically for streaming everything about yeah
What which one?
That's the one that a lot of the really high traffic streamers use.
You can get the donations through it.
You can get a little media to play with the donation when people send it.
They can copy and paste the YouTube link.
They have all kinds of overlay apps.
It's really good. You should check it out summer.
You really should.
I have to talk to her about she helps me with all my stuff like that. I'm so not good with that, but
Katrina's amazing
You know Katrina yeah, she could be a Katrina's awesome. Yeah
Super super super mod here. I think I think she's I
Didn't mod it. I'm not everybody and remod them. And so sometimes I'm slow to get to hey
Is that the real person or I like seeing things I
Don't I have certain people blocked for obvious reasons
I'm not against them being in the chat or you know, it's your stream
But there's some people that I don't communicate with and they know why
Yes, okay, so I'm gonna leave so that other people can have
You might want to maybe she wants to come up if you will come up I will leave
Yeah, we're having a good time because anyone that I talk to she basically wants to be me
and I'll say it so she might want to come up maybe she wants some psyche insight and she
should definitely receive your insight if anyone should receive your insight psyche
it's her when I really think about it so if she wants to come up I will gladly come down
Well, I don't think she's coming up, but let's see.
I did put the power chat link and I'll bring up
my stream labs and so I don't know if I'll be able
to like actually like share my screen today
with the donation comes through and it will play it on air.
Click and like, you know, always replay it.
I'm just still testing it.
If you guys want to help me out,
I think it's just like, I mean, you can have your message
right on the air, you can say anything you want to me.
I'll read it no matter how bad it is.
I just can't say TOS works, okay?
So only thing is be careful with the power chat. You it does give you the ability to block certain words
You're not going to want things that go against what your own rules are
Yeah, I think I put I put some of those I put some of those words in and so hopefully all the words I can
Yeah
Yeah, so let me see stream yard or stream labs stream labs. Oh, yeah, they have a really easy little
Program called launch pad or something. Oh, there it is. Okay, and then it's like
One more suggestion for you psyche before I go because you're gonna hate me because I do put my nose where I should
Lighting psyche. I have I have the lighting look I have lighting now
It's more lighting on your wish list, please
Okay
There's there's like a goal of
Adhesive LED lights that you could
Yeah, summer has some good lighting examples. Summer's gonna be the model for the for the lighting. There we go
Hey summer you look good you look good
That's what that's what I'm talking about put that on your wish list psyche, okay. Yeah, thank you summer
Put that on your wish list today. Put that on your wish list. Thank you. Thank you so much. I will a lot of us
We want to we want to trick you out a little bit. We want to make it look
Do you put put a couple of them on there, right? Cuz one's yeah, you're gonna have to have you'll need you'll need like two or three
Yeah, I
Want to want this to be a really cool
Cool area or maybe see my alien
Oh my gosh, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on my floor, it's on
He sent me a little friend. I just put on my wishlist and then oh, it's like so awesome
I wake up every morning. I wake up in like
And I have some good life I have some a rural borealis
That feels so good to be the I've been working all day
Yeah, well, yeah
And I know you work hard and I'm gonna show y'all how dirty my floor is
Hold up. I'm gonna show I'm gonna show you. Oh look at how dirty my floor is
It's nothing but dirt
Uh-oh. That's horrible. It's all dirt. What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do? Mine's dirty. It was in your psyche. Look how dirty it is.
Look at look at there's a I got rocks and stuff. It's it's nothing but dirt
Nothing but dirt you better do somebody better do like a whole three hours stream about my dirty floor
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think that you know I went on that I went on somebody's show the other day that
Had a lot of to say and then like someone was saying to her they're like or someone had said to her
Oh, you know
Same matter, you know, it's her parenting skills and she was like, oh, what look at these people
They don't even know me and they're talking about parenting skills
I'm like that's like do you see how I feel now you don't even know me you're talking about my my cat father's skills
I was like, that's karma. She's like, that's not karma
Then I went on a panel it is. Yeah, it is karma
But all it is all it is is like, you know, like
Up
Is it just me
Okay, well hold it down. So everybody, my floor is dirtier than everybody else's. Sorry. I have the dirtiest floor in the community.
No one can beat me. I want my trophy for being the dirtiest. I'll be the dirtiest girl.
I'll be the dirtiest girl in the community. Nothing but dirt.
Nothing but dirt.
Oh, you you look like summer and your summer dress. Yeah, it's like a little jammy things or a romper
We're in charge now we're in charge of the stream wait, let's see if I have a dirty floor
There we go
So. Dirty floor. Yeah.
All right. Well, we're going to be the dirty crew. We're getting dirty.
We're the dirty crew. Right out. Everybody right out.
Let's be dirty. What does he have? We're going to be the dirty, we're the dirty.
Hey, hey, you're not dirty little cat. Look at you.
He's like, I'm clean. Damn, mama.
I'm going to jump on this thing over here and jump all over your head.
There's the boy. He says, Hey, you guys say, how do we do?
They're spoiled, spoiled little buddy.
It's good to spoil the kitties, the kitties and the puppies and whatever else kind of I used to have a neighbor who had little pigs, little toy pigs, basically.
Oh, yeah, much can pigs. I don't know what you call them, but they were tiny, but it was crazy
I remember the first time I saw my son. I thought I didn't know what kind I thought was a dog
I was like a dog is that she's like it's a pig
And she had multiple she had like three of them and they were really cute though
My mom had I still been so my father's had a family was in Chicago and my mother's had a family lived down here
So I would bounce back all the time
Um, and I come back from Chicago one time to visit my mom and she had a potbelly pig running around
I was like what in the hell lady? I was like just because we're in kateke
But it was cute. It was that's what they're called the potbelly. I couldn't I didn't know what they were called
I remember telling me they were potbelly pigs
But they were so like they were full grown, but they were like the size of a small dog. They were really cute
Um, she had a black one. She had a brown one and she had one that was like
Callico kind of it was like brown black white everything. Yeah, this one was like that
It had a bunch of brown and white and just it was really
He did the cute little shit. He
This is run around the house with a little fat ass
They're cute. They're cute like it's hard when you see him so cute because it makes you guilty about eating pork or
You know, whatever. All right. Yeah, psyche has a message. She says since psyche a message read aloud on the show
Power chat somebody test the power chat, and we want to see if it works
Or she somebody down there we could do the power check
Send him some donations ask him for a reading someone should get a reading today
People should get readings today
What is his what is his what is his handles like he awakens on power chat
Um, yeah, it's those. Let's see.
What do you say?
Yeah, it's like the Awakens.
Okay.
I'm trying to get some.
If no one tests it, I'm going to test it.
If nobody's been in.
Okay.
Do you want a reading today, Summer?
I'll treat you to a reading.
Sure, I'll take one right here.
All right, let me try to get into the power chat.
Let's see.
Let me see.
Do you feel like doing a reading today?
Yeah, for sure.
Absolutely.
I don't know what I did to my screen.
I have like some other kind of screen up.
Oh, I can close it.
Oh, that's okay.
Oh yeah, I think I'm fine.
Let's see here.
What is going on?
We're going to test.
Oh, here. That's perfect.
Let's get my cards out.
And I can actually bring it up on my...
Um, okay, wait a minute. You don't...
Okay, I'm trying to do it. It says,
you do not have any valid payment methods.
Si awakens.
PSY awakens.
Oh, okay.
I think I...
Let's see.
All right, let's try again.
Let me get it backstage.
Let me see it.
I don't know how it comes through, but let's do it.
Okay.
I'll see.
Let me see.
So this is, what website am I?
I do see the powerchats come out.
Let me see if they have this.
It's working.
Hold on.
Let's make sure everything's good.
Okay.
I set.
Let's see if it goes through.
Okay, let's see if it works.
Okay, it says completed on this end.
Yeah, I know it's like that.
So I think you have to pay to use it. I don't think you have to I don't know you have to pay to use a psyche like if you're a creator
No, I mean there's a there's a premium version of it. They take a person. Thank you, Jenny
And thank you Jenny too for the super chat. That's awesome. Thank you. I
Don't I don't know if they take it not as mean YouTube takes a
Kind of a 30% I don't know that that's the super chat work. Thank you. Jenny. You're getting a reading today for sure
Um, let me see if I, I might have to bring it on, on stage.
Will it went through on this end? It didn't pop up on the thing.
Yeah, mine went through, but it didn't pop up on the end.
Okay, let me, I mean, if I share the screen, it might be on my,
because I have it set up down here. So it's a power chat, right? Okay, there we go.
I think this one, okay, let me see.
Share, uh-oh, I have it there, let me see.
Oh, I see, it's all on this stuff, okay.
I don't know if I can share the screen
on something off my tabs, so, all right.
I'll see if it came through there, let me see, okay.
Don't see but maybe it's slow. I have to ask my
Well, there's like a there's like a
Code that you'll need to insert in an overlay whether you're using OBS or something else
That's how you know
I did a test of it and I mean the test went through.
Oh, I see, hold on.
There we have it, here.
Jenny girl, Jen Jen sent,
I got it, it went through the,
it went through the, this one, let me see.
I'll try to, see if I can share the screen.
Super chat, that's $4.99 one.
Yeah, no, no, it's a, oh yeah, that was a super chat,
but it did get, oh yeah, but I see it through here, hold on.
So, oh, school bath and sent,
the C sent a super chat or a-
That's a super chat.
Okay
And he dropped it a second ago
Drop your power chat link again, that's kind of up, but now
Let's see
Where's my okay? Oh
I see. Oh, I can I can pick it. See this is my central thing. This is the thing right here. I want to share this one
Hey, so do you see this yet? There
And so, see, I can see, like, this chat, right?
You see, you guys see right here?
Let me see if I go back.
No, I don't see.
Oh, yeah, I need to bring it up there.
Oh, come on, gosh, I have to bring it up.
I'm so sorry.
I thought that reads it, don't it?
Like, have a little voice,
because I picked a little voice.
So, yeah, yeah, I mean, it's like,
it should have the voice, but it's like,
because, I mean, I can play,
I think you will play on that on the screen.
If I were going to show the screen,
I think the voice will play.
I just,
Okay, there okay
Let's see. So yeah, right here. So this is what it looks like right there. See so I think we're coming
Oh, here's some school bathrooms coming in. Okay one second
Or it says Santa, hold on. That's cool. Vapins are Santa. I don't know Santa. I don't know if I trust Santa. Oh, it is cool
Hey, but you see guys
Sorry, I didn't you
Yeah, I apologize. It was a little bit loud. Whoa. Anyway, we could see what he's been but then not super loud
I'll put a full screen. Here you go. Oh look, it's Nick
What's up, Nick? Oh
That's Nick
I think that's a thing. I thought it was cool bathrooms or Santa Claus, uh-oh. Oh, yeah
Yeah, it's probably Nick. I think those abs belong to Nick
Yep
Oh, there he is, looking good Nick, oh there he is, from his shadow, let's see what else
can I share, let me see, I can share like some stuff, let me see, I'll try to present
shares. Okay, image file. Okay. You have the top, it's the DTS overlay and put it in a
screen. That's what you see. Yeah. Yeah, let me see. I can do, oh yeah, I can be using a
simple one, but then I'll use the more, the other one, see if I have anything not
I don't want to make a mess back about it.
Okay.
Let's see.
Downloading.
Okay.
I don't know what to do.
There we go.
Okay, I need other back guys and I need to be okay
That's a nice view actually skateboarding is he on a skateboard or a scooter
is read in.
I'm sorry
If we're there, can you hear me?
You're now I'm back. I was typing. Sorry
I
Didn't know what happened. I felt I while I fell when I picked my kid
Okay
We have sound holler
What's up Memphis, how you doing baby 420 Amanda was all in the check
I'm so sorry guys
Don't talk. I mean I was a Jamie. What's up? Hello as I was like I fell off and then I'm like damn
Is it me? So then I jumped off again because I didn't hear anything
But then I realized the chat didn't hear anything either. So I hung out
He mans in the house
She's hot. I made some pasta. She's hot as hell, but it's good
Nick's frozen and I think psyche's probably trying to fix his super thing with jigger power chat
Can you hear me playing a song real quick. Oh, I don't hear the song
But I can't hear it so I'll fix it shit
Yeah, it's not I don't hear it on my end at all
We're having some technical difficulties everybody we will get back to it as soon as we figure it out
How's everybody's day it's been beautiful in Kentucky, I don't know about where you all are at
But it's been gorgeous last couple days man, and it's supposed to get hot again, but I am really enjoying this like fall weather
bound bound bound bound
What happened to your scooter
See, it's good. I changed the smart plugs and a few things. I was running great now
Shit it would feel good to ride a scooter right now or a motorcycle. Oh my goodness
Hmm
420 if any of us get on your thing you just
Criminals you have to stop to stop son
Or to want to be floating
Yeah, that's how it's been here. It's been it off. It was so good. I'm so over that fucking hundred plus weather
Summer yes, I know yeah, you sound far away, but I can hear you
I'm so sorry. Yeah, they didn't go through they didn't go through a summer summer said love you and then um and then
Alice I said reading for summer. Thank you so much Alex for the ten dollar
Power chat and summer for the three dollar power chat. So thank you so much appreciate you
And I will figure out how to have them read on this on this on the screen soon
But I mean it's like I was I did I was able to go to the website and they were there
And so I don't know whether or not happening to the other
thing but let's see uh i do have like a little song i made like about about the goddess psyche
this is about the goddess psyche you want to hear it somewhere sure and then i'll do your
reading okay this will get me in the mood for you i trust you for 20 i know you wouldn't hurt us
okay so let me just have a there's my mousy okay
we'd have to go get us a top smear
This is my mind. We're back. 74 where you're at? Shit, that's nice.
Jamie said it's 100 in Cali. Yeah, I was watching somebody streaming Cali and they were talking about
how hot it was. Yay. Oh, I put something on my belly.
I was hangry. The only thing I ate today was a bag of little bag of chips.
If it's nice tomorrow, I'm like,
it's the thing I gotta work. Maybe we'll go down to the walking bridge. Oh, there goes all.
Her lover came with hidden wings a secret kept from sight
Trust the darkness don't betray
Love is more than eyes can see
But doubt crept in like candle flame burning curiosity
Love is
Stay
Yeah, that was nice. That was very calming
It was a nice melody
I like your topic here
I had to change summer I saw you look in summary and I was like I'm not
summery enough I have to be summery I had to match you I know I know I I just
like that if I see somebody wearing something I'm like yeah you look cute
let's party
I don't know where I might have problems with my camera, do you hear my voice though?
I hear you.
We hear you perfect.
I like that.
Even gods can bend and break, but the heart learns what the state is.
Love will fall, but rise again.
Well, I'm gonna acknowledge the chat. Let's see who's in here
Let's see, let's see
See yes, I just bought some cherry dr. Pepper had it that's crazy
So there's tariffs on dr. Cherry Pepper
There's
That's nuts. They're gonna try to do whatever they can do to make everybody poor
That's the agenda
Hello
I'm sorry my camera's not work every time I sort of put the camera on it like he's like it's like
Exiting me from the studio, so I'm not sure but I have to be my voice right now, but I can still do shoot
I would love to be able to maybe I can make a picture put it on the screen of the full reading
But I'll do some rooms reading
Okay, it'll be
It'll be verbal, but we'll see.
That's OK.
OK.
I'm a good reader for summer and Jenny wants one as well.
OK, so summer, if you're first you
have the two of Pentacles, the two of Pentacles
that says a journey into equilibrium.
And so it's really been getting stabilized
in the recent past.
And even though it's been a little bit rough water,
sometimes you've really got your hands on things
and are able to make the necessary adjustments.
good balance and equilibrium, so you're coming from a really good place where you're mentally
and physically everything's in balance.
You also have the seven of wands, the seven of wands is like you know traditionally somebody
they're holding up a wand and they've got all these like you know villagers surrounding
them like you know the kind of people with the pitchforks and stuff like that and maybe
you feel like you are.
You are kind of like under attack by certain people and like having to defend yourself
It says traps, but who is the monster but because it's that it's actually a picture of Frankenstein
You know and he's he's holding off the villagers and it's like are they the monster or is he the monster and you know
It's interesting questions
In that in that car of the
Seven of wands, which is but it's basically acting for you is like basically defend this
Equal the room you have and make sure you know it because he's also kind of balancing this about balancing this stick
like he's like balancing the way right and so
It's maintaining this maintaining your equilibrium. Also. We have the night of swords. Okay night of swords
Uh night of swords is somebody that comes rushing in and out
really good communicator but that is always like you know coming going one of
the fastest of the of the nights he's most likely to just come stop by real
quick and then beyond his way also you know the air signs are kind of known as
They're very intelligent, good with money, and sometimes associated with spy crafts and
things like that.
But this is maybe somebody coming to you, bringing you news or something like that, some kind
of communications incoming for you, that you've been waiting for.
Also we have this magician card that says, he...
holds the power of all the elements in the palm of his hand as the magician so
this is like also you having all the resources you need you have everything
you need to continue to manifest what you have and also to manage you know to
use the elements at your disposal to create whatever you want in this world
because you know all the everything is made up of these elements and so basically
you want to manifest anything you can you know start start with the materials
right you also have the eight of cuffs okay eight of cuffs is saying to me
That okay, so this is like in this deck is
It's like a lot of overwhelming emotion and maybe like I feel like this this moon energy
This new moon energy might have been like for kind of emotional for you too, but also like
You're also starting to like see things like
It's kind of things are coming out of the illusion of the moon, but it was passing
I would believe but yeah, you also have you know this a to comes is also a to also the number of strength
And I know you're very attached to the
Raise some some simpatico with the strength card, right? No, I said really see that for you
So I say you have the strength of your emotion to also the strength of the manifesting
Oh in the seven of cups also, so there's gonna be a lot of options presented towards you
Coming up and it's like a lot of them will look good a couple of them are like it's like only let's make a deal
It's like behind like hurt number one hurt number two hurt number three
I mean, it's like there might be there might be a like a you know the whammy or whatever they call
I don't know what you know when they
There might be one of those hidden in there.
Some of the cups are not positive, right?
There's seven doors.
There might be like two or three of those
that are false things that will make you happy, probably.
So I would say concentrate on actually
what you really want and choose wisely, okay?
Because there's a lot of stuff that you want
in those cups that will make you very happy, okay?
I'll do another part of advice.
Okay, we have the nine of wands.
It says, okay, we have another one of these.
Huh, this is like, you know, kind of like, you know, secure your force, you know, you know
Dig the mode a little bit deep or something. It's a survival is a matter of perseverance and vice versa
And so it's like I say be vigilant because I still think you do have these negative forces trying to
Not not distract you but just like trying to interfere with your work somehow because it is good work
I mean, it's like a good hard to work and whatever that happens. It's like there's
These demons all of a sudden come out try to you know, try to cause all these kind of problems
Just stand your ground and it's like, you know, you might be too might continue to go through through it a fight
You know, you might go through a fight, but just like don't let it
Affects you too bad mentally don't let to keep you up at night like too much because
You know, there's a lot of it. There's a lot of maybe
energy being sent to you in a negative energy because to interfere with whatever
good works you're doing I would say you know just keep keep cleansing and keep
mentally strong and know that you know you know you know how much of a fighter
you are you know how strong you are it's like you you have you have all the in
this magician you have everything you need to succeed and to win I'm gonna put
a little more cards though oh page of swords okay page of swords is the
It's a somebody's watching you kind of thing. It's like it's like they're not in a not necessarily in a bad way
It's upright. It could be somebody watching you and just seeing your progress and wanting to make me work with you
And maybe it will grow into something but to see this night and the page of swords. There's definitely some
Lot of energy communication coming right around this time for you. Okay, so so be vigilant and
You know and be on your guard too. It says you might need to be on your guard because I don't know if you can trust
Everybody you're talking to not ever since sure. Okay
Sounds about right
Good advice and I definitely have been feeling more balance than you know, so yeah, I definitely like that
You did a good job as always
Thank you so much. I hope that was helpful for you and you know you enjoyed and
You know, I think you know Jenny Jenny paid for a reading and or if you would like one
I'm not sure she'd like one right now, or you know or she or and also school bathrooms
If you want one I'm happy to pull cards for you
Or if not, it's not that I'll pull like I'll do one card reads of another deck for anybody that would like
I wish my camera was working
It's working, but it's not working on this. I don't know if my browser for some reason. That's really weird
And I had knocked it out.
Are you on a cell phone or like a regular computer?
I'm on a regular computer.
And my camera was plugged in, but then I
think I hit the quarter or something,
and now it's acting funny.
Here's what you do.
Unplug and re-plug your webcam if it's through USB
or something along those lines.
And then restart your browser, because that's
going to reset the driver.
OK.
Okay, I'll be right back. I got a phone call. I'll be right back. She's talking to the
chat for like two minutes, Alex. Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, absolutely I will. Okay, I'll be
right back. I'm just sitting here. I'm plugging in my cell phone right now to my battery backup.
That way I can turn my camera back on. Okay, I'll be right back. And I'll turn my camera
Hey everybody. How are you doing? Welcome to Psyche Awakens Chat. I'll be professional.
I hope everyone out there is having a nice day. I changed my top because I wanted to match summer.
Her vibes just make me feel a little bit more summery, so I felt like I needed to put on something
Amazingly discounted readings for those of you who might just want to brief reading as to where you are in life and maybe a little bit of insight and a little bit of, you know, direction as far as where you're going. Sometimes we all need that from time to time.
Like I said, at the end of my little stream that I did the other day with Psyche, he gave me some excellent, excellent advice when he pulled that final card.
He was very correct, but what I like about readings when I think about it is that you really are truly getting another person's perspective, like a third person point of view as to where you're at.
where you're going, what you should do, what you shouldn't do.
And a lot of it really has to do with just making good choices.
That's why I've always had, you know, a draw personally to astrologers because sometimes
our ego stands in our way of knowing what's good for us
and making good choices. Like nowadays I make better choices because I think about everything that my dad taught me
Here in this existence, I didn't always pay as much heat or attention as I probably should have
but
You know
Take the time to listen to people who are really looking at you
Because sometimes they see things that maybe you miss
at times
All right, so I was just saying, yeah, I hear you perfect.
I hear you perfect.
Thanks for letting me hang out on your panel today.
I appreciate it.
It's fine.
You've always been to hang out with your, oh, I just,
I love your energy and your bright, uh.
Well, Summer added to my energy.
She got me a change my top.
There you go. I'm pink girl now. A lot of times, you know, I gotta, I gotta take cues fashion-wise for summer because I think I wear a little bit too much gray.
I'm starting to realize that I went through like a gray phase. Everything I have almost is gray, black, white, and red.
This is like the only color top I have right now.
You know I ordered some shirts. I think I might have ordered finally like well
I'm actually I want to put that heart on like some of my merchandise and I want to get some I want to get that
Yes, yes, you should you should definitely do that. I saw the um
I saw the merchandise you have right now, which is beautiful. I like the cat. I like the cat a lot
I know a lot. I'll probably get maybe I'll get bigger merchandise for Christmas presents this year
Oh, I I know people with I'm I don't I'm not a cat. I'm not a cat girl the cats like me
But I'm trying to not have pets
My life but the cats like me
My dad and his partner have two beautiful little cats
And, um, one of the cat, well, both of the cats at some point might end up becoming my cats, and that's when I'll have to be in one place.
So, I don't like being only in one place. I'm a little, that's where I'm spoiled. I like being in different places.
A sign of travel and the sign of like wanting to be at other places and me you're a lot
But I think since it's in my 12th house with Venus in the 12th house
Which is the house of kind of seek is a house of darkness secrets and all kinds of stuff like but I have Neptune and Venus in this
12th house and
It makes it's basically saying you're gonna meet somebody either from abroad or like somebody of like a very different than you
Like something like a completely different like something like or so maybe I'll need to travel in order to meet somebody because it's certainly not having any luck
You know sitting at home. I did the grinder does not work
I just like you're saying like you're not really like promiscuous the promiscuous. I'm not promiscuous either
I was not because of the section
the thought of sexual ties or, you know, of sexual ties, sexual soul ties from, you know, the...
Getting all our energy all mixed up with people that we just like see one time. We'd maybe dive in like like and stuff like that
So I think some of their traits on it, right?
And so you got to be careful who you share your bottles bodily fluids with I think they are very known as very powerful
mediums of magic. Yeah, and so you want to be careful with like, you know, who you share those with and what the intention is with
Everything, you know, it's like
But they say, you know, sex is a very powerful act of creation, you know, it creates a human being.
And so there's a lot of magic in that.
It can create more than a human being.
You just got to be careful with any sort of intimacy.
And intimacy is one of the most powerful things.
I mean, think about it.
You know, I guess the physical manifestation of intimacy would be the exchange of bodily fluids, right?
But, I mean, with the exchange of bodily fluids, your energy is in that, so you have an extreme energetic exchange when you're sexual with somebody.
Yeah, because isn't it like a form of consciousness or consciousness or something, there's like
some kind of form of your consciousness within that, but yeah, and so.
Yeah, yeah, I'm going to go and slice my pizza out, I'm making a pizza right now, but um.
You know what the adult actors and actresses know there's there's a few in these communities
I didn't know about summer having worked in along those lines, but there's a there's a few
There's a few chatters
That are my friends who quietly are males who worked in the industry who are around and
We all pretty much
share the same
thought on that because
Well, they say the body renews every seven years. I think that's about right. I
know it took me a solid
seven years to
Feel free of certain things from my past and
No, Matt, you know, it's funny. I mean the last time I was in a scene as far as being an adult actress that was in
Oh, gosh. 2011 maybe. Now we're in almost 2026. So it's been such a long time, but it's
funny. People don't let you let it go. And you're like, really, it's been this long.
Yeah, I think if that's all you can say, why are you watching so much adult content? That's what I'm wondering for Ellie
I'm just kind of like come on
The young people nowadays, it's nothing to them because they're inundated with everything
Visual audio is nothing. It's really the people of my generation, but the people of my generation, I guess
Well, well, you're around my so I gotta say we're the same generation
We were kind of like in the 80s they kind of had the beta max and like you know
It was added that kind of the theaters like kind of theater kind of thing and they're fine
Like so the pornography was all of a sudden available on like a videotape
Which was like you know and readily available at the you know every video store, but then it's like
You know they came up with the internet and it really
Is like there's nothing in it anymore. There's everything every fetish every
everything. Yeah. You can make anything you want to see that was on the internet and so it's just
easily accessible with your analysis are you 18 and they didn't go yes or no and it's like what
how hard is that to bypass. I know right? Yeah. Yeah. Well it's going to be to where they want like
a fingerprint probably or like a face.
analysis to determine. I know that's what some of the systems are using now.
The kids nowadays, well I shouldn't say kids, but the young people nowadays,
they're not impressed by it. Like, I feel like, well, like in the industry,
People talk about okay. What was the last golden age of that world? I would say
Yeah, the early
2000s was the last like like when it got to where they were doing the
What do you call it the I have a brain part a brain fog right now
Yeah, the AV and the conventions that used to coincide with the tech conventions
And that that was when things were getting wild, okay, because the the adult industry drives the
technology or at least it used to because guys wanted to see the women clear, crisper,
more fluid video. They really, you know, they wanted to get off to where they felt like it was
the VR, the virtual reality and everything, that's all driven by the adult industry.
I mean, I even...
Well, it's a multi-billion dollar industry, so it's like, yeah, to put the money into
it, yeah, they're putting a lot into it.
They're trying to make the robots right now, right?
They have the real doll, they just have to put the real doll.
I don't know what else we want them to do, but it's like, you know, it's...
Pretty much, you know, they can get pretty much close.
They have all the parts already, just put it together.
Well, look, they already have it.
They've already done it.
And that was, I mean, I think that I was,
you know, maybe not me.
There's another woman in this community
who might've been the very, very, very end.
of the last golden age.
But what I like about it is that you'll never have
that age again, you're never gonna have the girls
that were like the real girls signing
to where you had lines of guys.
Like I'm so happy I got to experience that
because it's an ego of this.
Well, I'm thinking like if Jenna Jamison,
a little Jenna Jamison, I'm thinking like Howard Stern,
like, you know, who actually would have a porn star on
and then he would like interview them like they were,
you know, you know, Barbara Streisand and stuff like that.
You should reach out, you should reach out to Jenna
to have her on your show.
Why not? I think you should. Every once in a while, I do talk to her. Maybe she'll come on your show.
Would you want to have different people on your show who I think that like really there's women in these communities?
I think that you know who you should do a stream with.
Tritilitis.
Yeah, yeah, I think I think that you I think that because she's open
Spiritually to a lot. I think that you would really enjoy talking with her
Yeah, you know what I'll suggest that I'll just do a stream suggesting and I'll know she'll hear it
Maybe she'll want to come on your show. Thank you. I would I would yeah, I would love to have her as a guest and
Because I do remember like in the 90s. There's also like a there's also the voice that
Chichi LaRue is actually this drag queen like port gay porn director and then like
There's also like
Remember a Buck Angel have you heard of Buck Angel? Yes. Yeah, I'm very aware of Buck Angel. Yes
Yeah, I feel there's porn star, but it's a female to male transgender
But you know one of the first ones that I saw like on the talk shows in the 90
I was a big talk show person in the 90s. I just love
My mom my mom is what got me like hip and height to a lot of
My mom always wanted me to be a talk show has that's probably why I do what I do
But she she does watch and I she doesn't always admit it but she does and
Yeah, it's funny what influences us when we're young, but when you were, if you had not become a
Tarot reader, what would what do you think you would do?
Well, I
Might just be like I just think
The tarot reading is such a big part of my spirituality that I just think I'd probably be like a less spiritual person
I probably I don't know if I'd be around because it's like
you know, spirituality has brought me a lot of peace and ability to stick with the material world,
even though it's really difficult sometimes.
It's having faith, and I have a faith that everything will turn out okay, everything will be fine.
Or at least, you know, I think, yeah, I think I really love it.
Like, you know, I'm not gonna, like, go into life with luck and stuff.
I've already been, like, throwing everything with the kitchens, including the kitchens sink,
thrown at me in terms of, like, accusations and slander and just, like, you know, demeaning
and bullying.
I've had everything, and it's like, I'm still here, it's like, I just take everything, you
know, I've been building the kitchen.
Everything that they said to you, because I was looking, I was like, okay.
Let me investigate. What are they saying to psyche everything? They said to you. They said to me if not worse. It's really
But it's not bad because you're you're kinder than me. I wish I could be like you
Because I tend to
Fight back in the worst of ways and I'll admit that but what people don't understand
I think people like to act like I'm the antagonist. I'm really not I just fight back when I hit somebody
I do hit them to where they can't get up
And I was taught to be that way because it's survival
But I wish I wasn't like I said, I wish I didn't have the hard shell that I have sometimes
I'm trying to soften up. I've been listening to
softer music I've been trying to re-engage with my own femininity in a lot of ways
Yeah, I'm trying. I'm trying. Oh, it's working, but I'm trying. I'm working today
Well, I think you're like you're like a beautiful blend of like, you know, masculine and feminine qualities
And that's like that maybe it's like insulting. I don't know if it's not insulting. No, it's not. No, no, no
I use honestly, I used to get insulted. I used to be
insults when people are like you're kind of a masculine woman and I'm like, huh, let me embrace that
I am actually
I am a little bit of a masculine woman.
I'm definitely very independent if you want to deem that as a masculine trait.
My voice, I have an extreme range with my voice. I inherited that from my mom.
My mom used to be a professional opera singer before she went into education.
I can do a lot of things with my voice and I can understand why my voice would be perceived as a little bit masculine because I have a lower range, my natural speaking voice.
Yeah, your voice is like.
Michael Jackson has a much like a much higher voice.
I'm relating to the Jackson family a lot of people believe me when I say I actually am yes.
When I was younger, I was very athletic. So that could be masculine. I tend to
About like that. Yeah, you're talking about your qualities where it's like you're just like so
Strong as if we would say maybe a little bit aggressive
Yeah, yeah, and so and so that's like that's like I'm more talking about them
Like I can never think because everything is like very feminine feminine
Appearance what well, that's what makes people uncomfortable
Well, I was in the I was in the adult industry. Well, the authority that's you're actually it's it's my dad that you're seeing
Okay, I used to get mad at my dad when he was with us and he would be like, you know, Alexandra
You're just like me
You're my you're you are exactly like me. You're my clone. You might go that far. Okay, and I'd be like, no
Dad, I still got mom and in me too and
But that was just a part of it and I think about what I'm saying that to me now
That was him saying I love you very much
That's what it was
But there is I'm definitely I have the masculine within me, but I like it like I sometimes I wonder like if I was a man
What would I be like? What would I do? I well if I was I would probably I would be horrible. Oh my god
If I was a man I
Would have so much. Oh, I would I would have so much fun
Oh, I have fun now as a woman, but if I was a man
Oh, it would be ridiculous.
That's why I think I was designed as a woman instead of a man.
Because if I was a man, please, please.
A lot of these men who think that they're doing stuff,
I would have already pounded them into the ground.
I just would have.
Yeah, you're gonna have some fun like I think I would like to be a woman like in a future life like because I
Just like I have more of a female mind
But it's like it then I like I have like a male very much in the body and like I think mostly masculine
Personally, I think well, you know, here's what I think about you. Do you mind me giving you a
Alexandra reading it's not yes, I love it
Read me. It's all like BWM, right? Do you mind?
Don't get don't get mad don't get mad
Okay, I actually feel that you are an alpha
you have a very alpha quality about it, but you're afraid of that part within you.
I think that you do hold back tremendously. I've seen some glimpses already of who I think you're
probably going to...
You're going and I'm not saying that you're not evolved or that you'd even need to shift
I just kind of see something in you
You definitely have that alpha quality
But I think that you hold back and I think that the reason that you do is because you might have scared people in the past
hmm
Here a lot of people
Yeah, there's people and people will people get scared like I'm not necessarily scary, but
There are people that in my chance that chase away people and scare them with trolling and then it's like sometimes
I'm in a bad mood like yelling at people and it's like
But people people come in and they I'm like a mean person or rather than you just hear someone other shows
I'm not I'm not like I'm really forgiving it too. And it's like I really do love all people
and what the best for people and
You know, I want people to like
Go either evolve, you know
To the their highest so you know at the north of the north star
They're the best the best side of them because our south node
There's gifts in there, too, and there's like and we can have the benefits of that sign
But the but really like the negative parts of it are like really
Accentuated there and it's in like the positive will really be positive if you like go to that higher self
rather than
With ns like it's hard, but it's like I think it's
Always like nudging you and I think it's like I think God God knows it might be a slow process
But God ultimately you're part of God. He wants it be collected back into him
You know, it's like
to the all back into the all and then maybe the turn into a billion stars again and then
for eternity just keep thinking
the big bangs
Continuous processes and of creation destruction, but that's but every that's all in these lower planes and then like do
Higher planes where we're like really are and we're really from the spirit a real spiritual place
That's like eternal and that's like, you know, all we have to worry about is finding a body and
incarnating and that's like we were a race of a billion or about 60 billion sperm or something like that
We were like this one the we're the one that won that race right if that was a huge race imagine that
That was a giant rate. I'm so glad you brought that up actually because think about that.
It's almost impossible. It's not impossible. I mean, when you think about mathematically
statistic wise, how many sperm there would be and then the tips, you got to put that on top of that.
So, all of us who actually exist, who are humans, who have grown to adulthood, we're
all miracles.
When you really think about that, when you think about just the numbers of, like, it
could have been whatever sperm was right behind us that could have become who we are instead
of who we are.
thing to think about when you really really really think about it um
Yeah, and all the all the sperm would have been our brothers and sisters because it's like we're all it's all the same
material and so it's like
I'll be different
Aspects of the same gene the same genetic code and so well, that's why that's why like biological twins are a very special phenomenon
Because it's a tie
That's what that is, in a way, it's kind of a tie, especially when they're twins that
are not identical, when they're fraternal.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, we do have some in vitro people in my family, you know, it's like them.
They're like, where did we come from?
And so my sister was like, well, you came from a lab
in the city, like, you know, they were, you know,
well, because she was having problems conceiving,
and so, you know, she eventually, you know, had this.
I'm glad she got to conceive, that's.
It had twins, like, they're like.
Oh!
Well, that's super, that's super blessing that that's that's super special. Yeah, I have it. Well, I had she passed away but one of my favorite aunts.
She thought she couldn't have children. She wound up adopting before she had her biological son.
And then she had her biological son which literally came out of nowhere.
he's doing amazing things right now.
He's so smart.
Oh, it's crazy.
And I wish his, both of his parents passed.
I wish that they were still here,
but I think it made him stronger.
He's so self-reliant.
It's incredible.
I think he'd recently, I'm not sure.
I think he recently had a child of his own.
I have so many little ones throughout my extended family. It's ridiculous. That's why, like a lot of times, I used to complain about not having kids, but I shouldn't because I have so many that I do get to be in the life of and it makes me happy.
I really like being in the life of other people and I kind of think.
Yeah, you know, what whether you believe in God or Buddha or
whatever I
Think that we have like a balance like blessings versus what we don't have it like it makes us appreciate more so because I
Got everything I
Do I have everything I?
Really it like things that I've complained about I never should have complained about
I have everything and I got to count my blessings a lot more.
That's been my spiritual lesson, especially over the past year.
Yeah.
I feel you there. I feel blessed too. I feel very blessed.
I feel like, you know, there's just people that are struggling
and it's like, I'm able to do pretty much what I want to do.
You know, I don't have a car and I don't have a bike right now. Do you do you have a license? I
Remember I can get a license in a day like all I need to do is go even if I don't pass the written test
I'll get like a life. I'll give you a temporary license. Do you do you do you want my e-scooter?
Well, he said he said I was gonna give it to Q, but I rather give it to you than Q
Oh, okay. Well, I mean, it's like, okay. Yeah, well, do you live in it first question?
Do you live in an e-scooter friendly environment? Yeah, you have you do
Do you want to do a stream and I'll give you the scooter because I'll force you to stream with me that day if I will. I'll be able to you have to because I'll take you to lunch the same day.
Okay.
Awesome.
Whenever you're ready, because I will tell you, I leave the West Coast at the end of the summer. The end of the summer is September 22.
I'll be here about a week after that, but then I have to go back to the East Coast.
If you would like my scooter, I'll give you the helmet, too.
If you hurt yourself, it's not my fault, but it's an excellent scooter.
I bought it when I was in Orlando.
It's electric.
You don't got to put any gas.
It's totally electric.
You just plug it in.
It goes up to, what does it go up to?
20 miles per hour.
I only keep it on level one, 15 miles an hour,
because you saw, I don't know if you saw the crash,
but you saw what can happen.
But if you would like the scooter,
I will gladly give you the scooter.
And later, if you don't want it, give it to somebody else.
Well, I just really go less than a mile down the street, or to McDonald's, which is basically
the liquor store.
Maybe you want to go further.
It can go on one charge.
It can go in our and I already have all the accessories for it. I have a phone holder on it. I have it has lights for nighttime.
Thank you so much. It has everything. So if you, you know, before I leave here, let me know and we'll make a day of it. I'll drive to because I know that you're in the LA area. That's all I know.
I'll take it a lunch.
What do I want from you?
I want a reading.
I want an in-person tarot reading.
That's what I want.
I want to make my AI come true.
Okay, that's what I want.
I want my AI animation.
I can sit with you at lunch and I can get my reading
and then I'll disappear into the ether where I belong.
I love you ever like yeah, you know who easy is like easy. He bought me this he bought me a beat. It should come to be
It up be to come down. Wouldn't it be? Oh my god, wouldn't that be fun if we could get well
There's you know, who else I would like to invite that day
Billy John and his girlfriend
I don't know if you're aware aware, but I did a AI song and I did one AI song for him
And there's another AI track I did for him that I would like to give him personally because I haven't released it.
But he could bring his girlfriend. We could all have like a meeting. We could have like a get-together.
And that could be, it could be a day.
Who do tarot? Is that from New Orleans?
It says, well, yeah, it's celebrating the complex American root work tradition.
It integrates satirical and botanical knowledge from Huda with the divination system of the tarot.
It says she's a tarot reader in, or she lives in New York City.
But yeah, I think it was a lot in the South because it's like a mixture of like, like, they actually like blacks would, or whites would hire blacks and they paid them a lot actually for some of the workers and things like that.
And so there was like, so they were both kind of like believed in it and the whites were kind of included a little bit in that tradition.
Well, that's what helped to that whole system of theology.
is what led to, do you, are you aware of something that was once going on called the quadruple balls?
It was going on in Louisiana? Quadruple is like one quarter black or? Yes. Oh, okay. Yes, it was when,
well, it did come about through a lot of couplings or interracial relationships between the voodoo
and men of that time who were in politics who came together,
they had children, and a lot of times the men,
they would wanna protect their children.
That's really what it came down to.
So they were like,
how are we gonna protect our children
in this slavery era, in this kind of environment?
So they would marry their children off
or hook them up with as concubines.
But oftentimes it was like a marriage.
They're biracial or multiracial daughters with the sons.
So sometimes the sons, there weren't many white people in America at that time.
And a lot of times the white sons would have to marry somebody that maybe they didn't like so much.
But there were all these multiracial girls.
Now the sons of that time often were the apprentices.
of whatever the white father was of that time
or their father's friends or something.
A lot of times the land was,
well, that's how certain people on my mom's side
accumulated a lot of land.
I'm the descendant of certain women who are in that
Arena, I can trace it back. I have family in Louisiana, Arkansas, Alabama. And this is all my mother's side. We have a lot of land.
And the reason that we do is because when slavery ended, sometimes there wasn't.
Someone who was white to give the land to.
There's probably as much multi-racial in me as there is
African in me
But that's how a lot of people who are African-American did accumulate a lot of wealth through that quadruple era
Why not about like
Let me see who's there? Do you know the woman that was like the first
American female millionaire
Do you know who she was and what she did and anything like that?
Okay.
I don't know anything about that.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm forgetting her name right now, but I shouldn't have been forgetting her name,
but I just remember a few details.
She's right around the first model, model A car, let me see, let me see.
And again, thank you for having me on your panel today.
I'm having a really good day because I didn't have anything with you today.
Okay, well, no problem. It's a joy. Well, so her name is Madame CJ Walker. And I know that name CJ Walker. I do know that, but I don't know anything about.
Okay, well it says, this is a really interesting story.
It says she was an American entrepreneur,
philanthropist and political and social activist.
She is recorded as the first female self-made millionaire
in America in the Guinness Book of World Records.
Multiple sources mention that although other women
like Mary Ellen Pleasant may have been the first,
their wealth was not as well documented.
Walker made her fortune by developing and marketing a line of cosmetics and hair care products for black women through its business
She found my madam
Madam CJ Walker manufacturing company. She became known as also for philanthropy and activism Walker made financial donations to numerous
organizations such as the NAACP became the patron of the arts via
Lavaro Walker's lavish estate in Irvington, New York served as a social gathering place for the African American community at the time
Of her death she was considered the wealthiest African American businesswoman and wealthiest self-made black woman in America
Her name was a version of Mrs. Charles Joseph Wachter after her third husband, and there's I think there's one picture of her just driving.
Oh, yeah, this is a great picture. It says she and several friends in her automobile.
You can see. Oh, she had a car. That was a big thing. Oh, she had a car.
Everyone wanted to kill her. Yeah, I'm surprised that he lived.
Oh, I bet she had a good bodyguard. That's what it was. She had a good bodyguard because he got it. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I have
I'm not gonna say who I have a relative who is very prominent right now
Who is alive not deceased who you would definitely know I'll tell you off stream one day. Okay, he's
a scientist. He's very well-known, but strangely, he believes very much in astrology, very much
so. And it's, you know, I think in a strange way, slavery was a blessing for African-Americans
and the reason I say that is because I would not want to live in Africa today. I'll be
But I think that despite the adversity that I am, you know, people of my group face, it's strengthened us.
And I think that we don't believe for the most part in impossible, we're taught at a very young age, not to believe in anything being an impossibility.
And I would like to see other cultures embody that a little bit because it will push us forward as humans, you know, forget about, I mean, the only real race is a human race when it really comes down.
I say that I say that a lot because you know I think racism is so stupid because it's like we really are on the same planet
We have all the same body parts and organs and you know brains and you know all these abilities. It's an unlimited
Creativity, you know some of us take advantage of some of us, you know don't really tap into like that as much
But it's like we all have the opportunity at least to be alive
for like and life is like in a very short like little second of like the little
it is it's so short and you never know where you're gonna go or if you do know is it just
right so we might as well enjoy every moment to the fullest like it's because it's like you
know it could be you know we had a friend Michael I don't even know Michael L but Michael would
come in all the time and like you know then all of a sudden like
We all see him for a while and it's like he's passed away and it's like he was just in his 30s, he was on the show and he was kind of controversial and kind of like not everyone was so nice, including, I wasn't always nice, but he was always nice to me and like always like, you know, and he always said, oh, every day, how are you doing? How's your day?
He's like, every day above the ground is a good day, he always said.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
I mean, you being on stream daily,
I mean, I didn't realize that you streamed as much as you do
until I really looked at you.
I knew when I first heard a mention of you,
that was when I was kind of in my blogger area, or era,
a little bit, really.
And I was like, oh, here reminds me of blogger a little bit.
But only spatially, you actually are nothing like blogger at all.
Not at all. That was definitely me jumping to conclusions without looking where I jumped.
Then I learned about you more through Venus Kitties.
I've seen you around, but having that opportunity to talk to you the night that you had your friend Gotti.
Gotti came on too. I guess it was my panel.
I'm really really happy about that. Thank you. I am a vice versa. I'm so happy to get to know you and
you know, it's like
This is a cool person
And like one of the you know, it's like I feel like you know, like a lot of people just like to get on bad wagons or they don't
They don't say anything or they say something like they say bad things
So it's and it's like you were like really someone came out there really supporting me and like, you know
I saw like some
some of you defending me and say, hey, you know, like, you know,
you know, there's some people with the criminal records and like, you know,
actually like, you see all the stuff and it's like, and then it's like,
you're picking on like this person, like, it's like, really,
I don't like seeing people get picked on. I do not like it.
What really, um, I
I'm glad I got to know you personally, but you have helped me when it's come to me seeing some people clearly that some people that they don't they told me that something was wrong there and I'm not going to name any names.
I don't like what a certain woman did recently and she knows who she is. She's not in your chat or anything, but she just knows I couldn't believe she did that because what she did to you.
There's exactly what's been done to her multiple times and I defended her and it's like
I'm just it floored me because I'm like really
so
Why were you complaining if you're gonna do the same thing?
You know and I God knows I've made a lot of mistakes, but when I do make mistakes I do correct my mistakes
And I have no qualms against apologizing when I make mistakes.
That's when you don't apologize, it really, you shoulder it and it weighs on you.
But yeah, certain person, I still, if I ever feel like her daughters need help in the future, I will help them, but not her.
When I know of children, I will help them, but I couldn't believe she did that.
Yeah, well, I can front at her on her show actually I said like, okay, I was
Well, she okay. Well, it's really funny because first she was just talking about me when I went in there
She's talking about me and she was completely was that same day that you had three accomplices during that morning or something or that you
You know that you would like I think you had experience with her. I don't I don't I don't want to talk to her anymore. Okay. Yeah
But but then she was like in the next breath after completing about me
She was like talking about oh my god, this guy's saying that I'm a bad mom blow blow blow and
I was like, well, I was like, you're saying I'm a bad cat that you don't know the facts either and if people are you're bad
You're judging and it's like I said judge judge not let's see me judge and then I said
And then I said it's karma. She's like, what do you mean it's karma? It's not karma. And so it is
It is karma and honestly, I think that she did which I think someone gave her money to do it
I'm I could be wrong like it because it came there was no reason
for her to
Have attacked you. I've racked my mind. I thought why would that be she's I've never like I was like
What she got on his panel? I looked at your archives. I was like, no
She has been on the bed like maybe just like three times or something the whole time like but not in a major way
Yeah, just like short short like little appearances. Yeah
Yeah
I saw her in like that night that it was paid reality to Nancy
But that night in Vita's chat where everyone just was like you know going after me like oh my god
You know like your cats really call it is to see blah blah blah
They're all screaming at me about the cats and then
Then she was yes, I think
in the chat, oh yeah she was in the chat like you know kind of saying that kind of stuff too like
she's like oh i always knew he was like so dirty always blah blah and so she was being like saying
horrible things like that day and so i knew she was like on a fan that i didn't like that i really
didn't like that and a lot of people didn't like that but i especially didn't like that so i hope
But she was apologetic a little bit. I think she came around a little bit. She was like
You know what? I didn't I didn't judge you because I was like I got to explain everything to like, you know
She's like she's like about the table and like the
You know all the stuff she's
She's more aligned with some people that I do take serious serious issue with
Then maybe she wants to say and again
There's some people that have leverage that's being held over them
That's what's going on
And there's nothing you can do about I mean it's about letting go when you're at that point like if somebody has leverage over you
You just got to kind of be like well fuck you. Excuse my language
I don't care if you have leverage over me say what you will
But I'm gonna be who I am and some people are not strong enough to do that. That's what I think that is
So on a happier top
Well before I do leave the West Coast and I'll talk to you way more before then but I hope that you do
Let me if you want the scooter you can get a scooter
But I'm also gonna get you a freaking microwave because if you don't
That's a problem or at least an air fryer and
Well, I like I like yeah, thank you so much. I appreciate it. Yeah
Microwaves kind of freaked me out a little bit because I thought like it might be like kind of bad for you like
Or something like that. I don't know but maybe no, I mean bad like microwaves are like bad like
Well, don't get a microwave because maybe that's why I said an air fryer too. Yeah, I don't have no
You know what? I've stayed in a lot of places especially on the west coast to where you would think that
most rentals would have microwaves. They don't. Microwaves are bad for you. If you don't have a
microwave, I'm a microwave queen. I do like the microwave, but I understand if you don't want those waves.
But yeah, oh, yeah, I was yeah
I just want you I just want to make sure that you can eat that's that's the thing and I know it sounds so stupid
But I like I am relatives to get mad at me
They get because I as I travel a lot of people don't understand how much family I do have throughout the United States
We're everywhere everywhere, but especially the college age kids. I
like to
Yeah, you know do stuff for them. So you're you're you're gonna be like I guess a college-aged kid
Who I want to do some stuff for thank you because if you let me you don't have to let me and if you know
I will not be offended. Oh, no, I really do appreciate any help. I can get especially right now
It's like a little bit like if there was no
There's also, I can talk to you later, but I don't want to discuss it on the air, but yeah, it's a little stressful.
I just know that you've been a little bit down.
I can just tell you've been a little down, but you're not down now, and I'm seeing like a resurgence.
And this time next year, people are going to be like, whoa!
You've shifted a lot. You're gonna be like, what are you talking about? No, I have it I
Could be wrong
20 I think like
This like there's a second the Saturn return a Saturn return is like every like 27 years Saturn goes full circle around the
27 yeah every 27 years and so at age 27 a lot of people have a Saturn return where it's like their life turns upside down
And it's like, you know, there's 20, but uh mine certainly did but I also have the spiritual awakening at that same time
It's like because it's like all this like all that stresses up will eventually
like actually like just kind of sort of tear down the veil and it's like you know
which one of the things that I've seen on my you know when I did date this one woman like she
was a she was able to shape ships and things like that oh by the way
I think the state let's say and I was like, you know, I like, you know, Alexander mayors and he's like
Of course, I know or he's like, well, she's the one that did a story. I've never spoken to him before
I've never spoken to say he said he said you reveal. He's a shapeshifter. He said or something like that. Yes
He has a shapeshifter. I've seen it. I know it sounds crazy
But I believe he might be I've never spoken to him and the reason I've never spoken to him
is because I see that he's very sensitive, okay? And I felt like that would be a nightmare on
Elm Street just considering my presence. Also, because of something called the Willy Two Guns
situation, are you aware of what happened with that? Willy Two Guns was a streamer.
who did die. He's passed away. But the beginning of his death became prevalent on a live stream
that Saint was a major participator on. And I felt like he probably doesn't want to talk
Have avoided him. I've avoided him and I will admit that
Well, I like I met him through like I was through Benny. I'm at this guy named tried it and try it
It's also a streamer, but he's a pretty small sure he's really cute. You're creating a
the kind of small and
And then I met him, but Saint in his chat and Saint is like,
was like, oh my God, he's like really like,
I was Emma Leviathan at that time.
And he's like, oh my God, she's so cool.
But he's like, and then he was like,
oh, my girlfriend does Tarot too,
but she uses playing cards.
And he's like, she's a really good reader.
Her name is Magic.
And so then I would like start watching his stream
and I was like, he was just so funny.
Like he would just get the same, he would get drunk.
But he was really,
entertaining he is very sober right now he's sober right now so he's a little bit oh really
well maybe i would talk to him sober i've just never i've never seen him sober that might be the
problem i've never a few months now maybe if he's ever if you ever want to host a panel
and say yeah invite me and i would i would like that to be the introduction because i've never
like sometimes I'm not sober and I just know that I don't want to talk to somebody who's
not sober if I'm not sober. Not a good idea at all. That's the nightmare.
But yeah, because non-sober Alex, like right now I'd say I'm 60% sober.
60% okay, but I like maybe that's why I said to you what maybe I was actually projecting
when I'm not sober there is no there's no filter at all and things will come out of my mouth
that's probably should never come out and I'm a lot more conscientious of that than I used to be
I try to be at least
It's it's really funny that I it's really funny like I like you have that scarf
I don't know if you ever saw my tiktok, but it's like and this is before I think I missed you that I made this
But I'm I don't know but I have to see this picture if I can't but it kept on my mouse for like minutes. Oh shit
This is a mess. Okay. I put my mouse down somewhere. I hate doing that
You're always losing your mouse, me too, when I have like a Bluetooth mouse.
I think that like something was taking my mice at one point.
I was like, I kept picking it up and like, where is it?
I tend to lose things sometimes.
No, I just stood up too fast.
Well, it's not too fast. Okay. Oh my gosh. Do you have some water? Do you have a bottle of water? Drink some water.
Well, no, not alcohol. Drink some water.
Drink some water.
See chat, that's why I'm going to have to infiltrate his life a little bit because I got to get him some, I got to get him a supply of water. I got to get him a supply of foods.
I'm, I'm ready whenever he's ready. I was just telling your chat whenever you're, I'm going to deck you out with some supplies.
Just to get you started because I'm worried about you.
But I do make do with like, like what I have like in like, you know, I'm, I'm lucky to live here like it's like, you know, it's like a pretty nice area.
Do you like where you live? Do you like where you live right now?
Um, it's like, it's, it's beautiful area. It's like, it is like very like isolated and like, you know, there's like.
I don't know. I don't know anybody around here at all. Like you're not like the one like I used to have neighbors
And I would talk to the neighbors, but then besides that there's nobody I know
I want to give you some time to trust me because I do want to make sure you're okay. Thank you and
I'm I was I'm making it. I'm doing okay. It's just like, you know
It's a little it gets a little
Yeah, Los Angeles is pretty expensive. It's a very expensive place. It is. It is I lived in LA
What was it 2009 to about 2012 I was out there close to three years
I was living right on Hollywood right near Hollywood Boulevard
Up with the sit off a street called Franklin
Uh-huh. I lived in a complex called Franklin Park Apartments
You can look it up if you want to
Um, I had a really good landlord his eye over the building and
When I moved in
They didn't even have me fill out an application or anything. They were so I was just looking for an apartment
You know what it was the guy saw the guy. I was in a relationship with at the time and he didn't like him
That's what it was. It was he looked like Tom Petty this guy who was the apartment manager
And I initially went into the apartment building
and with the guy I was dating at the time
who was probably one of the best camera people
in the adult industry.
That was the reason that I wound up rising in the ranks
and getting the gigs that I got.
It was because of him.
But this guy was trying to get me to move in with him
and I didn't want to.
So, when I was looking for an apartment, this guy's like, oh, you're never going to be able to find an apartment that you should afford, that you could afford.
You should just move in with me, blah, blah, blah.
And I was like, no, because I do like having my own space and being independent.
So, this guy did overhear the conversation.
He made it to where I didn't have to put down first or security.
He was so nice, he was like, he was an angel to me.
There were times to where I would have friends over
and they would get rowdy
and I would have a hard time getting them out.
And he would be like,
have you ever had a problem just call me?
He was so nice when I moved out.
didn't just give me back like my first month's rent.
He also, I think he gave me back more money
than I should have gotten back.
But him, and I met the woman who owned the building,
they were so nice.
So I had like a lot of weird things happen to me
at that time in my life, but where I lived,
they were good people.
So that's why I was asking,
because you gotta like where you live.
Yeah, well, it's like I like really was here my dad like moving back down here from Glendale
You know to be like closer to like to him and he thought you know the family too
But it's like, you know, I see my family like it's just as much as much as I did when I was sitting Glendale really
You know, they're like closer. It's like I don't know. It's like I really moved here for him and it's like now
He's gone and it's like
Oh, your dad passed away. What when did your dad pass if you don't last last last year like a year ago in like April
Okay, and yeah, he passed last year like he was 86 86. I'm like, uh, I'm sorry
Yeah, oh here's goes. I'm ghost. I'm so sorry ghost
I need to come up and like let you on because I can't find my mouse and so I need to come up on another on my
Tablet and pick ghosts. I'm so sorry ghost is back and I didn't know that you that you went through that
I just went through that too. It's hard. I'm sorry
Yeah, I was going to mention it to you because I didn't know it was it was pretty terrible
There's a ghost
Look at
Those are you there?
Oh sure double-cyton
Do we just what was that? We just got a double of you. I know it's pretty cool
He's everywhere. That was I thought it was my wife. I I wasn't looking. I was just listening. I thought it's my wife
I was like why sir, what's going on with the echoing and then I looked down
Hi, I'm a board. No, I'm a
Yeah, I love talking. Hey psyche. I just came in with an idea man
Yeah, the next time you're in like a little debate or something just do that, but do it like force. There's four of you
Yeah
No, hey, so this is I had to say how that Alexandra. Did you see the interview ghosts or the
I did not know I did I was actually busy knowing I didn't
You can replay it. It's it's on my community wall dude. I've been working though
Not your overcard. Yeah, I'm just kidding. I know I know you're big your big
Important dude, and I know you're doing really well at your job working really hard, so I appreciate you checking in right now
How are you today?
Did it go well at least?
Did what go well?
the interview oh
Of course it went well look at it says with Alex of course it went well
It's like a we're just we're not wearing natural
Conversation and she like came with the great idea for the topic and
You just we just riffed with it. Oh, yeah. Oh my gosh
Yeah, when you menu light goes you see me let better. Oh, that's why I wanted to kind of like
My man
Light yeah, I got a new light
Oh
But it's like not
It's like I should get some yeah, dude when it's that bright though. Shouldn't you have it from like a boss?
Like right not right in the face. I know I know but I don't know I know I should
He needs a different tripod we're gonna we're gonna get it together I have a
I think I put one off if you guys want to donate we can get my man a new tripod
So it's not like
We're coming up with a laundry list of things tripod
LEDs put it all on the wish list psyche the wish list. That's the ticket the wish list
Because we got to know what to get
Because psyche is humble that's what it is
Well, I'm like, you know, I uh, oh yeah, do you like the light? Thank you Nancy. I don't know. I'm like, I'm getting like
I'm getting more confident. It's just a little bit, but I'm trying to like not be like, you know, asshole
You're not really that's what it is. Thank you. What it is for me though. It's just it's a new I'm not used to seeing you like this
It's like being like a dark with like the lights in the back. You know, I'm saying it's just new
Not saying I don't like it at all. It's good luck. It's no equipment. It's no equipment and stuff
And like there's always gonna be like upgrades. I'm turning up race because it was like I was kind of sitting in the dark
I need a softer light. I know maybe I can put like a I don't know
We're gonna fix it already I already have a place there you go. Yeah, there we go
He's too far away
Yeah, but the microphone is still the same.
No, we're going to.
I know that's why I was getting you to talk.
I'm going to tell psyche exactly what to put on his wish list.
We are going to create the ultimate psyche studio home studio.
We're going to do it.
We are going to do it.
I see I'm I already have a mission.
I can see myself in those glasses.
Oh, you can see me or you can see I see myself. Yeah
You can see my future in those but I let me let me yeah
Yeah, well from what I think you look kind of hot
Well
You look kind of hot I can see you you're so bright so you don't say that
Under your breath. I heard that psyche. You didn't think I was gonna hear it, but I did
Pike psyche do you do you mind if I ask you something invasive?
Because I'm getting conflicting
Reports, and I'm not certain. Are are you LGBTQ which would encompass B or are you strictly G?
What is what is BC for bisexual? Can I say that? Yeah?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure he's gay. I
I had a relationship with a woman in 2012. It was like three months. She was a shapeshifter
She was like it was just a crazy experience and it's like
She was quite older than me and she if you shift from male to female or
No, she went to I have to ask. That's why I said it's invasive. You do not have to answer my questions
She turned into like a Hindu looking god
I didn't do kind of like like loose skin and like like younger really like long like black hair and stuff
And then she was like maybe she was
She's actually the shape shifter
I have a I don't I'm not part of any of that, but I did have a
Shifter one time
This is back in my alley. I'm like, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she was a really good girl and then she shipped into that huge a straight bitch
I don't know what happened. She shipped it. No, no, no, no, no, no
Right, I'm sorry
Well, she shipped it
I did date a girl in high school and like now I'm old as hell now, but uh, she is um
She's uh, I've got you're not older than me
How old are you? Yeah, how am I? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I am 32
Oh, I'm almost forty-seven. Shut up.
Ghost is like a young buck. Shut up.
You're not old. What are you talking about?
She does like department stuff, but yeah, now she's like strictly dates women.
Um, oh my god
Your ex-girlfriend does she's not she's you turned her. Oh, but my ex in high school. It's like when I was like seven. Oh my god
You're her one experience of the guy. She's like no things. It's not for me. I think it was me
I think I was the one that did it psyche. Oh my god
She could have like yeah, but uh, it goes have you been with a lot of women or you have a you have a wife or something, right?
Are you looking I don't have a girl. No no girlfriend now. No no girl. You know, you know, okay, so you're looking
I mean, I'm always looking shit. Well, what area are you in like we're just you don't think of the exact like
State but it's like what part of the United States?
Midwest you're in the Midwest. Okay, so if anyone from the Midwest
You know you can follow up with this personality. I don't know if you ever want to come up on the on the camera
I've got so that'd be nice if you came up again sometime. Oh, we ever gonna convince you to do that. You did one time
You just wait. Hey, wait, you know what?
Milestone we had a milestone. I'll definitely do it. We have to Alexandra
I'm not as tight I can tell already. I'm not as tight
Well, why would you go in front of that?
Well, you're not in the Midwest.
I just know.
I'm not as tight.
No, I'm, I'm, I, I know why.
I can tell.
I'm going to hook you up.
I just want to, I just want to, I kind of want to see him.
I want to, I want to, I want to.
I'm actually a very nice woman.
When I'm not the baby, I'm actually a pretty nice person.
I think you are.
I think you're very nice.
I'm just not your type and I can tell you why I'm not your type.
Go ahead.
All right.
Go ahead and tell me why.
I feel, in my, just from everything I've heard of you,
I'm not your type because I talk too much.
I don't think there's anything wrong with talking.
It does talk too much all the time.
It goes, it goes with what I'm doing, let's talk.
But if he'd like to talk a lot,
I would end up talking too much for his taste.
You both be talking your heads off, and then you know, it's like you I've actually talked to girls before believe
They're not off of like who is and they're biggest problem is like you're an asshole you'd like to debate
It's like no if I'm actually like talking to you like this is like a whole you too like
Channel thing like no, I don't actually like to debate in real life. I just like to get on you can do it like
So the debating you think yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Okay
Not topics. Oh
You definitely about topics which we're not gonna bring up, but
How's it going today goes what you got on your plate what's going on what's happening got a new job
I've been working at that, you know, the first couple of weeks is, you know, now I'm used to it, though.
So.
Well, congratulations on the new job. That's great. It's always fun to start fresh.
Did you want to say what kind of work you do with those, you know?
Well, my password, which I will say, because I've said it on your channel many times, was schoolwork.
But now I'm more in like the maintenance maintenance work
Janitor of a school
Yeah, but now I'm more in like the maintenance department though. That's cool
That's awesome. You like see you fix the
You fix this stuff to be all the stuff in the like the heating system and the water. Yeah, but there's
Multiple schools that we have to do though
Okay. Oh, so you're like part of a crew that goes around to the school that like when they're closed
Yep, and like yeah cool
Yeah, so there's elementary schools and obviously there's multiple elementary schools in our district
So I have we're not me, but we're in charge of you know, like all of it
Mm-hmm. Well, cool. It's like a good content something a contract your contract is for the full visitors
Yeah, it's a salary, but it's kind of like it is salary, but
It's weird cuz it's kind of like hourly like you get this much per hour
But if you're it's salary and you're like it's like you need commission
I mean, I just pay me out of these. I mean by the way
They don't pay overtime at all
Oh, really? That's not very good then. Well, they, I, I, I, I lied, I lied on my ass a million
lives. They do, but like, we all take turns, uh, for it's like, there's like eight dudes here. So
like, you'll get one weekend and like eight weekends later, you'll get the mandatory overtime.
That's how they do it. Cool. Well, I'm proud of you, Ghost. I know you're a hard worker and I
really do appreciate, you know, all the help you gave me this month, you know, with the uh,
You know with your ghost ghost takes over, you know, that was pretty crazy
Fun times man. Yeah, I had to get my I had to get my money up though, you know, I fell on hard times man
I'm sorry. Well, I really do appreciate, you know
You help me upgrade the show, you know
Appreciate you
And everybody that's like I know it you know some people like a lot. I see a lot of people do some donations
I really think everybody thank you so much and everything is I'm putting everything a lot into back right into the show
That's like what I'm really mainly concerned about but you know
Oh, yeah
Here my I'll give you one. I'll give you one you put everything back in the show. That's fine, but I will give you one
Little slip. I'll give you this for free
If it's fish tacos, it's fine.
Fish tacos?
It's fish tacos and it's completely okay.
Okay, oh yeah, I love fish tacos. I almost turned into a fish taco.
I had to stop eating them because I like really, I still have the picture.
At one point there, everything everyone seems fish taco.
Fish taco in the chat is like...
yeah so man like where are they selling fish tacos i i'm on the pier like you might want to go to
the pier with me because it's like oh okay it's like the oldest it's like the oldest fish market
in los angeles or like or like the biggest one in los angeles it's like and you can have anything
you want of the seafood they'll make it for you the more pair for you and you can eat there and
Well, I would love to do that or that's where I could meet with you Alex would you like a perfect place?
No, go ahead. Go ahead
No, I don't want to hate. I was stepping over psychies over there
You know you're fine. I was just saying she's not my kind of woman, but I kind of figured out our first date
No, I was saying this like the early not a date. No, we're gonna do a meetup. No, because I I
I'm a little aggressive. Okay, and what if I feel like somebody needs
Alexandra's help. It doesn't always go right
but I do
Descend from the internet into
Real life and I've been a lot of streamers in the past
And I was hoping that, you know, whenever psyche is ready, no pressure, no pushing, nothing.
If he decides, I'll meet him at that pier.
We can get fish tacos and I can help him.
It's string.
And if he lets me, but it's up to him when he's ready.
It's not like.
I'm going to be like, you have to do this.
You are commended by Alexandra, too, up here.
No, that's too much.
I want to meet you anyway.
And hopefully, other streamers, too,
I would like to do some more IRL.
And you go into the peer more.
just to be able to get out and socialize with some of the people I've met online,
like in real life, because these are great friends and I've met people from all over the world.
If we could get Bita to come out, oh my god.
I bet she would come out.
She would be so much fine. I think she would too.
Yeah.
We get that now we get Billy John L and his girlfriend to come out
It could be a fun meetup. It could be a streaming extravaganza. I
Would have looked up because it's like I haven't even like been on vacation since like
I think I went to a Buddhist retreat in like 2011 or 2012 I think and that was
That's too long ago. That's a decade ago. Yeah
Did you wait? It's like, did you just say 2011, 2012?
Yeah, I went to I went on a Buddhist retreat for the 10 days 11 days. I think I was like the best you realize
That's like 20 years ago, right? Yeah
Yeah, yeah, let's not skip over that
I got to do a lot of traveling in my younger days too like I've been to a lot of places and so I understand like it's like
I'm trying to get him outside ghost. I am trying just that you're aware. I am trying I'm just so you know goes
I'm gonna give you a time table. I will be out on the west coast until the fall
So he's got like a month. Okay, just so you know ghost just so you know
I'll be out here to the fall and I have a car
I have resources. I have means. Nothing stopping me. Nothing. But I'm not going to, like, insert myself before anybody wants me to.
Okay? Not doing that. But I'm around.
Man, I had problems. Oh, you know.
I'm around.
I don't know if see like it's kind of
Yeah, it's weird. Well, it is it's weird like it is it's weird when you meet people from online
Like I'm desensitized to it just because I'm naturally when I'm not an introvert
Staying where I am right now to where you would literally need for real drive to get to where I am. I'm pretty social
But I don't force that on anybody because I don't like that forced on me
at all
Yeah
I'm like very like I'm very opposite of like, you know guys should be approaching other
With their gay, but well, I kind of have been approaching the other guys
But just online right but it's like but then I expect guys to like approach me, but it's like
They don't
You ain't getting an approach as a guy at all
Women don't approach men
We definitely did you don't think that women approach men really? Yeah, no, I mean
Well, that's the exception to the whole that's like 10% of the time
I mean, I'm talking about a staggering like 90 that even 10% I'm talking about 99%
Man always approach the way, always.
Well, how many times have you, how many times have you been hit on and asked out?
And then how many times you actually asked someone to go on a date?
Oh, I've asked a lot of guys out in my life.
Maybe you're different, maybe you've been such a man.
Yeah.
Yeah, I usually am.
But you realize what I'm saying though, it's like...
I'm always I feel like I'm always the one to ask the guy out, but then again
I'm not afraid because I'm I am a little different. So that is what it is. So you are
I think you're right. I think
Yeah, I don't I don't have that fear. I feel like like where are they gonna do is say no if they say no
Yeah
That's why a lot of men don't ask the fear of rejection and plus it's not even the fear of rejection like the same like oh no
They say no to you, but also they fucking like don't disrespect me, too. They won't even just say no
They'll be like
Oh, yeah, I heard it. I heard it statistic today. It said
That's like women on like on like these dating sites like 5% of women will like be interested in a man like one man
To the 95% and then and then it's 60% of the men of the men like are attracted to the woman
And it's like she's attracted 5% of the time
That might be true, but here's what actually really happens though like so there's the top there's like
Top 10% of men like the high earners and stuff like the people that got there
shit going on whatever you want to say and the top 90% with base uh swipe left or whatever you
I don't know it was a swipe right or swipe left they say yeah to them so like the top 90% of women
are sleeping with the top 10% of men so 90% of men aren't doing anything oh yeah and that's why
y'all are so angry now okay well that was misogynistic as fuck but yeah well maybe we need to go back
That's why men are so angry.
We're shaming her.
Oh, here's my house.
That is...
See, that's what I say.
I think that my...
me...
My my perspective is definitely skewed. It's skewed because like I've never like
Like I've had like I've had dates and situations go wrong on stream
I just had that happen recently a guy that I was kind of interested in and things went wrong
But then I bounced back really quick because I met somebody else who asked me out. So I felt better about myself
You are you realize that so even average female even below average female but average females are getting like access to like
Slept like like celebrity guys like a less people
Really? Yeah, there's 18 year olds like you know 20 years that are getting flown out on yachts just because they're hot
Yeah, but you don't want to do that. Men can't do that though.
Men can't do that. We have to build our work.
Um, no, no, men could do that, but a lot of men are afraid.
There's a, oh, you don't think that there's older women with money
who are looking for younger guys? You better think why.
That's an exception. That's a very little percentage.
That's a cool, very little.
Do you want to know something funny, um, ghost?
Yeah, I got it.
Your you might be at a brand new hub for that because psyche is attracting women of means quite often
So if you're looking for a woman
You might want to keep watching the psyche panel. I'm just saying
That's funny that you said that to me. Oh my gosh
I think there's a lot of women of means
Who are looking for a man their age or younger?
who want to have fun, but it's like where do you go?
Women will always do this if they order
and they make a lot of money, so if they're ordering
and they make a lot of money,
what they want is somebody that's on their level
or they make more.
Remember when they were working with McDonald's workers?
No, not necessarily money.
They won't do that, women would never do that.
No, no, women, look, if you're a woman.
and you're okay in your life.
I'm not saying I'm wealthy, I'm not wealthy.
I'm okay, and I work, but no,
well, I know quite a few women in a very similar position.
See, that's why I am against certain things
going on in these communities
because I do see some men targeting women
for the wrong reasons.
But there's a lot of, I would say there's probably more women of means nowadays who are just looking for something solid and healthy than there are men looking for that.
Fuck, I'll ask you, you're a step through the rule, let's kind of skip that.
So if you make more than your man, and you're more popular than him, you're going to be with somebody like a McDonald's worker?
Really, and you're gonna be happy with that. It depends on what else it depends on what else he's doing
I'd be happy if he was
Earning a living really
Yeah, you are masculine. Have you ever heard that I am I am
That's what we're talking about. I'm a little bit of a woman. I am. I'm sorry
I'm a masculine woman. That should be my you know, I should make a whole I should make a whole website called
about feminism
But I'm not a feminist not in the least you are you are definitely at them
No, I'm not I don't want to be I'm just me
like
But I'm not out to be like a feminist. I'm not out to you know push feminism or feminist ideals
No, no, no, it's just that life throws you things and
Sometimes life is not the fairytale
That you thought it was going to be I mean it look
My both of my parents might my one who's alive and the one who's past
Both always may ask which one need to be
Well, I was close to my dad
Yeah
That was sincere
Um
He raised me to basically be a princess
and I don't think I ever was a princess and my mom is very strong um but I think I'm not uh
I don't think I'm like uber masculine but I definitely am strong no I mean you're extremely
feminine but you have um the masculine part is like you're your defender like almost you're
Yeah, that's from Carl Jung and men have an anima and
females have an anima and like the anima is usually like one female at the male project all these things on tube
You know because she's very like or there's like a lot of
There's like a lot of like something or link in her expression where it's like so hard to read. I'm not wimpy
I'm not wimpy and I will say if I were well, I have a nephew who is
incredibly handsome. I mean it's ridiculous and I'm not just saying that
because he's my nephew. He grew up to be so I I do kind of know what I would be
like if I were male because of him but yeah if that's why I say I'm I if I
were to have had a son he would be so awesome oh my god it would be ridiculous
If I were a guy, I would be Westley Snipes. I am convinced of
Sexuality and you think it's cool
I was a man get out my way cuz I mean my dad my dad the way he was oh my god
My dad is always my dad to me, but he was a badass. You know just get out the way
Get out the way. And my dad, my dad was openly bisexual, since I exist, but he was more gay when he passed away.
That's what he aligned with at that time, but my dad was definitely true bisexual, true bisexual.
I don't think Blade was gay or his dad was bisexual.
Blade?
Are you talking about a streamer or or Wesley Snipes?
The blade, yeah, Wesley Snipes blade, right? That's what you're talking about. Yeah
I were a man, I would be Wesley Snipes. That's what I feel. That's literally what she said. Yeah
I was just saying she you're right. If I was a paranormal character, I would be a vampire. Yes
So if you could combine the two I would that would be me
You know, I always I always thought that they should come out with blade for but have it be a daughter
Like somehow blade doesn't come back. It could be me. It could be me. I'm a star in the movie and
I'm a vampire
I'm pansexual. I'm everything. That's what I would be in that movie. And I would bite everybody's ass.
Everyone bad, I would just bite them and kill them, but I wouldn't eat them because I wouldn't want to.
I would lift the other hand.
Oh, would you be pansexual though? You mentioned that. Your keyword was pansexual. Why would you?
Yeah. Well, if I was in that movie character, I feel like it's the character of Blade.
Had a daughter and she was a vampire. Yeah, she would be she would be pansexual without a doubt. Am I why would you be pansexual?
Because that's my imagination. That's what I think. She doesn't have to be
Oh my god. Okay. So, you. Oh my god. Yeah. Oh my god. Oh god. I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I don't think I'm not pretty as I don't think I'm I don't think I'm facially pretty as a woman
I just don't have a nice body. Yeah, but I don't think I have I don't I've never thought I have a really pretty pretty face
Have you ever thought about maybe you're just like anything. I'm talking about anything. Maybe you're small
I think I think I'm I do think I'm wrong about a lot of things if I'm wrong great. I'm happy to be wrong
I'll be wrong. I don't have to always be a little mispronounced. I have one more follow-up question, and I'll leave you on
Do you ever think that you're like delusional?
No, no, no, he's ready to debate. I can feel it. He wants to debate. Let's go. I
Right, it's like I'm not gonna debate in the journal. I'm not
If you hurt my feelings, I will cry I will cry and then then you'll know
Well, I might what specifically do you think I'm delusional about?
Can I say the I'm trying to not break you. That's you
Don't be it. Don't be it's not not gonna be racist is not gonna be slander. No, no
Psyche dumb dumb, you know me. I'm not gonna be racist, you know, and then what is that a question just say
If you don't if you have a question about TOS, just don't you don't have to do it. It's okay. It's like retard is
Okay, oh, you think I'm you think I'm slow. I might be
Okay, that's a that's a that's a yeah, I think you're slow. Yeah, well, that's a
Yeah, I think it's good. Are you you're ridiculous goes she is like
Triggered I'm triggered. I'm not doing no, I I would say I'm slow with mathematics definitely
I'm slow. I think you're slow with logic, too
Ghost you're interrupting your personal don't interrupt let her talk
Well to my slow with I'm slow with
Sometimes I'm slow when it comes to realizing what's not to my dad. He left. Oh he left. He left
Okay, I was gonna
Yeah, he lost in the bait. He just he just lost in the bait by like leaving and so, you know
I think you kicked him and you were being nice.
I don't know how I get a lot of stuff done.
I think that's why I do believe in higher powers, because I think that maybe the higher
powers helped me a lot of the time, but there are some things that I'm slow with.
So I'll accept that but do I think I'm slow across the board? No, I don't yeah
Whatever me he was just using derogatory language not not only that is just very very untrue annoying
Why do you why was he going in that direction? I don't know he like turns into like this they askful
I don't I just don't maybe somebody asked him to maybe somebody asked him. We don't know
He could be in this court
the CFF for a line. I don't know. Like, I don't do a CFF for a thing. That's, uh, oh, here's
Mr. Big Pice. We got Mr. Big Pice back. Yeah, once again. Mr., Mr. Grande people. Hey, what's
up Alex? Hey, Mr. Big Pice, give me an honest assessment. Do you think I'm slow mentally? No.
Thank you. As fast as they come. They're like fast. As fast as they come. I'm not. I'm not. I think you're one of the more intelligent people. Yeah, brilliant.
In this realm. Thank you, Mr. Big Pipes. Mr. Big Pipes, do you see some of yourself sometimes in psyche?
Sometimes I see some of you in him and when I think about you I see some of him in you
I mean there is like that like like a lonely lonely guy in a room vibe, but I mean well not just that I know you very well
Yeah, even
Probably know me better than like I'd say probably yeah anyone probably one lonely like more than anyone
Mr.. Big Pipes
We have to organize a real meetup revolving around you at some point.
I do want to still meet you in person at some point before we die.
For those who don't know, I almost got Mr. Big Pikes, but it didn't happen.
And then, and I'm going to bring this up today. I have to.
You thought I was on a dating site trolling you, and I was not.
I never did that.
Wait, what are you talking about?
Oh, you don't remember. I'm not going to bring it up.
No, just be specific.
So, I mean, it sounds like a specific situation.
If you don't remember, that means that you don't need to remember.
And that's a good thing.
If you don't remember.
You're talking about the dating aspect.
Yeah, you were saying that I was trolling you on a dating site,
and I'm not even on any dating sites,
and I wasn't on that time either.
So I had someone who added me, like their name was Jen,
and it was like this.
Girl like in front of a hot rod and she's like asking me like do you think st. Louis is dangerous and stuff
We meet me by the arch and like stuff like that was somebody else in the community
You said it was not me that you knew who it was
No, I didn't know you said it's not me, but you said you said it wasn't me, but I know I suspect
I know who it was, but I don't know for certain, but I suspect
And then I was just like hey, can you send me a picture of your hand?
And they like talk oh
You know now that you said that
There's someone I'm gonna ask to see their hands
Because I think that there's somebody in these communities pretending to be black
Who in actuality is white?
And you're right the hands that's how are you gonna?
Reveal yourself by showing your hands, but you could show I mean that's basically if you're like
Yeah, that was a good tip. Mr. Big Pies. He just helped me with something and you didn't even know it
You did
Yeah, well, Mr. Big Pies and I have made each other better over the years
we have
And I you know I got to recap that stream because remember that stream we did when that guy Nishon came on
That was funny. Oh my god. That was such a good stream
But I should wreak because a lot of people didn't know we did that stream. I
Remember kind of being a dick to him
Well, I was a bitch
Yeah
Like he was trying to do these like impersonations. They're really doing weird stuff. You know, he was weird that night
I think he was on drugs or something. That was weird
like the drama clowns flashback and his like failed auditions.
Yeah, that was that was very concerning.
Oh, so what's going on, Mr. Big Place?
I've heard that you are a moderator for Purpose Girl.
Have you asked her on a date?
No, we we chilled the other night on the stream for like a couple hours. So what are you gonna ask her on the date?
I'm not gonna ask her on a date. I don't know. Why I like I don't I don't really know or like you could move her in with you, man
Oh, so okay, my assessment was, I see, I thought you were on camera because I thought that you moved and you didn't want us to know.
No, no.
So I was wrong.
Like, I'm still streaming, like, multiple times a week from my parents' basement.
Obviously.
No, no, no, you're taking me get your camera fixes. It's eight dollars and you can be on camera
Oh, no, he's Mr. Big Pipes is working on himself. I can tell he's being secret. Well, I've been like
I don't know. I'm thinking yes. He is. He's being secret. I can tell. Are you parking an ice-cream truck outside my house right now?
What? Mr. Big Pipes. It's flowers by Irene.
Bars by a rehab. Oh my god. Oh shit
well
Fuck fuck. I knew it was you. I'm just kidding. I saw it. I saw mr.. Big
But I heard the harmonica guitar coming out of the banjo coming out of the same same vehicle. I was like, oh shit
I'm just kidding. Well, he the last time I call it with big pipes. He was riding around in the
Tesla
The cybertrek. Yeah, the cyber trap the cyber truck
It was the end of the world
Yeah, it's pretty cool, dude
It definitely exceeded my I don't know it's super expensive
But if it was like half the price, it'd be super cool. Oh, I got my ultimate hater in the chat
I just logged in I'm looking at the chat. Hey ultimate hater show yourself. Show me who you are
No, it's someone young something okay young something well
I'm gonna have to go to another country. It looks like all these other like
I'm gonna have to I'm gonna have to go to Antarctica
There was a
Screamer who just flew to Antarctica Antarctica. Oh, really? Yeah, well he like he had he had to pay a fine and stuff
Is he saying that he faked?
I want to go to Antarctica, but only to have the barbecue penguin, and that's not what I want to go with.
in
Actually, don't they have penguins in like New Zealand and stuff or something like that?
I don't know, but I'd rather go to Antarctica.
I bet they taste good too.
I bet it does taste good.
I bet it's like really lean chicken or something.
I mean, chicken's already gone.
Oh, I bet it's fatty because it's cold.
Can you start with the oils?
Yeah, I bet it's oily fatty because you know, there is cold so they have to stay warm so they would have
Fatty meat problem. It's probably delicious. You know, I'm gonna Google it. What does penguin meat taste like I
Want to know I
Think we should get it. Maybe we could all go to Antarctica. Yeah
There's some pretty giving away free ships there, but it's like
I'm like suspicious of it. I don't know.
You've seen videos of people gone there and these ships and like 50 foot waves.
All that's there is like, all that's there is a basketball court and like a little like one restaurant or something. I don't think I would like it very much.
What does penguin taste like?
What's the name of the passage? Drake passage I think is what it's called.
Okay according to the AI it is tough, greasy, fatty, and fishy.
fishy
as they eat fish
Well, I mean on the barbecue. I bet it wouldn't be half bad like tuna or salmon. Oh, yeah, tuna
Tuna are all muscle. They're cold. I like I like they're cold, but can you catch them in there already?
You could probably use penguin meat as a fuel source for like a stove
If it's if it's greasy and fatty that would be a really good fuel source. I like she should have went with well
I should go with white look the fat of the well like the well blubber
Guys have you heard of have you heard of amber grease?
It's like more value. It's more
value than gold. It's basically
it comes out of it. It's like
it's like but it's like they
use it on all this kind of
stuff. It's uh but it's basically
very it's very expensive.
Have you heard as well blubber
sir? Where does amber grease
come from? Guys, you know,
anybody know amber grease? A
Don't do it Alex
Fuck it actually make it make the joke. No, I'm not going to
You just had to say it is you already told me
Channel and I want to be respectful because I really like
Guys I posted my video like my in my intro
And I got seventy four likes on it. Well, all right, I'm 74. We live enough today, Derek
43 I have over a thousand followers on tiktok so I monetize
I'm ready. My boy is moving up
I mean we're not looking at like 12 hours. I was monetized within one day. It's okay. It's not very difficult
But uh, you know what psyche give yourself a little no no no no no no don't over look it give your little self a little
Round of applause for a thousand. I mean it's better than 24
20 for now a thousand
One thousand 453 views 74 likes oh shit two comments
We've got it to your publicity studs for you psyche. We got it. We gotta figure out publicity
You need to love yourself more need to appreciate your compliments a little like your customers a little bit more
I mean, because you don't you don't celebrate it at all
My cop my cop my costumes. What do you say?
Your consonants, so you my confidence a compliment a compliment. Okay, but I thought that word
Wait, compliments or accomplishments?
A complimation.
Or compliments.
Can I look it up a third?
Oh, God.
All right.
Well, I'm leaving.
My bad.
No.
Complimation.
I fucked it up three times.
Just go ahead.
It's okay.
I just fucked that word up though.
Hi.
Oh, shit.
I just got in trouble following each other.
I was just I was like liking every bit or like following everybody that um liked my posts, but
Okay, I'm sorry. Mr. Big Pikes
It's a terrible feedback. Hey, Alex. What's up, Mr. Big Pikes?
Do you want to do you want to join my mission in helping psyche grow his channel? I think we I think we should do some um publicity spots
We need public for psyches. I can I can I can pull the speed I can pull out the speedo out again
Like what?
No, no, I think you know, you know would be better than the speedo. It's like if
Psyche and mr. Goff. I haven't mine. Oh, I'm not in real life. I think that would be the kind of things in mind
Shit, if I put it we could do a meet-up with but that's what I'm saying. I'm mr. Big Pipe's
I'm trying to get both of you two out of the house and y'all that y'all are reluctant
Is there a way is there a way you want me down? I'm gonna like go anywhere
Actually, what I will say is mr. Big Pipe's
He did try to he was trying to get me out
But I wasn't ready yet because my dad just died you know, but now at this point
I might be ready to leave the house. No, it's just like that stuff happened way too fast
Yeah, that was to that was too much
But that's why I'm saying we got to do some IRL publicity stunts for psyche because he's in he's in this world
I'm not pleased that he's in the IRL because I know how treacherous. I think the most famous thing
that would happen to psyche if you certainly got a boxing tournament.
I don't want to be a ball in a boxing game. Me versus all these New York people.
I want to be an oil wrestling slip-and-slide.
I don't want to be an open slip-and-slide.
That's why I'm gonna do like Alex. Okay. I was it's just hey, mr. Big fight. We'll rest
Yeah, I just feel
Mr. Big
Mr. Big, mr. Big, I said if I
Should be like your bohemian chic thing
I'm heavy girl
And I might stay heavy girl for the rest of my life
Yeah
When you get when you do the RV thing um, I'll have a place for you to park it
no fee
full hookups
If I if I take an RV out there
Yeah, yeah, cuz I'm gonna buy some land. I need to get my own
Alex this is the this is the this is the oh what I made a few months ago. Hold on. What did I make it?
It was like I'm thinking about getting one. I have a date on it. But look at what I would look at wearing though
I'll show you now.
Damn.
What?
That's you?
Yeah, it was.
It's my face.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, it's A.I.D.
Well, it's like it doesn't come in.
Yeah, but he's going to be that.
It's going to be that.
No, don't hit on him.
I'm showing you the scarf.
Look, we're both wearing a scarf.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Let me put on a scarf right now. Fuck it. Let me go. Let me. I have a scarf collection. I should show you all my
Great there, let me see. What else do I have here?
Let me put on a scarf. Let me put on that. I mean like a seizure alert on that.
Scarf for now, come on. It's good.
Well, I don't think it will cause a seizure.
Yeah, it will.
Yeah, well, it totally will.
It may be for LD, but he's not going to watch it in his car.
Well, don't do that to him. Please don't do that to him. He'll be driving. He'll be driving. Don't do it. It's not even funny
Yeah, cuz he got some people do you have that problem? Dude, how great that he drives around like after years
You know some people do have that problem. Do most people on psyches have that problem? No
They might I don't know
Watch out because I don't I don't want anyone to have like a seizure out of nowhere
I've seen that happen. It's horrible when it happens to people. Oh my god. Have you seen it happen on this panel?
Yeah, well I've seen it on panel. I've seen it in person
I've seen it like
I mean, it's like, you can show where the fuck he wants, so you want to make everyone like, oh, some people have a seat, I mean, we have some people who do have a seat here, like 10%, but...
It's horrible when that happens.
It's horrible when it happens.
It's under some of the time.
Alright, I'm going to model a mint green scarf for some of you. Okay. Here we are
when you put on
scarf
There
I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready for I
Don't know scarf weather
I'm ready. Yeah, it's starting to cool down
There I'm ready. Let's go
We're gonna go out the mister. It is starting to cool out
You know, I got that RV too Alex, I was totally down to like
I know you are I know I wasn't down
I was ready and I was I was a motion. How can a mother fucker be invited or no? I
Don't know. I mean you're gonna tell me I'm slow. Maybe I'm too slow to invite you
Yeah, I don't know this car wasn't like a nice
I'm too slow to even comprehend what you're saying right now. What are you talking about like like what's happening?
Just like a airy soft accent scars
I just want to go somewhere with a bunch of good looking men so everyone can be like who's that girl with all these hot guys who's she
Yeah
I'm not ugly I'm average
I'm at least average and I'm old so that makes me above average because I'm old and average
So Alex you admitted bars and stuff. Yeah a couple months. I'm fricking rocking out. I
Bet you are well, you've developed very well truthfully. I knew you would I knew it
I feel like I'm finally making it happen, but it's just getting started, but it's like well
Don't change because I love how you are very
Humble I like that you're a little shy. I love that little kid bit of awkwardness
That's what makes you sexy and hot. No, and you plus you got the hair
You got the height
Well, yeah, I'm single in 47. I'm at my goddamn peak. Get out my damn way
Get out my way. I'll be 47 next year. Yeah
So I do know but with mr. Big Pikes
I always he's always been a little bit of a heartbreaker, but as he's maturing he hasn't his speak yet
Not yet. How old are you now? Mr. Big Pikes? How old are you?
Yeah, you'll hit your peak at about 45
Yeah, you will yeah, but you well
No, unfortunately, because of genetics, my applause won't hit until I'm about 55.
Women in my family tend to have children very, very, very, very, very late, but I'm not going to have any kids.
You know what gets the biggest reaction is the harmonica, actually.
Well, I bet it does, because it's out of nowhere. It makes the girls think about, like, Steve Tyler from Aerosmith.
You know that song, Beaver.
Fever fever, you know what I'm talking about. Yeah
When you girls hear that they're like what it's like the pie piper
Please
Yes, yes
Fever yeah fever you ever play this song play this song mr. Big Pipe's you can I don't I don't want to strike on
Oh, that's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That's true. That
Yeah, girls like that. I know what women like. I
Know what men like Tim. That's why I'm nice. Are you not 47 and single so you know what men like but you're 47 and single
I was married once please. Yeah, what happened to it? It didn't work out did it?
Yeah, so you don't know a man once then
You divorce and you're single
And I've had a lot of really good relationships. I you don't think that I okay, and then where are they now?
Wait now and then they were so if they were so good
Would you really like to I killed them? Yeah? Oh?
Yes, you okay
So you're 47 you're single
Yes, you don't you actually don't know what men want
I do I do you wouldn't be forty-seven
You want to know where they are. Yeah, I buried them in my backyard there. They're right there
They're right there
rest in peace
Oh
So you're 47 single
I'll be 47 January and I will be single once divorce once when you're trying to tell these younger women what they want
really
Well, I'm keeping them away. There's a lot of people listening. Well, good
Good, yeah, they shouldn't listen to you. I'm not the advisor psyche is the advisor
Not me not me. Well, you're 50 years old twice divorce. Oh, I'm 50. I'm 50 now
Now I'm 50. Well, let's just make it a hundred. I'm a hundred. I'm gonna be a 45. We're gonna be 50
I want to be a hundred. I'm a hundred now. Fuck it. She's under it. I'll roll with it
He has some like automated towards women he rejects. I know he's so mean
How do I have a who the fuck are you first of all who the fuck you're projecting you it's called a project
All right, let me go. Oh, no, no, no, let me talk to him
How am I? No, let me talk to him. Hey psyche. Let me talk
You're not gonna be right back here to be back here now. It's like you let me talk to him real quick
All you can do is run
Fucking pussy
No, you're mean don't want to talk to me. How well, you know what ma'am? I don't want to be me. How am I mean?
Please explain. I will literally a little if you change. I will change my ways. Go ahead. I'm so sorry
Go ahead. No, no, I guess it's working for you. Why would I want you to change? It's not working for me
I'm hitting us. How am I mean? Please explain how I mean?
Rewind the bot and listen to yourself. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm talking to you. I'm asking you how many I am so sorry
You don't have to be sorry
You're very confrontational, but it's okay. Okay, cool. If I'm asking you how mean and you you literally have nothing
You already
Open your mouth you just say not mean for what?
What the fuck is the point of you opening your mouth
What the fuck was the point of you but you want me to double down?
What's the point of you double down now?
You didn't know I don't want to argue. Well, there you go. I don't
I'm not gonna argue. I just I don't have to show you just know what the fuck you're talking about
Okay, that's your
Yes
You win no matter what goes I well I can see I'm not gonna win
I can see. You already won. You
already did.
But I can see this one but
you're only coming here like
**** I mean he had your bag.
I'm just hanging out. I like
come to him. I know and I'm
not trying to **** that's
fine. It's it's not my
panel. That's fine. The other
He left. Oh, yeah, he's he went away cuz he doesn't like damn it. Look what you guys make him do. No, I'm back
I'm gonna go back
All right
Mr. Big Pipe is Mr. Dumb Darn
He is like he's like you're here. I'm not put an album am I allowed am I allowed to debate him or not?
You have to
I don't know. I don't know.
Well
I am I am weird you are weird Alex you are weird you think I'm trying to help you psyche
I'm trying to help you psyche what you've never helped me in your life. Like what the fuck are you talking about?
He's helped you. I'm trying to help you
Alive I want some of it. I want some of the mister if you guys like trauma
Yeah, yeah trauma. I want some of the mister if you guys don't mind
Hey, go ahead. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
He's like he's like big band I miss you big part. So you're just like a professional like
He's a he's a he plays the harmonica and the banjo at the same time. All right, well, I did I was
A white knight
Well, that's a good question, what do you tell me that?
One of the good guys
By the way, what are you white night?
Mr. Big what do you white night? Oh, maybe me. Maybe me. Maybe Mr. Big
Somebody that he knows that I love him. He knows I love Mr. Big Pikes. He knows
No, I didn't know
No, I just
I've known Mr. Big Pipe for a long time, and I know the good and the bad, and there's way more good than bad, so I love him.
I just do. I love Sly Guy.
I wasn't putting him down. I was trying to make a joke. I was just making a joke.
I was like, you know, because there's a sign that DMX saw, and the guy, it's called Damian.
And he goes, I'll be your friend to the end.
And he's like, like Chucky, he's like, just like Chucky.
And in the end, we'll both get lucky.
Yeah, it was a DMX song called Damien. Have you heard it? It's a trilogy of songs. It's really good. I believe it
It's just it's a song. No, I mean, I'm not like saying that mr.
I mean, this is your panel. I feel like I'm taking it. Maybe I should
Taking over I've got some weed. That's what it is. No, I'm gonna smoke some weed. Don't worry. Yeah, I'm gonna smoke some weed
Yeah, I'm in smoke and I got the good shit. I got live rocks. So Mr. Big Fives, you're like a microphone is like hurting my my my soul.
Hold on. I need to like. Thank you. Oh, I can turn it.
Ah, I can turn it down on my ears.
Okay, that's not helping. Okay, that's not helping.
I'll fix it all.
Microphone is like waiting. I didn't even try to fix it. Yeah.
I did. I'll do it for you. Perfect. Perfect. I'll put here. I'll put the automatic on. No, I got it. I got it.
But next time we stream on my thing, I have to set it correctly that it wasn't your microphone problem. It was me.
Well, I don't I'm not sure like I've always I've dealt with a lot of audio issues. I'm not sure if it's me sometimes
Sometimes the banjo start all mr. Big Pipes is the kickoff. Yeah, he's gonna bust out the banjo
Well, I mean it's like it's like there's too much like background noise and it was like hurting my ears
It was like it was I felt like I had like a ray gun or something in my mind brain or something
So it's like not it but I don't like it and I can't take it right now mr. Big Pipes
He needs to fix your microphone get a decent webcam
You know, regular microphone, Mr. and the Big Fives,
you're just sound, you know how it sounds?
It's supposed to sound good and not hurt your ears
because even if you play wonderful music
and it's like hurting my ears
with all the feedback and stuff.
It might not be wonderful at all times.
No, no.
I think they might play his music.
If one time I'll play them, I play his music on a loop.
I'm not sure, but no, he's fine.
I'm gonna go and slice him.
It's gonna storm here, Sam.
We're about to have a storm.
But I'm going to see them outside while it comes because I like watching nature like that.
Yeah, I do too.
I wish I would.
I mean, I do have some beautiful nature around here in the ocean nearby and then it's a beautiful
ocean breeze usually.
There's like a lot of beautiful natural trees down the block and a nice, right down the
street from like the fire department, like the city hall and stuff and the library and
So you can pretty much walk everywhere. There's this little shopping center nearby with the Whole Foods and the Michaels and the
Sorry Memphis Memphis. I want to clarify something to you. I've known mr. Big Pice a very very
very very
very
long time and
That's what that is
Yeah, yeah, that's good. That's what it is. I've just known him for such a long time.
I remember like when I first like sort of hearing your name it was like people say oh
Mr. Bigpipes is it he's like that's how it's mayors is by he's here to like get information about you and stuff
Well if I had a son
But the guys I liked to be like, I figure if I had sons, they would be along the lines of certain things.
And Mr. Bigpipes knows that about me. I care about him. I want to see him happy.
Yeah, I think he should be too.
There's a lot of people that are like just like lonely because it's like harder in this society to like, you know
The closer or the more social media and all this stuff you get the less we like connect here. He's back
Ah
So it's fine on board
My audience
I listen back.
Ooh.
I hear sirens.
I mean, can you hear me all right?
Oh, I hear you perfect.
Hey.
Why is there sirens?
Is it hurting?
Is it hurting your ears?
I turned it down.
Now it sounds better.
It's hurting psyche.
I was hurting my, but now I turned my headphones way down.
My headphones were just loud.
I usually have them right now.
Yeah, maybe you just had it up too loud.
You still hear me?
There's my microphone too low.
Yeah.
Hello, do you hear me?
There I am.
Hey, Tracy.
I can hear you.
When does the banjo start?
Whenever Mr. Big Pipes decides he wants to break it out.
Oh, you got the floor.
Oh, are we going to get some music?
Are you playing instruments on streamers?
Sounds terrible, huh?
Because, like...
No, it doesn't.
Go for it.
There's echo cancellation on, and...
I'd have to turn it all down and stuff, but...
Okay.
How many do you need a few minutes to get it ready, Mr. Big Pipes?
What is that in the chat?
Wait, is it a peep-op?
It's like the ghost guy behind the car.
Oh.
If I ain't sure, I'll prove I knew you.
Sorry.
Rather I love pipes.
How does that sound?
Sounds good.
What's it like canceling out and shit?
What's that noise?
It's egg.
It's like super loud.
Stone and steel, I'm the mountain sun.
Voice of the dawn, where the climbs begun.
Words like pillars, fire in my hands.
I build the temple on shifting sands.
And a freedom flame
I love in secret
Yet I love the same
A hidden fire
A mystic song
A banner that's kept the tribe
I love that song. Yeah. Yeah, for coin rising.
Where is that song? I want to download that song. Where is that freaking song? Is that AI?
Is it? Yeah, I made that. Yeah, I made that. I love
It's based on my astrology, like it's based on my astrology.
Oh, oh my God, I got down, you put the link in,
well DM me the link, please DM me the link on Instagram,
DM me that freaking link, I will, I want to sing that,
that is the song, I love that.
I was like grooving in the soft and I was like ready to go,
ready to go, I was like in the world
cause I just smoked some weed too.
And I was like, oh, Capricorn rising, I was like yes.
as a Capricorn.
I love that.
I'm sorry to get all excited,
but I get excited over stuff.
Yeah, that was a hot song.
I mean, you know what reminded me of?
Suddenly, from the 80s.
Remember that song?
Suddenly, life has a new meaning to me.
It's a very similar pattern.
Oh, I love that.
I love that song, Capricorn Rising.
Is that the name of it?
Yes. It's called, well, it's called, yeah, it's called, yeah, I forgot what it's called.
It should be called Capricorn Rising. That's a good song. I love that. I'm going to download that song.
A lot of my placements and stuff. Yeah, I'm trying to figure out how to get my music.
Like, I want to get, like, because I have so many songs now and I still have a few more to do.
I made it, yeah, I made a few today.
Yeah, that was a jam.
And I was like, I was into it. I was like, yes. I like this.
That was great.
I do have the song to go along with the band or two.
That's a very good song.
I like that song.
That should be your closing theme for Friday night.
Not all the time, but Friday, Friday night.
And I want to let people know.
That's a hot song.
If they're interested in, I'll do a whole thing
where I'll do a piece of art.
Oh, well, you know what? I'm Katrina in your chat. I'm looking at the chat Katrina liked it, too
She was like 80s James Bond
Yeah
Is that my profile?
Yeah, that is my profile, Capricorn Rising, Capricorn Ascendant, I mean Capricorn Sun.
That was a hot song, it was something about that song, can we hear it again?
Sure, let's play it again.
I have another song too, do you want to hear the other song first?
I kind of want to hear Capricorn Rising first, because it was good, it was really good.
and steel I'm the mountain sun voice of the dawn where the climbs begun words
like pillars fire in my hands I build the temple on shifting sands Capricorn
Secrets I keep, visions awake where the dreamers sleep
Lightning hearts and a freedom flame
I love in secret, yet I love the same
A hidden fire, a mystic song
A banner that's kept the tribe
Thank you for playing it again.
I really like the groove of that.
That's good.
Okay, when you made that song, did you have the ability to pick the vocalist?
How did you create that song?
Yeah, you used the style.
You used the style.
The style.
Okay.
Yeah, I really like how it reminded me of a combination of last Unicorn from America
Suddenly, Lionel Richie from the 80s,
I was getting a little bit of that vibe from that start.
That was nice.
For a I mean to me it's it's a regular song. I don't care if it's AI or not. I love that
Some of them are so cat and fricky catchy. I'm like, actually, this is a pretty good album. I was like
You should you should make I told you you need to make psyche music. Yeah
I mean, I'm really good. Similarly. I heard for AI music is that AI music is like trying to tell people how cool your dreams are
Well, you know, it's like, you know, like look go for it back in like have like some hope for
Look, I'm Bill with the AI
No, I love AI. I make AI music right now
We all do. Come on.
It's a way to make our dreams come true that has never been available before.
And you can download the stems with some of it because I'm going to make my Christmas album perfectly this time around.
I did make AM 2023, but it sucked.
I'm going to make an AI Alexandra Christmas album this year.
I sure as hell am.
And y'all can download it for free once I do it.
but it's gonna be great. I can't wait. I'm looking forward to Christmas this
year. Are y'all looking forward to Christmas? I'm gonna have my Alexandra, Alexandra, you know,
Christmas album, so. Well, I'm all about Christmas. It's really my favorite.
Oh my God. Well, Christmas is like too sad, kind of so close to our birthday though, right?
Well, my dad's birthday actually was Christmas. He was born on December 25th. Yeah, so I mean, for me,
Christmas has always been double. You know, and this year especially is going to be super special for me.
But yeah, I've just always been Christmas girl. I wrote a Christmas song called, It's Christmas Time.
I read it several years ago. I have my own Christmas song. I read it.
So, you know. But yeah. But no, I like that.
Capricorn rising. That's a nice
song that you put together there. I really like that.
I like the lyrics. I like everything.
My astrology book. So it's like I put it all together.
Are you a singer psyche? Do you have a nice singing voice?
I can sing like I can see I'm a deep singing voice. I can say I have I can carry a tune. I like to sing
But it's like I used to sing a little bit on the show. It's something like that
I can sing I like I like I'm the karaoke. I see
Sorry
How about I
like bony M2
The rivers of Babylon, we once were there.
Did that sound better, because I muted it and turned it up?
Oh, you were talking.
I didn't hear you.
I didn't even hear you.
I was singing really soft.
Yeah, you were singing too soft.
Damn.
That sucks.
Mr. Bigpipes, you naturally have a very soft voice, so you'd have to really, like, belt
it out when you're singing.
No, I mean, I was playing the banjo, too.
But you have a nice thing well, I thought I listen back to it earlier. I've always like I can tell that
Boy you're tuning up. It takes you a while sometimes. I mean I was trying to sing white Christmas
But it's not, it's not Christmas time yet, Mr. B5, it's bad luck to sing Christmas songs in August.
She was just talking about Christmas.
No, no, no, but she's not singing the songs, so don't sing the song in August.
Please don't sing white.
I can change the play.
Okay, I'm gonna play the other song.
Rock ballad!
disguise bathed in waters naked wise lightning cracks across the skies the
thunderstorm is me
I like that one a lie. I really do. I like I like the guitar solos on it
See it was a bit like I I heard you mr. Big Pies pick that up like it was no thing
See that's what I'm saying. Mr. Big Pies has a talent for real because any song he hears
It takes him a little bit, but he picks it up quick. It takes me like to be a band person. Oh
Okay, ten minutes
Whatever, no. I couldn't play it again, I was like listen to it.
Ten minutes.
But you already have that memorized so that was a really catchy and that was an easy progression too.
But you got it.
I hear it and I know and I like put it somewhere and then I work around my patterns from there and stuff.
Yeah, but you picked it up quick because I heard, I did hear the banjo solo, I heard it.
It was cool.
That was just cool.
I actually listened back to it. I was like, oh, I could hear it a little bit.
Yeah, I realized Mr. Big Pies does have a very good musical ability.
When you first started really doing your, like, remember, like, on good times,
you would come up and you would play the banjo sometimes,
but then you start doing it more so on your own.
And that's what I think everyone's a player after their talent, yeah.
Well, he gets jealous, yeah, he gets a little jealous, yeah.
I mean, that happens with weak men, like, anywhere I go.
And flamboyant gay men and, like, bullish lesbians, like,
like these pretenders, like, they get...
Well, you know, you have to...
What I've said for you for a long time is that you have to create your own audience
because I know pretty much who your audience would be but I
Think you'd get wrapped up too much in other people. Yeah, it's like a bunch of people that you create them
Well stop doing creative. Don't you don't need a freedom?
Like why why is this seems like it seems like everyone in my like chat like I mentioned curriculum
They'll be like like ten people. No, you know me. We'll see that's a problem. So let Rick you've been doing really good
Mr. Makepies do not
overly communicate with the substance abusers who are trying to get you to do stuff you shouldn't do you know better
Come on. I don't I've always like
Had pretty high standards for the people I communicate with. Yeah, but you do
Or something in entertainment, I'm not gonna I'm not gonna like reprimand you I'm just saying because
You know my credum consumption is pretty damn low. I take like 10 I wouldn't even bother
I mean it's look I have some credum coffee
Someone gave me some credum coffee like a bag of it and I was drinking it and I was like
Oh, this is a really amazing coffee and then before I knew it. I was like out of my mind
No
Like be careful. Just be careful, please I
Don't like
I don't even think that anyone even really needs tile and all.
I think that's a little bit strong.
All you need is a little bit of wheat, a little bit of alcohol,
cigarettes.
Let that be it.
You'll need all this crap.
I'm like, I have a lot of ice.
I have alcohol.
Well, I mean, I can't talk.
I have a lot of stuff.
And I just didn't.
So it's like the hell here.
I've been on it.
Yeah, I've been like myself imposed therapy until the fall, but seriously
Just be careful because you don't want to
You just don't want to fuck yourself up, you know
You don't want to do that. I've been out of heroin addiction since 2018 by the way. I know I
Know stay out of it
There's nothing really detrimental about it.
Yeah, I hope not.
I've never done, I don't do the 7-0-H stuff or anything.
So are you going to help Psyche make his album?
Maybe you could ask Psyche to be on this album.
Why not?
And then it won't just be A.I., it'll be A.I.
I was going to make a G.F. about the dude.
He's doing all kinds of stuff.
Psyche's very cool.
None of that music playing?
Well, Psyche knows how to put things together.
He knows what sounds good.
Well, Psyche said he's bi.
He said he's bi.
I would say like I would say like you got it here. I would say queer or maybe pansexual. Do you hear me? Hold on. Oh
I can hear you. So now you're well, what do you have? Is there a definition?
For what if we were queer or pansexual?
Or are there also there's like self-partners? I don't know so Lena Gomez called herself self-partnered
I kind of like that too, but it's oh, I like that. Well, you know, I want to be self-partnered. Yeah
Well, it's like now yeah, I mean it's like you should but I mean I've been by myself most of my life, right?
I was I was days more like for three months, but it's like very hard to like date a guy for guys to like date another guy
It's such a short attention span like women are the one thing
No, I think you're you're stereotyping
I can't believe I'm saying this to you. It's like, you know, I think well, maybe I'm supposed to um
No, you can't stereotype guy-guy relationships as being overly difficult because I've seen
some really like easy-going, seamless, long-lasting couples.
I just get in like, dating a guy, I just think I get very like, I'm very independent, I'll
put it that way.
And you probably understand how you're very independent and it's like if you have somebody
You know, the lady I had dated was trying to change everything.
Yeah, they want to take over your life.
Right, and she was like, she made like a bird's nest of blankets in my house.
And she's like, let's make a nest.
And I was like, I feel like Dick were sitting in a nest.
A nest?
Yeah, like a nest.
Or are you going to live in the nest?
You two are going to live in a nest.
I hope not.
I didn't want to live in the nest.
Yes, you were going to live in the nest.
Yeah, you had to stay in the nest with her forever, all the time.
That was her dream, I can tell.
She was definitely a big bird.
Well, one time, actually, I woke up and she was like...
A bird?
If I was an egg, I would have been late because I was like...
Oh, my God.
She was like rolled over me.
I was in the crevice of the couch, squished.
And she was like, you know...
Because she was like...
Oh, she was a big girl.
Was she bigger than you?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. I'm skinny. You can see how I'm like, you know, like,
How do you meet this woman? I know I, well, Mr. Big Pies.
I'm Facebook. I'm trying to convince, I'm trying to convince
like, to let me basically feed him.
It'd be like that. I really want to.
that movie or that I would I would let you I would let you because I will I will just whenever you're ready I will just send you food you will you will be twice the size if you if you let me like give you the proper diet I could like 300 pounds I would actually look normal at 300 pounds
I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I'm actually I
I
No, no, no one's showing the IDs. We're not
Psyche
I didn't say that big time I never said that you're like making things up
can't handle me being the same height as you?
What's wrong?
You're like being really strong.
This is a big pipe, so it's competitive.
We'll stand out.
This is a big pipe.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
No, I'm not being aggressive.
I'm just saying I'm going to know this.
No, you're competitive.
You're naturally competitive when it comes to guys.
That's to stop it.
You don't have to be competitive with psyche.
Stop it.
I'm not.
You are.
To big pipes, yes, you got all, like, I have six, three, three, three.
Okay, we're going to make, okay, Mr. Big Pies, do you want to be six four because you got nice hair. Okay, you're going to be six four.
I'm not six four.
Well, between the Harley boots that you wear and your beautiful luscious locks of hair, you're six four.
There you go.
Problem.
You're six four now.
Okay.
I mean, the basketball players.
You could claim six four if you want to.
Well, there you go. Who was it? It was Spudweb. It was Spudweb, wasn't it? No, Cliff Mealy.
Not many people remember Spudweb, man. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh, gosh. Okay, so Mr.
Big Pies, you're six foot four. Slikey, you're six foot three. I'm five foot seven. Everyone
happy? Perfect. All right, there we go.
I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six. I'm six
a pair of shoes and I know shoe size because of that.
I haven't sent them in the mail yet,
so I haven't made time to dress.
I know, what happened to the shoes?
They were in my storage unit
because I haven't talked to you in forever,
but I just finished them.
No, I finished them.
And you're gonna love them.
You're gonna love them.
And for the record, I did not send Psyche a day.
I heard your underwear. I heard that you did. I heard that I heard that you did
You could literally show it on stream. It's not addictive. I don't want to show it on stream.
Psyche is secretly seductive. I mean if it happened, I'm not going to be upset about it,
or no one's going to be upset. Psyche, because of certain things, I've seen him do it. I've watched
some of Psyche's old streams and some panels. The reason that some people are mad with Psyche,
Psyche embodies the power of seduction.
I do know that about you, Psyche, and I love it.
I love it, I love it, you do, you do.
He tried to seduce me, but he couldn't.
I was trying to seduce Alex, but I was trying to seduce Alex.
No, he didn't.
All right, no, no.
Psyche also seduced me in a certain way.
He seduced me intellectually, and I love it.
I have a surprise for Alex.
OK, what is it?
I hope this work is going on.
Psyche, you can send it to Alex if you want.
Ooh, I like that.
Is that me?
But you got to show your reaction live and be honest
as your experience.
I do like this.
I like this picture.
Is it the picture?
No, I might not be the picture.
I feel like sometimes like that picture,
like when it's late at night, I'm drunk and I'm angry.
Yes, that is me.
Absolutely.
Absolutely. I wish I could be like a lavender purple like that, like seriously. I love that color.
I wish that like I could be that. That would be nice. That's what I want to be, a lavender.
Okay, well that was that was a performer like going into is something I would definitely consider like
I feel I don't know like why not okay, but I don't think you should do that mr. Big Pipe's no
Are we talking about in adult movies? No, no, please don't yeah, like Alex
Morals about it like it's like if you go to a restaurant you wouldn't be able to know you're too sensitive
You need to be a musician be a rock star. Do not be a porn star. It's not like having a second
These tapes kind of wrap start with that one. Oh
Yes, that's good. That's it. I was going yes. I think I have that outfit actually. I used
Yes, I like the black
Capricorn. Yeah, that could be, yeah, Capricorn rising. If I, if I, if I like, recreate that song, I'm going to put that in the background, in the blue screen, or the blue screen, yeah.
Oh, come on.
Oh, no, this always happens.
Whenever I talk to Mr. Big Pies,
what, we're looking at him talking about that.
He always.
When I talk to Mr. Big Pies, Mr. Big Pies, at some point in Mr. Big Pies's life, he
will date a really hot black girl.
I already know this about him.
I don't know when it's going to be.
It's going to be when you're like 45, 46, if you're still single.
Well, hell, you might be married knowing you.
I think I was like, she's only black.
takes on the back of his motorcycle, rides off into the sunset, they have it up there.
Oh my God, you're asking me. And then he finds out he's training.
No, no, no, no, she'll she'll be petite. She'll she'll be a petite girl and that's what it was because he was in the small
Ari for at one point I remember that you you were you you know what a little bit wait she's you say T
Ari no small Ari remember oh dude that's like 29 she's like 29 I know but you you were digging her for a little bit
She is hot. She's a hot girl. You know, it's like nothing. I'm just saying you you sometimes like black girls
I know that about you. Yeah. Yeah. I'm attracted to sometimes you like black girls
Yeah, well you like all girls you're very universal with your taste
extremely so, a little too much so sometimes, but you're
eliminated. I don't think that like race is a deciding factor
in anything. Well, it's not at all. It's just not at all. Like
what the fuck? Well, it depends. You can't say prettier.
Anyone, any ethnicity can be equally pretty. You can have a
girl. Just give me a feeling like right away. And it's like
wow. But that could be pretty conceptions that you have.
It could be it doesn't have no many girls really, but it's like when I get that feeling it's like damn
I want to fucking like date that check or some shit
Well, I have about eight types of men that I am extraordinarily
It's rough to eight types. I've narrowed it down eight types. And if I see you that I'm like
And like a half of it has to do with like 80s doctors or something
Um, one of the types, yes, I do like the Sebastian Bach type. Absolutely. Not, not now. He didn't age very well, but, um, in the past, yes, yes, but there's eight types that I do, like, in their various looks, various ethnicities, um, I realize I did have certain types.
My mother my mother Alexandra. Yes. Is that where your your accent comes from? You're like neutral. Um
Between my mom and my dad. I don't I don't I shift a little bit. I do shift but um my mom Alexandra
You know
I know exactly what your times are and i'm like really mom
Yes, I do. And I've created a chart because she does that.
That's how she talks. Like that's very like, man.
That is how she talks. That is powerful.
It's like a, like...
If you think...
You're being held like verbally hostage a little bit.
My mother, oh my God.
Or like...
My mom is me times a hundred, seriously, when it comes to certain things.
Think you've been wasting yourself over the past few years, but it's not too late. It's cold as fuck. Oh
I know
now first off I
Don't know why I
Just I don't understand why
That's not I can tell that I can hear the narcissist like it reminds me of the you're seeing whiplash. I
Don't want to see it. Whatever it is. I don't want to see it
No, it's a great movie with J.K. Simmons.
It's about a drummer and a teacher, a music teacher.
A drummer?
Oh, yeah.
I've seen that movie with a drummer.
Yeah, he's a narcissistic, abusive music conductor.
No, no, that's not good, buddy.
This is J.K. Simmons and Miles Teller and Whiplash.
OK.
But holy shit, but yeah
Definitely, I have a certain kind of but she's awesome. She's not quite awesome. I would
But yeah, well, what would you say to you young man?
I was like the disrespect is like I better not I better not do it. I better not. I better not. I better not do it. I better not. I better not do it. I better not. I better not do it. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I better not. I
That that would just be the end of it. It would that's that's my mom and the older I get
The more it comes out
So, so yeah, so what's going on mr. Big five?
your
Something is going on
What's going on? I'm just chilling dude like I always say that I am like I don't know
I got some gigs coming up and some jams coming on
Just kind of you need to have you thought about putting the band together. Have you done that yet?
Yeah, I mean some really cool people lately
Talking to him about music and like possible settles is it's people that I would like
Well, I'm hoping that you're gonna kind of follow the MC frosty pamp pattern because he was uh, oh, yeah, I'm sure yeah
That's yeah, same same just don't end up with a bitchy girlfriend cuz I'll miss you
If you do
That's what happened
You can't have a bitchy girlfriend. I
Want to take out your attention I get pretty
Wild I bet you good good good good
Like the comp the complements and like or it's just even like I don't know. It's kind of crazy
Like well, yeah
I'll see some of that. I just like taking videos of me and then like I'll go to the bathroom
Oh, really and I just tell the guy just to say like hey
You know, it's just stuff like that like walking around. It's like
Trying to be humble, but just know that everyone's alike. How's that do well?
I'm the manager this week. Do you want to come back on I?
Hope that you become I I've always thought that like you're gonna be more of a songwriter
then a front guy
but
Just don't stop with your music, please because you're doing really good and I'm really just I'm glad you're doing what you're doing.
I mean, it's just it's kind of starting but it's like everything I ever like.
So I want to be this good before I do it so that does happen it's happening so.
Yeah, and I can honestly fall back on being like
I'm in I'm it sounds crazy. I may be one of like the better players in the fucking region like
Well, you know what a lot of people have talent it's like a little bit more than talent because there's so many people with talent
it's about like
Partly luck the right place at the right time, but part of the
Yes, yeah, I think right no, it's like
Attention or like liberty isn't important to
Could I like I just want to get better?
One of your $10 readings if you don't mind all right, give me a second walking inside
Sure pipes, I gotta get on my other phone. Mr. Big Pies. You want a reading from psyche? Yeah, sure
Thank you, man, hold up I
Think that the big pipes needs a psyche reading
Is there a question you have mr. Big Pies or is this a general energy or
Yeah, I kind of had a cocky manifestation a little bit ago. A cocky manifestation
cocky. It was like, I think I'm going to sign my first autograph within a year.
Well, that's good. If you like, like, how do you, well, not manifestation. Do you mean like vision?
Yeah, it's like I just saw these situations and that's kind of weird that I mean, that's a level of slavery where someone wants like
Your signature because they liked what you did. It's like, oh, you know, I don't think anyone really out of grass nowadays
You know, it is weird, but I think it will happen. I think it will happen to some degree within a year. Maybe I
Think you should focus on actually like a solid album
Oh, no, no. All right, musically. Yeah, I could do that. What I was trying to do is just to like
Play my shit and like play these fucking pretty songs that have like
meaning and
History in St. Louis, Missouri too with like John Hartford and stuff. Oh, so you you want to make music that's like, you know regional
Well, I mean this where I'm starting now. I'm in St. Louis. So
Well, you're never going to live in St. Louis.
What are you thinking about, Mr. Big Pops?
I'm headed out first.
You like it.
You don't have to trust me.
Really?
Mr. Big Pops, what are you thinking about?
Because there's kind of some weird stuff coming up.
What are you thinking?
What is weird to you, I don't know.
Well, OK.
Well, it sounds like you're almost like a story, OK?
So it starts out with a straight card.
So there's this guy feeding the lion.
It's like, this is about you have some natural strength
no catching more of flies with a bit of honey than you do with vinegar or sugar with vinegar or something like that
yeah you can put some randwraps over it, poke some holes
okay hold on oh why did you don't please don't be stupid just just
I'm not I mean that's how you trap
no we're not talking about I mean it's a metaphor it's a metaphor okay so
yeah it's like I'm not talking about catching anything okay
get in but you can't get out
Mr. McVibes I don't want you to pick up the energy
Also, Mr. Big Pipe, so you've been fighting right like so there's been like this
It feels like being ganged up on and like a lot of it says who's the real monster?
It's like trapped who's the monster and the things that Frankenstein is the villagers
Can I see that one again? Yeah, sure. Thank you
Queen Frankenstein it says trap 2
There you go
Okay, but he's but he's bigger and like you know, but also so you have the strength and stuff like that
And maybe you can defend yourself because also we have
This is kind of interesting. We have this judgment card that came up next to the star
Okay, I'd say there's like I'd say there's been a maybe a positive judgment for you because the stars usually like make a wish card or like a
He's a positive
Manifestation and you maybe the star power you're looking for but that's gonna be maybe up to this judgment and I think you know through
We'll probably be some worthy of that right and then
Okay, we also have this in the middle of the deck. We have the queen of pentacles. Okay, so the queen of pentacles is very
You know earthy woman. It's sensual. This one has like a bat
I think that's like a we that shape she's making is like
Like that kind of powerful
Okay
And maybe it's like some kind of secret society pose or something. I know you like armpits too. So she's like
You really like armpits you're that's like, you know, Capricorn is associated with the armpits actually it is because it's like
What's the word it's like?
I don't know, but there's some kind of like, it is.
Can I do it with the armpit?
I'm sorry, I'll look it up a little bit.
But there's a queen in the middle of the deck,
so everything's revolving around it.
Around you there's this, you're growing them in energy,
and there's some kind of abundance around.
Also, okay.
We have a couple things and so it's like we have this woman or man or woman right there the four of Cubs
and so there's been some kind of like really like
Somebody being very thoughtful. Okay, right there
And so like maybe you can thought but also we have this night of a swords energy
Which is like kind of a henchman energy also like you know can take out someone's head with his words or you know a verbally
Swords our words for you know, you don't have to be the weapon, right?
It may be better for if we take don't take don't take off some of these heavy stripping types
It's just a metaphor, right? But we do have a we do have under that
I'd say you have a good chance of coming across like dirt wean, right?
Okay, this queen of wands actually, that's like Norman Bates from Psycho, or you know,
I'd say it's Mother.
But then we have, finally we have this reunited Mrs. and Reconciled, it says the monster
comes home.
So maybe somebody or something that you know you had a conflict with, and maybe you like,
you know, had demonized the person, maybe you're going to have a reconciliation or just
I would watch out for that. Let me see some advice from Mr. Big Pipes though. Is there a good card of advice from Mr. Big Pipes?
I know he's not listening, but you know what? Maybe he can play this back. Mr. Big Pipes, you have this suit of penicillin.
Dude, I'm locked in. Why would you say that?
Okay, the king of penicillin.
I'm locked. The word of advice is the king of penicillin.
I can't. Just slow down, brother. Take a breath.
Okay, we said count to four. She said you're dragging out with the music. Okay, stop it stop there mr.
Vets might forget but you got you know, you got this king of pentacles as the advice is as the man who has everything
The advice is to like, you know continue working on your abundance and you might be able to master that
You know, I think actually you're not a little bit everything else will it everything else will follow. Okay, just
master that abundance and then
First you get the money, then you get the woman, then you get the car, then you get the woman or something like that, I don't know what's happening with me.
The Harley?
Yeah, then you get the Harley, then you get the woman.
First you get the money, then you get the, I don't know, how'd that go? Does anyone know what I'm talking about?
Get the woman and then get the money.
Well.
First you're gonna have to get your attention span because you didn't have a very long attention span for that reading Mr.
Big Pikes. I think he lagged out. I mean, I'm not poor by any means.
So didn't we say you're poor? No one's talking about.
Actually, like some people do.
Well, the reading was saying that you're coming into abundance from times.
Yeah. See, you were paying attention to the reading.
Yeah, I mean, at times I am.
Okay, never mind, Mr. Big Pies.
Sometimes I do come up.
Maybe it'll sink in some other stuff.
It was a good reading.
Well, I heard the reading, and I know Mr. Big Pies.
I think that you are on point with the reading.
I've given you my thoughts.
Watch it back. Watch the reading back, Mr. Big Pies,
when you're not six so close off
in one and paying attention.
Dude, I was tuned in.
I was tuned in.
The only reason I responded was...
is because he said, if I sort of played the piano when you were talking to me, right here, I'm listening to you, I was vibing with it, dude, I was vibing with it, jeez, I was giving you like, instead of like talking, I was just playing my, what I felt through my fingers, my instrument.
Well, I enjoyed the reading. I thought it was a good way to speak. I just want to rewind it back if you remember
It's it's at a it's at about six hours into the yeah, I'm chilling like hey, you know what you could just like a
Here's a suggestion for your channel just tech wise it if you want to you whenever you do readings or
You know like the $10 readings you should make a special
playlist of shorts, because you can make the shorts up to like a minute and it'll make you rank higher in the YouTube algorithm.
You should, you know, make the keyword astrological or tarot or both, readings, commentary, live stream, initial reaction, you'll get way more views and traffic to your channel, you know.
I'm like, I, I, like, because I've got into the shorts, yeah, the shorts, because there's some actual sites that will like, you know, go and like, you know, Google out a number of them, you know, from the videos and like, my old videos and like, you know, there's some people that passed away from the show, I want to find there, I'm on the show, I want to find, you know, I want to advance my interview, I want to cut up that interview into like little things and then, and you got to, anything that, any interviews, you just always link it back to the original video, right?
I feel like I'm ready for the I'm ready to get bigger because my channels just kind of solve a little bit like
Numbers wise they said a good way because 75% of the people that come here are returned people
But then it's like the 25 drivers do you have like like what range is almost 3,000. I think I'm almost at 2700. Oh
Well, look at this point. Yeah, you got to keep growing. You'll keep growing. That's great
Yeah, and sometimes they sometimes it's like it's like planting a tree
It's like it's not just gonna have been doing this for like a little bit less than a year of the live streams
And it's like sometimes it's like
It takes a long time to grow out of that seed phase and then it's like, you know, it's like, you know, it takes a second for a while while it's like, so much smaller and there's competition and people trying to vandalize the tree and stuff, and then you, you know, you just keep growing and then as soon as it becomes very, very strong, and you know, you just do it.
You'll do it.
I have a marketing degree and so I like I'm interested. Oh, do you? Oh, we have a secret we have a secret
Little tip bit of info. Yeah, that's good
Minor fashion merchandising and a major in marketing. Oh
fashion merchandising
It was gay, it was pretty gay, but you know what, we got to do a fashion show, I was the
math class.
I got all A's because math class was the best math class because it was merchandising
math and so it was just like, you just learned how to like, you know, it was too basic.
It didn't subtraction percentages and stuff, I was like, hey, I learned this in like fifth
grade.
And then I did it. I think my hardest math class was actually about my my last two years
I was a statistics class, but that I still think I got an A in that so
Okay, and like when I was like ready to but I was like almost 30 years old by that point
I was like 26 or something like that
Then I went right to work. That's not almost 26 is not almost 30. Come on. Yeah. Well
From then I was a blur the Saturday term was really brutal and now I'm coming in
Yeah, I've been in Saturday second return coming by when I'm 45. I think that's when it happens
There's a lot of things I don't remember and it really like
aggravates me because I really like there there are certain years of my life
where they were blurs you're just like what happened wait a minute
I'm in the world
Alex oh I was gonna say yeah what's up pipes
I kind of want to just ask you questions about music and how you play your pianos well
I was well, I'm I'm I'm kind of debating right now whether to go or not because I do have my music
Yeah, I like when you started talking I was like, yeah, I was well
It's because because I hear you playing your music and it's influencing me to
Yeah, I do. I have my shit set up right now.
I have it set up.
I changed my top because I was getting a little cold.
Why did we do that?
It's you, Mr. Big Pies.
You, Mr. Big Pies, it influences me.
He does, yeah.
I'm thinking about because when you were starting to play before
and we heard Capricorn rising because I got that melody in my head now.
And I'm like, ooh, I want to make some music.
And then I heard Mr. Bigpipes.
And I'm like, oh, I feel like doing some music right now.
You know?
I'm using it as magical.
And I still do it on Oscar.
Yeah, I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about doing some music right now.
Because I got my keyboard, and I haven't set up.
Well, I got to connect my.
I
Software to my keyboard, but I can do that in like a few seconds. I think I'm gonna go yeah
Yeah, that's that because I'm in that mode I'm not like exactly ready when I'm ready
I will let you go psyche because I'm not
quite there. I smoked some weed. I've been partying with you today. Like really, that's why I say you
provide a service. You don't even realize what kind of service you provide because sometimes for me
to get into the mode to be creative, I need to vibe with a kindred spirit and thank you for existing.
Man, thank you for existing. Thank you for not only existing but for being a bright light in the
And someone who helps people, and someone who has a kind heart.
You see the real heart of people.
I think it was good people, it was good people.
I see it.
Who has a good heart?
Who doesn't have a good heart?
Yeah, people get mad at me, though, because I'm vocal about it.
you know a shoesteller or you know and then it's like also people like to say
oh you know women and stuff like that and you know women are so
Thank you for loving women because I can tell that about you not and I'm not
talking necessarily you know sexual you love women because you love the female
energy thank you as a representative of women across the
Plain of existence and beyond. I think he is like he for
For being like getting women things seriously because well because
Women are like yeah, they bring the life to the earth
I think that they're like without women men would just be like, you know wrestling each other in the mud all day
women cosmetically go out and like, you know
Start to like, you know, create like they're basically
Abundance comes through them like they're just like you know women are abundant and it's like and then it's like
men will also want to
Impress them and that's good. Yeah
Well, I think men need to let go of like look I understand in certain cultures and a lot of
circumstances women are weak and they need men to care for and protect them. I totally understand
Figure the world out and when we do
We do become very strong and when we become strong
for some reason it really like even if the guy is like
Your friend or more than a friend if he realizes your ability to
Be the provider or the producer or whatever
They get mad
And yeah, it's ego anger. Yeah. Yeah. And then they, they, they, they like, they like almost want you to fail. But for no reason, only because they want to be, I guess, more of the.
Caretaker, but what if like the girl is better at caretaking because that happens sometimes
Well, sure. I mean, no, I mean a lot of the time it's like and there's so many women that do the job alone, too
I mean, it's like and so yes, and
Yeah, women it can be like they they can't they can't be providing the thing is it's like you know a lot of women just like our
No, you have the Disney princess programming as they go
You know find the the wild prince and then you know tame him a little bit and you know
That that fairy tale that hardly ever it sometimes it works out, but it's rare
Right, I mean that's the thing is like I have that programming where I'm I'm waiting for some like kind of white horse to like come up
And like you know save me and rescue me and take me out of this place and stuff like that
But it's like it will never happen. You know because it's like people have come to
You know, it's like art. I don't know
Approaching me is like well, you know, here's here's you've got to position yourself if okay, if you want someone
To rescue you or to I don't really I mean
I mean I mean facetious, but it's like, you know, it's like
Oh, okay, I was like not facetious, but it's like, you know
You know how the Disney always has the guy in the white horse and they won't you know
She's like yeah house with like the family and stuff like that
And this is like
I love that excitement, but then it's like the excitement is dangerous. Like it is like
you know, I like danger, but then it's like I don't want the consequences of
Exactly excitement from what?
Excitement of just an adrenaline rush of life
But you know, especially what I'm saying like, you know, you meet like a bad boy kind of a guy and like
And then he's like, you know, he's just kind of exciting life, but he might have you like, you know, yeah, it's like
I'll say
She like shopped it from the store came out and I was waiting in the car and like, you know
Not knowing she was like doing it, but it's like then like the manager came out
I see it and like he like jumped on the hood of her car and like she like started speeding out of the parking lot
That's a really extreme circumstance that you should not have been in okay. That's not. I know I know
Okay, you got it that doesn't count
That doesn't count. No
I've been assaulted by I've been seven in the year before you know, it's like in the year
You've got a fault it
Yeah
How are you in this situation?
Where is Glendale is that the valley is that in that is that a San Fernando Valley?
Glendale it's like it's like north of Los Angeles like it's like near and they kind of like yeah, that's it's
Valley, okay. Yeah
You're there
It's very Armenian a lot of Armenian. Yeah, there are a lot of Armenians there. I remember that I know pretty much where
Glendale is I know Glendale. Okay, you were in a trap house in Glendale
Yeah, my was this this woman from Chicago came down and like with my friends
He was actually African-American guy his name was Eddie and he was just like I think he was very attractive
But you see a straight guy and everything he was kind of crazy and
Like he but he brought her from Chicago. He ended up getting arrested and first like stealing cars
And so then she like was like, okay. Well, I'll be here for whatever until like, I don't know
It's basically tries to move in and stuff like that
Please send it up having to take her out of sheep. She punched out my window and like, but you know, oh my god
Stealing cars is a red flag
Was this linked to the porn industry in any way
Because when I was in the porn industry and I was because I know that area
Okay
I mean, oh, there's a bunch.
Yeah.
I had more like, man.
I had some lap dances.
Oh, my gosh.
The guy.
I bet you did have some lap dances.
I bet you did.
Man.
I'll tell you the wild stories later on.
What year was this?
That's what I want to know.
2008, 2016, 2002.
Actually, I lived in Glendale.
Oh, this was recent.
It was in Glendale.
That's for a Ronda Rousey training, actually,
with an Armenian.
Ronda Rousey. Yeah, he was a total like scammer fucking shady weirdo
Well, when I think about Glendale, I kind of think about the smell like clone from a mile away you can smells clone from like
Everywhere, but you don't know I just did a whole stream about how like over the internet through media sources
You don't know what anything smells taste or no, I had Armenian neighbors. All right. They lived like
They smell by
No, I've known a lot of really cool Armenian people
They're very look the Armenian people are very aesthetic they're very beautiful people actually
They're all
No, your culture is to be very pristine, very pristine, very clean.
Well, they're trying to overpower the smells of like,
No, they're not.
You're being racist, actually.
Okay, you are.
It's like...
Why would they...
I'm trying to think of why I would want to put that much clone on.
Because they like the smell, they like strong smells,
but they don't do that because of the base smell.
It gives me a headache.
Well, you don't you know what mr. Big Pies? I remember on a stream you were saying
That you had issues being around women doing their nails
So that's why it's you. I heard no way the smell. I heard you say it
No, you had an issue with women doing their nails
I remember it smell. Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, actually, I don't like that. Okay. Okay. I know I'm right
That was something that's happened to me like
I wasn't asking for an apology
Nail polish remover is very sensitive. My whole point is it's offensive. I don't know why you would deny it because I have when it comes to certain things
I do have a good memory even though I'm slow. Yeah, no like I mean that's an example of why I would be offended by strong smelling profium is like
nail polish remover
Gives me a migraine
You're not supposed you're not supposed to smell clone you're supposed to discover
So, you rub it on your shorts or whatever your pants.
You know what, that would be such a good tagline for a scent.
You're not supposed to smell it, you're supposed to discover it, and the whole ad campaign
could revolve around an explorer.
looking to discover something like in a far away place somewhere to be in
Mr. Big Pies I hope you just I hope Mr. Big Pies discovers a woman this woman's vagina someday
I've been I've been there once and uh it was interesting it was like I don't know it seems
like you're like getting offended by it or something but no he's right he's right he's
like I don't know how much you know how much I'm appreciating being on this
panel right now I really am extensively so she appreciates like my levels of
humor mr. Big Pipe if you ever find the vagina I'll join you in a
No, you said all you said last time was I needed to buy a rainbow wig off Amazon. You want you to buy it, right?
What?
You said buy a rainbow and wig and then I'll
No, I never saw yeah
Yes, you said and you said one time you said you'd make out with me if I brushed my teeth and took a shower
When you said that I ban you for months
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't know psyche. Can you? No, I don't. No, no, it's not. It's not graphic. I don't want to. I don't want to shock. I have my box. No, let's
Yeah, you can show the dick pic if you want.
Okay, let me see it. I want it. Oh, well, it's not my panel. You don't have to show it. I don't want you to
I can show I don't want you to breach any TOS or anything. I don't think it
It's a little graphic. It's just I have a boner and box to break
Well, they can't show a boner on it. Come on, dude.
Well, I mean, that could just be how, you know, maybe I'm like a...
Boner dysfunction
But it was a chick alright, it was a chick that took the picture
Okay, okay, I'll send it to you on on on another side
Okay, okay
Yeah, send it to me. I'll DM don't put on your on your stream. No, I remember a time you ask me go inside
are you really yeah I want it I'm gonna go inside hold up hold up hold up hold up
hold up okay oh my god okay I don't remember I can tell you just saw it I'm
gonna tell you saw it when you said oh my god oh my god I'm gonna say Alex you
I
Wait, is that right?
Yeah, it looks like it's a you know, sort of diamond bit of balloon animal down your pants
Oh my god, I believe you send me these photos really thinking you're welcome
Really was like
Let me know when you see the picture.
I like a mystery.
I got too low.
It's a little mysterious.
It's not mysterious.
It was too much.
I saw too much.
Okay.
Let me see.
There you are.
Okay.
Oh, I think I hit down on him, okay.
Okay, here you go, Alex.
Okay, I'll wait for the picture.
Oh, you gotta cam up. You gotta cam up.
No, don't show it.
I'll just cam up.
No, he wants to make it.
I want to see your jaw drop.
Don't show them.
Yeah, your reaction.
Is that real?
Yeah.
That's what I said, that's what everyone asked, is it real, like fuck that there?
Huh.
It's not like a pair of extra large socks in your hands.
I don't know what's going on.
It's kind of, seriously, it didn't send me the real...
I mean, I'm going to have to zoom in.
Yeah.
I think it's real.
But the reason, no, I think it's real, but it looks larger because if you look really
close, it's the way that the fabric is kind of, you know, the way that it's stretched.
It looks a little bit, yeah, so don't look at the fabric, look at the actual, you know,
But it is big, it's big, it looks big to me, yeah.
Under the burlap sack, you're looking like you're a potato sack.
I don't need to see a nude, no, I don't need a nude.
I mean, just be, just be, no, no, no.
Okay.
We've already seen each other.
But you're tall, so it makes sense, like it would be kind of like you wouldn't, you wouldn't
you know, being tall, I would think you would want to right, right.
So I mean, three or height is 8.36 inches, 8.36 inches.
Wow.
And it's like, you like, look at the three six of it.
And I can, I can even like look at that.
I mean, do you find that, well, let me ask you, have you encountered situations to where women were a little intimidated by your size?
Oh, yeah.
Holy shit.
You wouldn't really be able to go for super small girls with that size, you know.
It's Shaq
Well, I mean ladies that's really not all girls like the other girls I can fist and shit if that's really
And then I would say it's a good size but keep it to yourself. You don't need to like hell the world. I mean
So I mean, yeah, I would say that you I would say that you're definitely well in doubt. Yeah, thank you. Yeah, I agree
No, I mean, yeah
Somebody had to maybe wail in doubt. It's like I'm in the 99
I'm in like with the over 99 percentile
like not only dick size, but height too.
Well, I think you did stop, you know,
elaborating at this point.
Yeah, we heard it at this point.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to be like, you know,
if I had, I think it would be a good choice.
I don't want to hear about your penis anymore, okay?
I'm not sure it's straight, okay, stop it.
It's another avenue, I could...
Oh my God!
What?
What do you mean another avenue?
What are you talking about?
And to like...
No, don't, well, is you, let me...
Well, you'd have to have your own production company because no guy goes into the adult
industry only doing straight unless he creates his own production company because the work
does dry up.
No, I want to do VR porn.
Oh, virtual reality?
Really?
You want to do that?
Are you going to be the model or is it going to be a point of view?
How are you going to do that?
This producer from Evil Angel like oh, yeah
No
Lena moon
No, it's like she's really cool like I know what you'd like to do a movie with her a scene
I don't know if I would like she could probably like I mean she produces now so we wanted the first trans VR scene
No, it wouldn't be in oh you see oh you watch
Considering all the trouble I went through that I told you about Mr.
Bigpipes throughout my foray in the adult industry, why would you want to make
that choice? I'm just asking because it's not a good choice.
No, I'm not saying I'm gonna subject myself to sex trafficking. I'm gonna be in
charge, I feel, if I ever did something like that.
You know what you need to do before you do that, why don't you just serial date?
Why don't you just date a bunch of girls back to back and then you'll get that out of your system?
Why don't you just want to be straightforward? It's like if I'm trying to like if I want to make
You will cut off a lot of avenues for yourself if you make that choice.
So don't act like nobody warned you, okay?
I would not make that choice.
I mean, you do whatever you want to do.
I'm just telling you, I don't think that's a good decision.
And I'm telling you as somebody who actually-
I guess it's more of like, if we're talking about that,
like you guys are all talking about your phrase into, you know,
I actually made that decision and I would say it's not a good decision, you know if I could I don't regret it
I don't like it or anything, but I'm just saying
You know if somebody like me had approached me back then
I would not have, you know, made that decision because they would have told me, so I was telling you.
I'm a single guy.
Okay, well, be a porn star, be a super porn star, Mr. Big Pipe.
I mean, you already got the name.
That's what you'll call yourself, I guess, Mr. Big Pipe.
You know, but there is no porn industry anymore. It's everybody making their own content
Yeah, it's not like you're gonna get to work with Jenna Jamison. It's not like
You know, Brie Olson or any of those girls are still active anymore every note. There's nobody there, but
Move to the valley. I'm just
Well, then go ahead and do it
I'm just like kind of flexing you know that's what you should you know what
like you see like all right now that you see that and it's like I back to the big
pipes triple X IRL addition that's what it's gonna be it'll just be called mr.
big pipes that's a great porno it sounds like a poor thing it works with
music well that's what all those guys are about I mean look I know Vince
It sounds like you're going to be like Vince Boyer, but he's old.
He's, I don't think Viagra would help him at this stage, but I could come to a call.
I just like how he said that, like, is that real?
If I actually, that's like the response, like, it is.
Well, look, if you, but what I'm saying is why not, like, preserve that for whoever the next love of your life is going to be?
How can I not feel cool about like I can't really advertise it, but it makes me feel lucky. Well, you did you got it
You just advertised it. You just did you advertised it
You know
I've you chest is that what that's something I like
5d dick pictures. Okay, you know what they play though. Hold on in a
Street pipes
Okay, I don't know. You're gonna be rocking each man. Mr. Big Pipes, yeah.
Um, hey, oh yeah, Spunky, yeah. I got you Spunky. I'm coming. Spunky's, uh,
I didn't do that for Spunky. Doing her, uh, special...
Astrological thing. Have you heard of Sabian symbols though? You have to Sabian symbols are that word before say yeah
No, you're thinking about the Greek etymology
sabotage
What?
Yeah, what what's about sabotage? It's a Greek word for like sabotage sebo. What is sad?
What is a Sabian?
Oh, you're saying maybe it means star. It means from the stars. It means sabotage. Yeah
Yeah, it's like pointed and pointed projectile like it was meant in war
And actually it was a type of you that slaves would work
Slaves would wear these wooden clogs and they would throw them into the mission
I like to hang up on them. I'm getting bored with them stupid types.
Well, why are you asking me? It's not my panel. This is your panel.
Yeah, I'm like, yeah, I just want to be respectful.
It's like, you know, I just like, I don't want to like, say,
if you're having a good conversation with them, I won't be mad.
No, I feel like I think that you have personality conflicts.
I'm surprised that you've been talking as long as you have, actually.
It's not my panel.
Starts talking nonsense. No, he's he's he's messing with you a little bit. I could tell
Have a good night, mr. Big Pikes. I love you. I do love him
But he's annoying sometimes and he fucks with your mind sometimes
It's just he's just annoying me. It's like I can't be my fuck because
I've been mind game-banged, like my mind's already, you know...
Oh!
So, it's like, I've had enough people play with my mind to feel it together.
Mind game-banged.
Well, it happens.
Look, I feel like, look, I was...
deeply mind-fucked not too long ago, extremely so, but I can't even be that mad about it because when he tried to get aggressive
I just cut it off and I was like ha ha not doing too much damage, but
Yeah, you got to be careful sometimes
Yeah, no, it's like, you know
There's programming all throughout our lives and we're in a cultural program is us and then there's
Specific things that they want to do that. They mean they detect a purposefully
Poison the culture in order to poison some of the people in the culture right and it's like they perfectly
Make people sick they purposely you know one people to get worse if they want people to unalive themselves
They want people to do all
All kind of things so mr. Big Pipes keeps coming trying. He's desperately knocking on the door on the studio door and mr. Big Pipes
Uh, you know, take five, Mr. Big Pipe, take five.
I mean, it's like, Mr. Big Pipe, it's like, you know,
not terribly, music, I was not terribly...
It's just because I'm on here.
It's, it's cause like, you know, I'll tell you my,
can I give you, can I give you an Alexandra reading?
Mr. Big Pipe's got jealous that I'm talking to you.
He gets a little...
That's what it is. Yeah. Well, he should be I'm charming. I'm charming and it's okay. Well, you know what it's like
Tell us I mean it's like what it's like. I have a friend. It's like you know people have to be jealous
I mean it's like
People the guys in these communities are worse than some of the girls in these communities
Oh, yeah, you will you will see that there's it's I've seen it happen with
Victrola I saw it happen with Trisha. I've seen it happen with crystal Marie. I've seen it happen with
Vita
Sometimes the guys feel like as a woman because there's really not that many women who to do like, you know, regularly come regularly come on the panels
Unless it's like a woman's panel
The guys get possessive over you
They do
That's a bit of what I've noticed other guys contend with on occasion
Yes
Well, like I said, it's like girls do too
It's like women are like, women are like, you know, maybe, maybe like 5% of guys are in there like, oh, you know, they're consideration
on the on the on these dating sites and then it's like but
Women it's like 60% of women like guys like 60% of the women, right?
And so it's like well, I mean the men that they create is impossible
The men want the women nowadays to be like the AI women
But we're real
No, they want the AI and they want you to look like the AI woman
That look is coming back there's like a very cookie cutter
Artificial even the sort of look and I thought it was going away for a while
And I was like, oh, I bet these young girls are going to be so happy they can finally relax,
you know. And now all of a sudden there's a resurgence of the artificial again.
And that's a little intimidating.
Well, yeah, well, I mean just thinking about plastic surgery and thinking how much like you know
It's so much how it's marketed so much for these PBLs and lips and the people were getting these tough lips for a while and they
Overdoing the plastic surgery some of the people like
It's really something that you should what should be very lightly done because it's like, you know
It's you got to be careful. Well, I don't like seeing the girls who are really young like super young getting into it because a lot like you don't really know what your look is or what you really look like when you're a woman until you hit about 35.
I would say 35. Maybe some people would say younger. I don't think so. I think 35.
That's what you're gonna look like really and if you get the plastic surgery like when you're 25
Well, you know your body's gonna change
Yeah, well, it's like I mean 25 the brain subs growing but still yeah
You'll go through like you know if you're pregnant and stuff like that then that will like do you know anything around your life
Oh, it's kind of out the window at that point. It's it's good to like my you know after like five kids my mom had five kids
And so yeah, that's a lot of kids. Yeah, I remember you said that
Yeah
You said you have a big family too. It's like I do have like, you know, 15 16. Yeah
My mom only had my mom had two kids, but I but then here's what's crazy. Okay?
Her mother had like 13 kids. Okay, so that's why there's a lot of us and
then
Aside from my mom and her closest sister everyone else had like
between three and six kids
sometimes more
So
Yeah, yeah, well my mom had five kids
Yeah, we'll see you birth to five, but you know there's there's seven of us
Wow, you know, I'm looking at some some of my demographics, you know my it says I have a my show
Which is really this is really crazy for a terror show. It says male 58 percent point one
female 41 percent point eight
I would have thought you would have more women, honestly, and that's always most most tarot advertised channels would but yeah
It's a
More majority man here. What and what worse? What are they from? Okay, so where are they from? Let me look at all time
All time. Lifetime it says they're from US, Canada, UK, Australia, Germany, India, Indonesia,
Netherlands, Turkey and Portugal. That's the top country. Interesting. Interesting.
And then the ages it says...
25 to 34, 24%, 35 to 44, 35%, 45 to 54, 24.6%, 56 to 64, 13.5%, 65 plus 2.4%.
Okay.
Well, that's good. I mean, that's that's pretty good. I mean, you're kind of to split down the middle
You're close to 50-50. I think in time you're probably gonna have more women, but maybe not
Maybe you're different
Maybe a lot of males feel comfortable
Listening to and talking to you because you do have a certain energy about you. That is very
You're pretty confident
You know ghost he like he wrote me in the back-back shot. What are you saying?
He said oh, it's already white if he wasn't really mad, but I kicked him off the show.
He's being rude though, and it's like he's not, I don't know.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna, I am gonna let you go. I'm gonna let you go, because I'm sure, well, thank you for
letting me on your panel, and I had so much fun today.
Thank you. I definitely did.
This week and we'll talk soon about
And uh, bye sweetie.
And Spunky, I'm gonna get off right now.
I'm gonna start working on yours
and I'll probably try to get you
within the next couple hours, Spunky, okay?
Love ya.
Bye.
Have a good night.
Bye Alex.
Bye.
Thank you guys for being here.
Actually, I'll play a couple songs on the way out.
Play a song and I'll play like a video
and then that'll be it.
Here we go.
This song for you guys.
The trivia's rigged, but we still say yes.
Purple curtain swaying, mods holding the line.
We're psyche at the helm, everything's fine.
We've dodged a few bombs in the chat room nights.
Still made it through with our fan-pied tights.
No shame and Speedos, tacos on the plate.
Fish are not, we're here.
We said
and psych
and stripes parade fish tacos on the table another wild charade he's hitting
on the straight men come on lose that shirt meanwhile beaters on the hotline
yelling till
Christine's with fozzy bear
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare
It's here.
Why is Arthur?
I've been missing in my sleep